Maureen	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Andre	B-PER	O
is	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
look	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
list	O	O
of	O	O
curves	O	O
needed	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
global	O	O
assets	O	O
(	O	O
August	O	O
Board	O	O
meeting	O	O
)	O	O
one	O	O
more	O	O
time	O	O
before	O	O
I	O	O
forward	O	O
it	O	O
to	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
will	O	O
make	O	O
sure	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
do	O	O
not	O	O
request	O	O
FX	O	O
and	O	O
inflation	O	O
(	O	O
CPI	O	O
,	O	O
PPI	O	O
,	O	O
etc.	O	O
)	O	O
curves	O	O
when	O	O
only	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
curves	O	O
will	O	O
actually	O	O
be	O	O
used	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
valuation	O	O
process	O	O
and	O	O
to	O	O
determine	O	O
which	O	O
inflation	O	O
index	O	O
is	O	O
needed	O	O
.	O	O

Typically	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
receive	O	O
both	O	O
FX	O	O
and	O	O
inflation	O	O
from	O	O
you	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
both	O	O
curves	O	O
may	O	O
not	O	O
always	O	O
be	O	O
used	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
hope	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
give	O	O
you	O	O
some	O	O
time	O	O
savings	O	O
by	O	O
eliminating	O	O
any	O	O
nonessential	O	O
requests	O	O
.	O	O

For	O	O
now	O	O
,	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
list	O	O
of	O	O
countries	O	O
for	O	O
which	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
probably	O	O
need	O	O
the	O	O
FX	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
inflation	O	O
curves	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
send	O	O
the	O	O
specifics	O	O
per	O	O
Andre	B-PER	O
later	O	O
today	O	O
.	O	O

India	B-LOC	O

Philippines	B-LOC	O

Bolivia	B-LOC	O

Jamaica	B-LOC	O

Guatemala	B-LOC	O

Venezuela	B-LOC	O

Columbia	B-LOC	O

Puerto	B-LOC	O
Rico	I-LOC	O
CPI	O	O
only	O	O
(	O	O
I	O	O
need	O	O
historical	O	O
inflation	O	O
data	O	O
,	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
)	O	O

Panama	B-LOC	O

Brazil	B-LOC	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
current	O	O
data	O	O
already	O	O

China	B-LOC	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
current	O	O
data	O	O
already	O	O

Euro	B-MISC	O
inflation	O	O
only	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
not	O	O
certain	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
needs	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
London	B-LOC	O
Underwriting	O	O
/	O	O
IV	O	O
group	O	O
but	O	O
will	O	O
request	O	O
the	O	O
information	O	O
from	O	O
them	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
not	O	O
done	O	O
so	O	O
already	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
!	O	O

Cindy	B-PER	O

David	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Cindy	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Please	O	O
send	O	O
us	O	O
the	O	O
list	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
curves	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
will	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
revalue	O	O
our	O	O
international	O	O
assets	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
August	O	O
Board	O	O
meeting	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Maureen	B-PER	O

Philip	B-PER	O
,	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
decline	O	O
the	O	O
invitation	O	O
with	O	O
regrets	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
too	O	O
many	O	O
commitments	O	O
right	O	O
now	O	O
.	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O
Kaminski	I-PER	O

Dear	O	O
Vince	B-PER	O

Just	O	O
a	O	O
quick	O	O
message	O	O
to	O	O
follow	O	O
up	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
email	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
sent	O	O
you	O	O
recently	O	O
inviting	O	O
you	O	O
to	O	O
speak	O	O
at	O	O
our	O	O
forthcoming	O	O
congress	O	O
,	O	O
Risk	B-ORG	O
2001	I-ORG	O
Australia	I-ORG	B-LOC
,	O	O
which	O	O
is	O	O
taking	O	O
place	O	O
in	O	O
Sydney	B-LOC	O
on	O	O
20	O	O
&	O	O
21	O	O
August	O	O
2001	O	O
.	O	O

Have	O	O
you	O	O
had	O	O
an	O	O
opportunity	O	O
to	O	O
consider	O	O
the	O	O
invitation	O	O
yet	O	O
?	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
aiming	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
the	O	O
programme	O	O
printed	O	O
next	O	O
week	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
would	O	O
really	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
know	O	O
as	O	O
soon	O	O
as	O	O
possible	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
available	O	O
to	O	O
speak	O	O
at	O	O
this	O	O
year	O	O
's	O	O
congress	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
working	O	O
from	O	O
our	O	O
Hong	B-LOC	O
Kong	I-LOC	O
office	O	O
for	O	O
this	O	O
week	O	O
only	O	O
(	O	O
Tel	O	O
:	O	O
+852	O	O
2545	O	O
2710	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
be	O	O
contacted	O	O
by	O	O
phone	O	O
there	O	O
or	O	O
by	O	O
email	O	O
.	O	O

Kind	O	O
regards	O	O
.	O	O

Philip	B-PER	O

Philip	B-PER	O
Annesley	I-PER	O
Conference	O	O
Producer	O	O
Risk	B-ORG	O
Waters	I-ORG	O
Group	I-ORG	O
+44	O	O
20	O	O
7484	O	O
9866	O	O
+44	O	O
20	O	O
7484	O	O
9800	O	O
www.risk-conferences.com/risk2001aus	B-MISC	O

Beth	B-PER	O
has	O	O
made	O	O
our	O	O
reservations	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Round	O	O
Table	O	O
Friday	O	O
night	O	O
(	O	O
5/18	O	O
)	O	O
at	O	O
Sullivan	B-ORG	B-PER
's	I-ORG	I-PER
Steak	I-ORG	O
House	I-ORG	O
for	O	O
6:30	O	O
.	O	O

See	O	O
you	O	O
all	O	O
there	O	O
-	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
ling	O	O
overdue	O	O

Paula	B-PER	O

Paula	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Thanks	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
.	O	O

Will	O	O
you	O	O
drive	O	O
on	O	O
that	O	O
day	O	O
?	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Beth	B-PER	O
has	O	O
made	O	O
our	O	O
reservations	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Round	O	O
Table	O	O
Friday	O	O
night	O	O
(	O	O
5/18	O	O
)	O	O
at	O	O
Sullivan	B-ORG	B-PER
's	I-ORG	I-PER
Steak	I-ORG	O
House	I-ORG	O
for	O	O
6:30	O	O
.	O	O

See	O	O
you	O	O
all	O	O
there	O	O
-	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
ling	O	O
overdue	O	O

Paula	B-PER	O

FYI	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Anne	B-PER	O
,	O	O
Mike	B-PER	O
will	O	O
call	O	O
you	O	O
regarding	O	O
Sarah	B-PER	O
.	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O
,	O	O

As	O	O
I	O	O
mentioned	O	O
in	O	O
my	O	O
voice	O	O
mail	O	O
,	O	O
Mike	B-PER	O
Roberts	I-PER	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
hire	O	O
Sara	B-PER	O
Woody	I-PER	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
recent	O	O
MBA	O	O
grad	O	O
from	O	O
Rice	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
into	O	O
his	O	O
group	O	O
.	O	O

However	O	O
,	O	O
when	O	O
we	O	O
were	O	O
talking	O	O
about	O	O
this	O	O
position	O	O
,	O	O
Mike	B-PER	O
compared	O	O
Sara	B-PER	O
to	O	O
Elena	B-PER	O
.	O	O

Elena	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
title	O	O
is	O	O
admin	O	O
coordinator	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
Sara	B-PER	O
should	O	O
not	O	O
have	O	O
this	O	O
title	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
honestly	O	O
do	O	O
not	O	O
think	O	O
that	O	O
Elena	B-PER	O
should	O	O
also	O	O
.	O	O

Admin	O	O
coordinator's	O	O
do	O	O
primarily	O	O
administrative	O	O
work	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
suggest	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
compare	O	O
Elena	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Sarah	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
duties	O	O
/	O	O
level	O	O
to	O	O
other	O	O
Sr.	O	O
Spec.	O	O
in	O	O
your	O	O
group	O	O
such	O	O
as	O	O
Kenneth	B-PER	O
Parkhill	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Sevil	B-PER	O
to	O	O
determine	O	O
if	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
equivalent	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
if	O	O
their	O	O
scope	O	O
of	O	O
responsibilities	O	O
and	O	O
experience	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
as	O	O
broad	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
the	O	O
latter	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
case	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
could	O	O
place	O	O
both	O	O
Sara	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Elena	B-PER	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
specialist	O	O
job	O	O
group	O	O
(	O	O
the	O	O
salary	O	O
range	O	O
is	O	O
33	O	O
-	O	O
66	O	O
K	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
advise	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Anne	B-PER	O

Clayton	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Thanks	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
appreciate	O	O
all	O	O
your	O	O
help	O	O
.	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Vince	B-PER	O
-	O	O

Good	O	O
news	O	O
.	O	O

Martin	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
box	O	O
is	O	O
working	O	O
wonderfully	O	O
-	O	O
I	O	O
'll	O	O
have	O	O
everything	O	O
transferred	O	O
to	O	O
it	O	O
and	O	O
give	O	O
him	O	O
the	O	O
keys	O	O
by	O	O
Friday	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
was	O	O
(	O	O
another	O	O
)	O	O
nice	O	O
deal	O	O
for	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
save	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
21,000	O	O
in	O	O
real	O	O
money	O	O
this	O	O
way	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
cash	O	O
refund	O	O
Sun	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
giving	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
for	O	O
our	O	O
other	O	O
server	O	O
,	O	O
using	O	O
a	O	O
box	O	O
that	O	O
was	O	O
n't	O	O
being	O	O
used	O	O
by	O	O
anyone	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
happy	O	O
about	O	O
this	O	O
.	O	O

Clayton	B-PER	O

Iris	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Congratulations	O	O
.	O	O

Anne	B-PER	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
,	O	O
include	O	O
this	O	O
info	O	O
in	O	O
Iris	B-PER	O
'	I-PER	O
file	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Michael	B-PER	O
:	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
putting	O	O
the	O	O
paperwork	O	O
together	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
have	O	O
interest	O	O
in	O	O
meeting	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
can	O	O
present	O	O
unique	O	O
investment	O	O
opportunities	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
have	O	O
access	O	O
to	O	O
now	O	O
.	O	O

Most	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
contact	O	O
with	O	O
financial	O	O
advisors	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
past	O	O
has	O	O
consisted	O	O
of	O	O
them	O	O
suggesting	O	O
a	O	O
mutual	O	O
fund	O	O
,	O	O
telling	O	O
me	O	O
to	O	O
invest	O	O
in	O	O
Home	B-ORG	O
Depot	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
Sun	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
Coke	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
pass	O	O
off	O	O
their	O	O
banks	O	O
'	O	O
biased	O	O
research	O	O
reports	O	O
as	O	O
something	O	O
valuable	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
above	O	O
services	O	O
provide	O	O
no	O	O
value	O	O
to	O	O
me	O	O
personally	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
can	O	O
present	O	O
opportunities	O	O
such	O	O
as	O	O
access	O	O
to	O	O
private	O	O
equity	O	O
or	O	O
hedge	O	O
funds	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
other	O	O
ideas	O	O
with	O	O
strong	O	O
growth	O	O
potential	O	O
and	O	O
low	O	O
correlation	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
S@P	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
'd	O	O
listen	O	O
.	O	O

John	B-PER	O

John	B-PER	O
-	O	O

We	O	O
'll	O	O
get	O	O
the	O	O
paperwork	O	O
together	O	O
and	O	O
sent	O	O
to	O	O
you	O	O
for	O	O
naked	O	O
options	O	O
.	O	O

At	O	O
some	O	O
point	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
'd	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
talk	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
diversification	O	O
strategy	O	O
in	O	O
more	O	O
detail	O	O
--	O	O
perhaps	O	O
over	O	O
dinner	O	O
or	O	O
a	O	O
quick	O	O
meeting	O	O
after	O	O
the	O	O
markets	O	O
close	O	O
?	O	O

Michael	B-PER	O
Gapinski	I-PER	O
Account	O	O
Vice	O	O
President	O	O
Emery	B-ORG	B-PER
Financial	I-ORG	O
Group	I-ORG	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
,	I-ORG	O
Inc.	I-ORG	O
713-654-0365	O	O
800-553-3119	O	O
x365	O	O
Fax	O	O
:	O	O
713-654-1281	O	O
Cell	O	O
:	O	O
281-435-0295	O	O

Michael	B-PER	O
:	O	O

Appreciate	O	O
the	O	O
idea	O	O
.	O	O

However	O	O
,	O	O
with	O	O
my	O	O
natural	O	O
long	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
not	O	O
looking	O	O
to	O	O
really	O	O
trade	O	O
around	O	O
the	O	O
position	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
believe	O	O
ENE	B-ORG	O
will	O	O
continue	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
range	O	O
bound	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
in	O	O
case	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
forgo	O	O
50	O	O
%	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
option	O	O
premium	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
price	O	O
targets	O	O
of	O	O
where	O	O
I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
lighten	O	O
up	O	O
exposure	O	O
to	O	O
ENE	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
use	O	O
calls	O	O
to	O	O
implement	O	O
the	O	O
stategy	O	O
.	O	O

To	O	O
that	O	O
regards	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
noticed	O	O
I	O	O
was	O	O
not	O	O
approved	O	O
to	O	O
sell	O	O
naked	O	O
calls	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
that	O	O
ability	O	O
in	O	O
order	O	O
to	O	O
hedge	O	O
some	O	O
exposure	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
of	O	O
unexercised	O	O
vested	O	O
options	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
look	O	O
into	O	O
that	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

John	B-PER	O
.	O	O

John	B-PER	O
-	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
looking	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
recent	O	O
pullback	O	O
in	O	O
ENE	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
thinking	O	O
it	O	O
might	O	O
be	O	O
an	O	O
opportunity	O	O
to	O	O
buy	O	O
back	O	O
the	O	O
calls	O	O
you	O	O
sold	O	O
.	O	O

Of	O	O
course	O	O
,	O	O
you	O	O
would	O	O
then	O	O
be	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
position	O	O
to	O	O
sell	O	O
calls	O	O
again	O	O
if	O	O
the	O	O
stock	O	O
makes	O	O
a	O	O
bounce	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
not	O	O
sure	O	O
that	O	O
ENE	B-ORG	O
@	O	O
75	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
place	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
maybe	O	O
@	O	O
73	O	O
.	O	O

Call	O	O
me	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
're	O	O
interested	O	O
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	O
Gapinski	I-PER	O
Account	O	O
Vice	O	O
President	O	O
Emery	B-ORG	B-PER
Financial	I-ORG	O
Group	I-ORG	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
,	I-ORG	O
Inc.	I-ORG	O
713-654-0365	O	O
800-553-3119	O	O
x365	O	O
Fax	O	O
:	O	O
713-654-1281	O	O
Cell	O	O
:	O	O
281-435-0295	O	O

Notice	O	O
Regarding	O	O
Entry	O	O
of	O	O
Orders	O	O
and	O	O
Instructions	O	O
:	O	O
Please	O	O
do	O	O
not	O	O
transmit	O	O
orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
regarding	O	O
your	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
account	O	O
(	O	O
s	O	O
)	O	O
by	O	O
e-mail	O	O
.	O	O

Orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
transmitted	O	O
by	O	O
e-mail	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
accepted	O	O
by	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
responsible	O	O
for	O	O
carrying	O	O
out	O	O
such	O	O
orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
.	O	O

Notice	O	O
Regarding	O	O
Privacy	O	O
and	O	O
Confidentiality	O	O
:	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
reserves	O	O
the	O	O
right	O	O
to	O	O
monitor	O	O
and	O	O
review	O	O
the	O	O
content	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
e-mail	O	O
communications	O	O
sent	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
received	O	O
by	O	O
its	O	O
employees	O	O
.	O	O

Notice	O	O
Regarding	O	O
Entry	O	O
of	O	O
Orders	O	O
and	O	O
Instructions	O	O
:	O	O
Please	O	O
do	O	O
not	O	O
transmit	O	O
orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
regarding	O	O
your	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
account	O	O
(	O	O
s	O	O
)	O	O
by	O	O
e-mail	O	O
.	O	O

Orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
transmitted	O	O
by	O	O
e-mail	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
accepted	O	O
by	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
responsible	O	O
for	O	O
carrying	O	O
out	O	O
such	O	O
orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
.	O	O

Notice	O	O
Regarding	O	O
Privacy	O	O
and	O	O
Confidentiality	O	O
:	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
reserves	O	O
the	O	O
right	O	O
to	O	O
monitor	O	O
and	O	O
review	O	O
the	O	O
content	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
e-mail	O	O
communications	O	O
sent	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
received	O	O
by	O	O
its	O	O
employees	O	O
.	O	O

Notice	O	O
Regarding	O	O
Entry	O	O
of	O	O
Orders	O	O
and	O	O
Instructions	O	O
:	O	O
Please	O	O
do	O	O
not	O	O
transmit	O	O
orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
regarding	O	O
your	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
account	O	O
(	O	O
s	O	O
)	O	O
by	O	O
e-mail	O	O
.	O	O

Orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
transmitted	O	O
by	O	O
e-mail	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
accepted	O	O
by	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
responsible	O	O
for	O	O
carrying	O	O
out	O	O
such	O	O
orders	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
instructions	O	O
.	O	O

Notice	O	O
Regarding	O	O
Privacy	O	O
and	O	O
Confidentiality	O	O
:	O	O
PaineWebber	B-ORG	O
reserves	O	O
the	O	O
right	O	O
to	O	O
monitor	O	O
and	O	O
review	O	O
the	O	O
content	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
e-mail	O	O
communications	O	O
sent	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
received	O	O
by	O	O
its	O	O
employees	O	O
.	O	O

Who	O	O
cares	O	O
??????	O	O

Please	O	O
note	O	O
that	O	O
effective	O	O
immediately	O	O
my	O	O
email	O	O
address	O	O
has	O	O
changed	O	O
to	O	O
Sean.Cooper@ElPaso.com	B-PER	O

He	O	O
just	O	O
rescheduled	O	O
to	O	O
Wednesday	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
about	O	O
dinner	O	O
on	O	O
Wednesday	O	O
after	O	O
that	O	O
?	O	O

Your	O	O
buddy	O	O
Beau	B-PER	O
invited	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
about	O	O
prior	O	O
to	O	O
that	O	O
or	O	O
after	O	O
that	O	O
on	O	O
Tuesday	O	O
.	O	O

not	O	O
really	O	O
...	O	O

already	O	O
have	O	O
plans	O	O
on	O	O
thursday	O	O
.	O	O

are	O	O
you	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
NYMEX	B-ORG	O
candidate	O	O
cocktail	O	O
hour	O	O
Tuesday	O	O
?	O	O

oh	O	O
god	O	O
is	O	O
there	O	O
an	O	O
agenda	O	O
.	O	O

Would	O	O
dinner	O	O
Thursday	O	O
work	O	O
instead	O	O
.	O	O

not	O	O
really	O	O
...	O	O

already	O	O
have	O	O
plans	O	O
on	O	O
thursday	O	O
.	O	O

are	O	O
you	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
NYMEX	B-ORG	O
candidate	O	O
cocktail	O	O
hour	O	O
Tuesday	O	O
?	O	O

oh	O	O
god	O	O
is	O	O
there	O	O
an	O	O
agenda	O	O
.	O	O

Wednesday	O	O
does	O	O
n't	O	O
work	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
about	O	O
Tuesday's	O	O
at	O	O
3:30	O	O
Houston	B-LOC	O
time	O	O
.	O	O

i	O	O
completely	O	O
agree	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
meeting	O	O
once	O	O
a	O	O
week	O	O
for	O	O
1	O	O
-	O	O
2	O	O
hours	O	O
with	O	O
all	O	O
6	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
just	O	O
to	O	O
make	O	O
sure	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
moving	O	O
forward	O	O
and	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
an	O	O
update	O	O
and	O	O
anything	O	O
and	O	O
everything	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
only	O	O
concern	O	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
take	O	O
the	O	O
boys	O	O
away	O	O
from	O	O
their	O	O
overwhelming	O	O
task	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
do	O	O
you	O	O
guys	O	O
think	O	O
.	O	O

John	B-PER	O

OK	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
move	O	O
my	O	O
weekly	O	O
meeting	O	O
to	O	O
Tuesday	O	O
.	O	O

Monday's	O	O
starting	O	O
next	O	O
week	O	O
at	O	O
4	O	O
???????????????	O	O

Wednesday	O	O
does	O	O
n't	O	O
work	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
about	O	O
Tuesday's	O	O
at	O	O
3:30	O	O
Houston	B-LOC	O
time	O	O
.	O	O

i	O	O
completely	O	O
agree	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
meeting	O	O
once	O	O
a	O	O
week	O	O
for	O	O
1	O	O
-	O	O
2	O	O
hours	O	O
with	O	O
all	O	O
6	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
just	O	O
to	O	O
make	O	O
sure	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
moving	O	O
forward	O	O
and	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
an	O	O
update	O	O
and	O	O
anything	O	O
and	O	O
everything	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
only	O	O
concern	O	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
take	O	O
the	O	O
boys	O	O
away	O	O
from	O	O
their	O	O
overwhelming	O	O
task	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
do	O	O
you	O	O
guys	O	O
think	O	O
.	O	O

John	B-PER	O

Not	O	O
yet	O	O
.	O	O

Did	O	O
you	O	O
happen	O	O
to	O	O
sign	O	O
your	O	O
employment	O	O
agreement	O	O
?	O	O

Please	O	O
respond	O	O
to	O	O
request	O	O
below	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
.	O	O

John	B-PER	O
Lavorato	I-PER	O
has	O	O
requested	O	O
the	O	O
attached	O	O
report	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
is	O	O
concerned	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
allocation	O	O
amongst	O	O
categories	O	O
-	O	O
in	O	O
particular	O	O
,	O	O
Real	O	O
Time	O	O
Traders	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
would	O	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
review	O	O
the	O	O
entire	O	O
list	O	O
and	O	O
let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
in	O	O
agreement	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
presentation	O	O
by	O	O
tomorrow	O	O
evening	O	O
,	O	O
if	O	O
possible	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
at	O	O
x	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
any	O	O
questions	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
understand	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
those	O	O
comparisons	O	O
,	O	O
however	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
reality	O	O
is	O	O
if	O	O
we	O	O
lose	O	O
Dean	B-PER	O
(	O	O
which	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
if	O	O
we	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
pay	O	O
65	O	O
k	O	O
+	O	O
10	O	O
k	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
end	O	O
up	O	O
hiring	O	O
a	O	O
replacement	O	O
at	O	O
75	O	O
-	O	O
80	O	O
k	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
is	O	O
pretty	O	O
easy	O	O
math	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
know	O	O
it	O	O
seems	O	O
like	O	O
a	O	O
stretch	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
the	O	O
market	O	O
for	O	O
hourly	O	O
traders	O	O
is	O	O
very	O	O
strong	O	O
right	O	O
now	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
this	O	O
done	O	O
ASAP	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
reviewing	O	O
the	O	O
request	O	O
for	O	O
an	O	O
employment	O	O
agreement	O	O
renewal	O	O
on	O	O
Mark	B-PER	O
Dean	I-PER	O
Laurent	I-PER	O
.	O	O

Juan	B-PER	O
communicated	O	O
some	O	O
numbers	O	O
to	O	O
me	O	O
and	O	O
when	O	O
reviewing	O	O
this	O	O
request	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
ask	O	O
you	O	O
to	O	O
consider	O	O
the	O	O
following	O	O
:	O	O

Current	O	O
Salary	O	O
:	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
47,500	O	O

Job	O	O
Group	O	O
:	O	O
Specialist	O	O

YE	O	O
PRC	O	O
Rating	O	O
:	O	O
Satisfactory	O	O

Original	O	O
Proposition	O	O
:	O	O

Base	O	O
Salary	O	O
65	O	O
k	O	O

1	O	O
Year	O	O
Agreement	O	O

$	B-MISC	O
5,000	O	O
signing	O	O

Revised	O	O
Proposal	O	O
:	O	O

Base	O	O
Salary	O	O
:	O	O
55	O	O
k	O	O

1	O	O
Year	O	O
agreement	O	O

$	B-MISC	O
5,000	O	O
signing	O	O

Business	O	O
Case	O	O
:	O	O
If	O	O
we	O	O
offered	O	O
Dean	B-PER	O
55	O	O
k	O	O
or	O	O
60	O	O
k	O	O
it	O	O
would	O	O
still	O	O
constitute	O	O
a	O	O
over	O	O
a	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
10,000	O	O
increase	O	O
(	O	O
approximately	O	O
25	O	O
%	O	O
)	O	O
and	O	O
taking	O	O
into	O	O
consideration	O	O
he	O	O
was	O	O
rated	O	O
as	O	O
satisfactory	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
specialist	O	O
level	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
top	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
salary	O	O
range	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
specialist	O	O
is	O	O
66	O	O
k	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
would	O	O
still	O	O
give	O	O
him	O	O
room	O	O
to	O	O
progress	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
current	O	O
job	O	O
group	O	O
should	O	O
he	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
promoted	O	O
.	O	O

Secondly	O	O
,	O	O
he	O	O
will	O	O
still	O	O
out	O	O
price	O	O
performers	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
job	O	O
group	O	O
that	O	O
are	O	O
excellent	O	O
and	O	O
strong	O	O
performers	O	O
respectively	O	O
eg.	O	O
Paul	B-PER	O
Thomas	I-PER	O
,	O	O
Jason	B-PER	O
Choate	I-PER	O
,	O	O
Todd	B-PER	O
DeCook	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Peter	B-PER	O
Makkai	I-PER	O
.	O	O

Salary	O	O
Listing	O	O
in	O	O
Job	O	O
Group	O	O
:	O	O

Maria	B-PER	O
Valdes	I-PER	O
superior	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
62,500	O	O

Paul	B-PER	O
Thomas	I-PER	O
excellent	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
55,008	O	O

Jason	B-PER	O
Choate	I-PER	O
excellent	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
60,008	O	O

Todd	B-PER	O
DeCook	I-PER	O
strong	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
42,008	O	O

Peter	B-PER	O
Makkai	I-PER	O
strong	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
47,500	O	O

Let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
your	O	O
thoughts	O	O
....	O	O
then	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
run	O	O
it	O	O
by	O	O
Oxley	B-PER	O
.	O	O

Are	O	O
we	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
attend	O	O
?	O	O

Transmission	B-MISC	O
Expansion	I-MISC	O
and	I-MISC	O
Systems	I-MISC	O
in	I-MISC	O
Transition	I-MISC	O
Conference	I-MISC	O
Feb.	O	O
5	O	O
-	O	O
8	O	O
,	O	O
2002	O	O
,	O	O
Miami	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O

OVERVIEW	O	O

This	O	O
conference	O	O
will	O	O
examine	O	O
the	O	O
business	O	O
and	O	O
regulatory	O	O
challenges	O	O
to	O	O
U.S.	B-LOCderiv	O
electric	O	O
systems	O	O
in	O	O
transition	O	O
in	O	O
effectively	O	O
expanding	O	O
transmission	O	O
capacity	O	O
to	O	O
meet	O	O
new	O	O
demands	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
larger	O	O
and	O	O
more	O	O
competitive	O	O
regional	O	O
markets	O	O
emerging	O	O
under	O	O
FERC	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
RTO	O	O
initiatives	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
conference	O	O
will	O	O
review	O	O
the	O	O
parameters	O	O
of	O	O
these	O	O
challenges	O	O
and	O	O
possible	O	O
solutions	O	O
to	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
will	O	O
examine	O	O
technology	O	O
options	O	O
and	O	O
new	O	O
business	O	O
models	O	O
for	O	O
transmission	O	O
expansion	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
will	O	O
analyze	O	O
emerging	O	O
proposals	O	O
for	O	O
effective	O	O
transmission	O	O
planning	O	O
and	O	O
pricing	O	O
,	O	O
including	O	O
market	O	O
-	O	O
based	O	O
pricing	O	O
alternatives	O	O
to	O	O
FERC	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
traditional	O	O
pricing	O	O
methods	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
conference	O	O
will	O	O
also	O	O
discuss	O	O
what	O	O
it	O	O
will	O	O
take	O	O
in	O	O
legislative	O	O
action	O	O
and	O	O
regulatory	O	O
initiative	O	O
to	O	O
achieve	O	O
an	O	O
efficient	O	O
regime	O	O
for	O	O
ensuring	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
nation	O	O
has	O	O
a	O	O
reliable	O	O
grid	O	O
and	O	O
regional	O	O
trading	O	O
system	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
brochure	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Conference	O	O
and	O	O
associated	O	O
Workshops	O	O
can	O	O
be	O	O
obtained	O	O
by	O	O
clicking	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
link	O	O
below	O	O
:	O	O
<	O	O
http://www.euci.com/pdf/trans_expn.pdf	B-MISC	O
>	O	O
<<	O	O
http://www.euci.com/pdf/trans_expn.pdf	B-MISC	O
>>	O	O

Electricity	B-MISC	O
Market	I-MISC	O
Design	I-MISC	O
Conference	I-MISC	O
March	O	O
25	O	O
-	O	O
26	O	O
,	O	O
2002	O	O
,	O	O
Atlanta	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
Georgia	B-LOC	O

I	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
check	O	O
something	O	O
in	O	O
969	O	O
's	O	O
2000	O	O
tax	O	O
return	O	O
.	O	O

Who	O	O
has	O	O
the	O	O
2000	O	O
tax	O	O
return	O	O
file	O	O
for	O	O
969	O	O
?	O	O

Essie	B-PER	O

Sonya	B-LOC	O
City	I-LOC	O

07/30/2001	O	O
05:17	O	O
PM	O	O

<	O	O
Embedded	O	O
Picture	O	O
(	O	O
Device	O	O
Independent	O	O
Bitmap	O	O
)	O	O
>	O	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
that	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
for	O	O
you	O	O
since	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
know	O	O
any	O	O
of	O	O
these	O	O
people	O	O
.	O	O

WHO	O	O
:	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O

WHAT	O	O
:	O	O
Happy	O	O
Hour	O	O
for	O	O
John	B-PER	O
Suarez	I-PER	O

WHEN	O	O
:	O	O
Today	O	O
at	O	O
5	O	O
pm	O	O

WHERE	O	O
:	O	O
The	O	O
Front	O	O
Porch	O	O
217	O	O
Gray	B-LOC	O
St.	I-LOC	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
571-9571	O	O

WHY	O	O
:	O	O
Today	O	O
is	O	O
John	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
last	O	O
day	O	O
at	O	O
EBS	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
is	O	O
NOT	O	O
an	O	O
Enron	B-ORGpart	O
-	I-ORGpart	O
sponsored	I-ORGpart	O
event	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
do	O	O
you	O	O
feel	O	O
about	O	O
taking	O	O
on	O	O
another	O	O
company	O	O
?	O	O

Essie	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Leon	B-PER	O
have	O	O
proposed	O	O
xferring	O	O
Co.	O	O
1691	O	O
to	O	O
your	O	O
world	O	O
(	O	O
see	O	O
below	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
you	O	O
concur	O	O
?	O	O

Please	O	O
let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
Monday	O	O
morning	O	O
.	O	O

Regards	O	O
,	O	O

Vicsandra	B-PER	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
not	O	O
already	O	O
made	O	O
these	O	O
decisions	O	O
,	O	O
Essie	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
guidance	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
helpful	O	O
.	O	O

Patty	B-PER	O
Lee	I-PER	O
Corporate	O	O
Tax	O	O
x35172	O	O
EB	O	O
1774	O	O

Please	O	O
see	O	O
my	O	O
comments	O	O
in	O	O
red	O	O
below	O	O
.	O	O

Essie	B-PER	O

Essie	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
recommend	O	O
where	O	O
these	O	O
companies	O	O
each	O	O
fit	O	O
within	O	O
the	O	O
new	O	O
organization	O	O
?	O	O

If	O	O
possible	O	O
,	O	O
can	O	O
you	O	O
also	O	O
give	O	O
an	O	O
indication	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
rank	O	O
-	O	O
1	O	O
through	O	O
5	O	O
?	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Patty	B-PER	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
entities	O	O
that	O	O
may	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
change	O	O
groups	O	O
or	O	O
be	O	O
assigned	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
group	O	O
.	O	O

18T	O	O
-	O	O
EI	B-ORG	O
Indonesia	I-ORG	B-LOC
Operations	I-ORG	O
LLC	I-ORG	O

This	O	O
entity	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
in	O	O
TIS	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
SAP	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
nor	O	O
Hyperion	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
2000	O	O
tax	O	O
return	O	O
has	O	O
no	O	O
income	O	O
,	O	O
assets	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
liabilities	O	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
corporate	O	O
data	O	O
sheet	O	O
for	O	O
this	O	O
company	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
this	O	O
entity	O	O
seems	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
inactive	O	O
since	O	O
it	O	O
's	O	O
creation	O	O
.	O	O

86M	O	O
-	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
Net	I-ORG	O
Works	I-ORG	O
LLC	I-ORG	O

Despite	O	O
the	O	O
name	O	O
,	O	O
this	O	O
entity	O	O
appears	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
MTM	B-ORG	O
company	O	O
.	O	O

Per	O	O
September	O	O
financials	O	O
,	O	O
this	O	O
company	O	O
has	O	O
about	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
3	O	O
M	O	O
of	O	O
MTM	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
about	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
8	O	O
K	O	O
of	O	O
expenses	O	O
,	O	O
nothing	O	O
else	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
next	O	O
5	O	O
companies	O	O
were	O	O
my	O	O
responsibility	O	O
while	O	O
in	O	O
EBS	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
did	O	O
not	O	O
get	O	O
assigned	O	O
during	O	O
the	O	O
reorg	O	O
.	O	O

80Y	O	O
-	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
Broadband	I-ORG	O
Acquisition	I-ORG	O
,	I-ORG	O
Inc	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
entity	O	O
was	O	O
created	O	O
in	O	O
2000	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
acquistion	O	O
of	O	O
WarpSpeed	B-ORG	O
Communications	I-ORG	O
(	O	O
now	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
WarpSpeed	I-ORG	O
Services	I-ORG	O
,	I-ORG	O
Inc.	I-ORG	O
83N	I-ORG	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
then	O	O
dissolved	O	O
upon	O	O
completion	O	O
of	O	O
merger	O	O
.	O	O

Company	O	O
is	O	O
around	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
small	O	O
amount	O	O
of	O	O
assets	O	O
and	O	O
liabilities	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
no	O	O
I/S	O	O
items	O	O
.	O	O

83N	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
my	O	O
responsibility	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
this	O	O
entity	O	O
should	O	O
stay	O	O
with	O	O
83N	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

So	O	O
I	O	O
suggest	O	O
it	O	O
be	O	O
assigned	O	O
to	O	O
Leon	B-PER	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
4	O	O
-	O	O
easy	O	O
.	O	O

1579	O	O
-	O	O
EBS	B-ORG	O
Network	I-ORG	O
Co.	I-ORG	O
Division	O	O
of	O	O
17H	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
one	O	O
should	O	O
possibly	O	O
be	O	O
assigned	O	O
to	O	O
Networks	O	O
&	O	O
Services	O	O
group	O	O
.	O	O

Not	O	O
currently	O	O
on	O	O
our	O	O
list	O	O
of	O	O
companies	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
this	O	O
could	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
either	O	O
Holding	B-ORG	O
/	O	O
Administrative	O	O
Companies	O	O
(	O	O
Same	O	O
as	O	O
17H	O	O
)	O	O
or	O	O
Network	O	O
&	O	O
Services	O	O
(	O	O
Leon	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

4	O	O
-	O	O
easy	O	O
.	O	O

1691	O	O
-	O	O
EPI	O	O
-	O	O
EBS	B-ORG	O
Europe	I-ORG	B-LOC

Set	O	O
up	O	O
last	O	O
month	O	O
to	O	O
centralize	O	O
merchant	O	O
asset	O	O
activities	O	O
.	O	O

Broke	O	O
out	O	O
the	O	O
activities	O	O
of	O	O
1179	O	O
.	O	O

A	O	O
similar	O	O
entity	O	O
(	O	O
1179	O	O
)	O	O
was	O	O
assigned	O	O
to	O	O
Commodity	O	O
and	O	O
Trade	O	O
(	O	O
Todd	B-PER	O
Richards	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Mary	B-PER	O
Fischer	I-PER	O
)	O	O
so	O	O
this	O	O
one	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
assigned	O	O
to	O	O
them	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
.	O	O

4	O	O
-	O	O
easy	O	O
.	O	O

1307	O	O
-	O	O
EBIC	B-ORG	O
-	I-ORG	O
Apache	I-ORG	O
,	I-ORG	O
LLC	I-ORG	O

Rolls	O	O
up	O	O
to	O	O
Cherokee	B-ORG	B-LOC
Finance	I-ORG	O
VOF	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
CFC	O	O
.	O	O

Cherokee	B-ORG	B-LOC
Finance	I-ORG	O
VOF	I-ORG	O
is	O	O
assigned	O	O
to	O	O
North	B-LOC	O
America	I-LOC	B-LOC
(	O	O
Glen	B-PER	O
Walloch	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Kevin	B-PER	O
Walker	I-PER	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Maybe	O	O
this	O	O
one	O	O
should	O	O
also	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
them	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
only	O	O
tax	O	O
which	O	O
may	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
provided	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
foreign	O	O
tax	O	O
.	O	O

4	O	O
-	O	O
easy	O	O
.	O	O

1689	O	O
-	O	O
EPI	B-ORG	O
-	I-ORG	O
EBS	I-ORG	O
Ventures	I-ORG	O
,	I-ORG	O
LLC	I-ORG	O

Set	O	O
up	O	O
last	O	O
month	O	O
to	O	O
centralize	O	O
merchant	O	O
asset	O	O
activities	O	O
.	O	O

Broke	O	O
out	O	O
the	O	O
activities	O	O
of	O	O
1307	O	O
.	O	O

Same	O	O
as	O	O
1307	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
assigned	O	O
to	O	O
North	B-LOC	O
America	I-LOC	B-LOC
(	O	O
Glen	B-PER	O
Walloch	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Kevin	B-PER	O
Walker	I-PER	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

4	O	O
-	O	O
easy	O	O
.	O	O

Let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
any	O	O
questions	O	O
.	O	O

Leon	B-PER	O
Branom	I-PER	O
Senior	O	O
Tax	O	O
Analyst	O	O
Networks	O	O
and	O	O
Services	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
345-8702	O	O
office	O	O
leon.branom@enron.com	B-MISC	O

No	O	O
problem	O	O
about	O	O
moving	O	O
Company	O	O
1691	O	O
over	O	O

I	O	O
see	O	O
that	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
4	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
that	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
no	O	O
problem	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
do	O	O
you	O	O
feel	O	O
about	O	O
taking	O	O
on	O	O
another	O	O
company	O	O
?	O	O

Essie	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Leon	B-PER	O
have	O	O
proposed	O	O
xferring	O	O
Co.	O	O
1691	O	O
to	O	O
your	O	O
world	O	O
(	O	O
see	O	O
below	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
you	O	O
concur	O	O
?	O	O

Please	O	O
let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
Monday	O	O
morning	O	O
.	O	O

Regards	O	O
,	O	O

Vicsandra	B-PER	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
not	O	O
already	O	O
made	O	O
these	O	O
decisions	O	O
,	O	O
Essie	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
guidance	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
helpful	O	O
.	O	O

Patty	B-PER	O
Lee	I-PER	O
Corporate	O	O
Tax	O	O
x35172	O	O
EB	O	O
1774	O	O

Please	O	O
see	O	O
my	O	O
comments	O	O
in	O	O
red	O	O
below	O	O
.	O	O

Essie	B-PER	O

Essie	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
recommend	O	O
where	O	O
these	O	O
companies	O	O
each	O	O
fit	O	O
within	O	O
the	O	O
new	O	O
organization	O	O
?	O	O

If	O	O
possible	O	O
,	O	O
can	O	O
you	O	O
also	O	O
give	O	O
an	O	O
indication	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
rank	O	O
-	O	O
1	O	O
through	O	O
5	O	O
?	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Patty	B-PER	O

Virginia	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Hello	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
originally	O	O
inquiring	O	O
about	O	O
purchasing	O	O
a	O	O
Cross	B-PERderiv	O
or	O	O
Signac	B-PERderiv	O
impressionist	O	O
lithograph	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
found	O	O
them	O	O
and	O	O
purchased	O	O
both	O	O
from	O	O
a	O	O
gallery	O	O
in	O	O
London	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
William	B-ORG	B-PER
Weston	I-ORG	I-PER
.	O	O

They	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
delivered	O	O
this	O	O
week	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
beautiful	O	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
add	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
to	O	O
our	O	O
collection	O	O
.	O	O

By	O	O
the	O	O
way	O	O
the	O	O
Lichtenstein	B-PERderiv	O
is	O	O
up	O	O
and	O	O
hanging	O	O
in	O	O
our	O	O
formal	O	O
living	O	O
room	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
magnificent	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
also	O	O
purchased	O	O
an	O	O
Appel	B-PERderiv	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
last	O	O
month	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
interested	O	O
in	O	O
several	O	O
artists	O	O
.	O	O

Actually	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
one	O	O
or	O	O
more	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
following	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
concept	O	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
over	O	O
time	O	O
I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
own	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
following	O	O
artists	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
all	O	O
depending	O	O
when	O	O
I	O	O
find	O	O
something	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
really	O	O
like	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
listed	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
our	O	O
(	O	O
sometimes	O	O
mine	O	O
vs.	O	O
my	O	O
wife	O	O
's	O	O
favorites	O	O
and	O	O
priorities	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
kind	O	O
of	O	O
in	O	O
rank	O	O
order	O	O
but	O	O
as	O	O
I	O	O
stated	O	O
if	O	O
I	O	O
find	O	O
the	O	O
piece	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
like	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
purchase	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
want	O	O
signed	O	O
and	O	O
numbered	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
realize	O	O
that	O	O
some	O	O
were	O	O
not	O	O
signed	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
artist	O	O
but	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
an	O	O
important	O	O
fact	O	O
in	O	O
my	O	O
buying	O	O
decision	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
also	O	O
realize	O	O
that	O	O
some	O	O
may	O	O
not	O	O
have	O	O
done	O	O
any	O	O
works	O	O
on	O	O
paper	O	O
or	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
outrageously	O	O
expensive	O	O
.	O	O

For	O	O
example	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
know	O	O
if	O	O
Rothko	B-PER	O
or	O	O
Kline	B-PER	O
did	O	O
any	O	O
work	O	O
on	O	O
paper	O	O
.	O	O

At	O	O
least	O	O
that	O	O
is	O	O
what	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
thinking	O	O
now	O	O
.	O	O

Bonnard	B-PER	O
(	O	O
colorful	O	O
only	O	O
)	O	O

Lautrec	B-PER	O

Suerat	B-PER	O
(	O	O
any	O	O
works	O	O
on	O	O
paper	O	O
?	O	O
-	O	O

I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
he	O	O
did	O	O
any	O	O
)	O	O

Other	O	O
impressionist	O	O
or	O	O
post	O	O
impressionist	O	O
lithos	O	O

Braque	B-PER	O

Moore	B-PER	O

Arp	B-PER	O

Rouault	B-PER	O

Modrian	B-PER	O

Rothko	B-PER	O

Kline	B-PER	O

Motherwell	B-LOC	O

By	O	O
the	O	O
way	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
interested	O	O
in	O	O
re-looking	O	O
at	O	O
a	O	O
Picasso	B-PERderiv	O
(	O	O
although	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
2	O	O
)	O	O
that	O	O
your	O	O
gallery	O	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
years	O	O
ago	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
cubist	O	O
piece	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
1920s	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
believe	O	O
you	O	O
called	O	O
the	O	O
technique	O	O
a	O	O
"	O	O
push	O	O
wa	O	O
"	O	O
(	O	O
pronunciation	O	O
Vs	O	O
an	O	O
attempt	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
proper	O	O
spelling	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
for	O	O
sale	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
galleries	O	O
in	O	O
SF	B-LOC	O
and	O	O
was	O	O
about	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
20,000	O	O
.	O	O

Is	O	O
there	O	O
1	O	O
available	O	O
?	O	O

Also	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
still	O	O
thinking	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
Matisse	B-PERderiv	O
we	O	O
discussed	O	O
before	O	O
but	O	O
as	O	O
you	O	O
can	O	O
see	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
of	O	O
other	O	O
artists	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
interested	O	O
in	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
may	O	O
remain	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
back	O	O
burner	O	O
because	O	O
we	O	O
already	O	O
have	O	O
one	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

mike	B-PER	O

Huskers	B-ORG	O
drool	O	O
over	O	O
Sooners	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

Ken	B-PER	O
Rice@ENRON	I-PER	O
COMMUNICATIONS	I-PER	O

01/19/2001	O	O
09:14	O	O
AM	O	O

Huskers	B-ORG	O
rule	O	O
,	O	O
Sooners	B-ORG	O
drool	O	O
.	O	O

Mike	B-PER	O
McConnell@ECT	I-PER	O

01/19/01	O	O
07:55	O	O
AM	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
note	O	O
.	O	O

Sooners	B-ORG	O
rule	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
'll	O	O
find	O	O
time	O	O
when	O	O
things	O	O
settle	O	O
down	O	O
.	O	O

m	B-PER	O

Ken	B-PER	O
Rice@ENRON	I-PER	O
COMMUNICATIONS	I-PER	O

01/19/2001	O	O
07:24	O	O
AM	O	O

Mike	B-PER	O

I	O	O
see	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
scheduled	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
lunch	O	O
today	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
may	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
postpone	O	O
again	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
'll	O	O
let	O	O
you	O	O
know	O	O
later	O	O
this	O	O
morning	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
out	O	O
all	O	O
weekend	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
the	O	O
final	O	O
comments	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
Analyst	O	O
Presentation	O	O
in	O	O
by	O	O
sunday	O	O
night	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
may	O	O
be	O	O
working	O	O
over	O	O
lunch	O	O
.	O	O

Actually	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
think	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
in	O	O
pretty	O	O
good	O	O
shape	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
probably	O	O
be	O	O
doing	O	O
lunch	O	O
but	O	O
just	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
be	O	O
too	O	O
mad	O	O
if	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
cancel	O	O
.	O	O

Ken	B-PER	O

PS	O	O
Your	O	O
brother	O	O
told	O	O
me	O	O
he	O	O
went	O	O
to	O	O
3	O	O
bowl	O	O
games	O	O
(	O	O
when	O	O
I	O	O
found	O	O
out	O	O
that	O	O
two	O	O
of	O	O
them	O	O
were	O	O
the	O	O
galleryfurniture.com	B-MISC	O
bowl	O	O
and	O	O
that	O	O
one	O	O
in	O	O
Shreveport	B-LOC	O
(	O	O
I	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
remember	O	O
the	O	O
name	O	O
of	O	O
it	O	O
))	O	O
I	O	O
realized	O	O
he	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
,	O	O
very	O	O
sick	O	O
college	O	O
football	O	O
fan	O	O
.	O	O

Jeff	B-PER	O
,	O	O
here	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
intial	O	O
draft	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
leave	O	O
as	O	O
a	O	O
word	O	O
document	O	O
and	O	O
make	O	O
any	O	O
changes	O	O
and	O	O
additions	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
think	O	O
necessary	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
n't	O	O
even	O	O
changed	O	O
the	O	O
wording	O	O
after	O	O
I	O	O
first	O	O
put	O	O
it	O	O
down	O	O
.	O	O

Mike	B-PER	O

Mark	B-PER	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
thought	O	O
you	O	O
would	O	O
enjoy	O	O
the	O	O
comment	O	O
about	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

m	B-PER	O

Ken	B-PER	O
Rice@ENRON	I-PER	O
COMMUNICATIONS	I-PER	O

01/19/2001	O	O
07:24	O	O
AM	O	O

Mike	B-PER	O

I	O	O
see	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
scheduled	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
lunch	O	O
today	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
may	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
postpone	O	O
again	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
'll	O	O
let	O	O
you	O	O
know	O	O
later	O	O
this	O	O
morning	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
out	O	O
all	O	O
weekend	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
the	O	O
final	O	O
comments	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
Analyst	O	O
Presentation	O	O
in	O	O
by	O	O
sunday	O	O
night	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
may	O	O
be	O	O
working	O	O
over	O	O
lunch	O	O
.	O	O

Actually	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
think	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
in	O	O
pretty	O	O
good	O	O
shape	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
probably	O	O
be	O	O
doing	O	O
lunch	O	O
but	O	O
just	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
be	O	O
too	O	O
mad	O	O
if	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
cancel	O	O
.	O	O

Ken	B-PER	O

PS	O	O
Your	O	O
brother	O	O
told	O	O
me	O	O
he	O	O
went	O	O
to	O	O
3	O	O
bowl	O	O
games	O	O
(	O	O
when	O	O
I	O	O
found	O	O
out	O	O
that	O	O
two	O	O
of	O	O
them	O	O
were	O	O
the	O	O
galleryfurniture.com	B-MISC	O
bowl	O	O
and	O	O
that	O	O
one	O	O
in	O	O
Shreveport	B-LOC	O
(	O	O
I	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
remember	O	O
the	O	O
name	O	O
of	O	O
it	O	O
))	O	O
I	O	O
realized	O	O
he	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
,	O	O
very	O	O
sick	O	O
college	O	O
football	O	O
fan	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
put	O	O
this	O	O
on	O	O
our	O	O
calendars	O	O
.	O	O

Too	O	O
bad	O	O
you	O	O
wo	O	O
n't	O	O
make	O	O
the	O	O
Compaq	B-ORG	O
thing	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
maybe	O	O
next	O	O
year	O	O
.	O	O

San	B-LOC	O
Antonio	I-LOC	B-PER
,	O	O
wow	O	O
what	O	O
a	O	O
let	O	O
down	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
other	O	O
cities	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
nice	O	O
time	O	O
of	O	O
year	O	O
though	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
can	O	O
recommend	O	O
some	O	O
good	O	O
restaurants	O	O
since	O	O
I	O	O
took	O	O
Ric	B-PER	O
there	O	O
last	O	O
year	O	O
for	O	O
his	O	O
birthday	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
stayed	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
Menger	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
time	O	O
.	O	O

Kay	B-PER	O
Mann@ENRON	I-PER	O

09/20/2000	O	O
04:18	O	O
PM	O	O

This	O	O
Friday	O	O
-	O	O
Michael	B-PER	O
goes	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
visit	O	O
at	O	O
St.	B-ORG	O
Francis	I-ORG	B-PER
,	O	O
which	O	O
may	O	O
be	O	O
his	O	O
new	O	O
school	O	O
(	O	O
so	O	O
far	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
good	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'll	O	O
be	O	O
in	O	O
around	O	O
1000	O	O

Most	O	O
Fridays	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
TRY	O	O
to	O	O
pick	O	O
Michael	B-PER	O
up	O	O
since	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
away	O	O
so	O	O
much	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
means	O	O
leaving	O	O
by	O	O
445	O	O
or	O	O
so	O	O
.	O	O

October	O	O
4	O	O
,	O	O
ENA	O	O
orientation	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
am	O	O
.	O	O

October	O	O
19	O	O
/	O	O
20	O	O
,	O	O
Neil	B-PER	O
is	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
town	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
pick	O	O
Michael	B-PER	O
up	O	O
from	O	O
school	O	O
(	O	O
leave	O	O
at	O	O
430	O	O
)	O	O

October	O	O
26	O	O
/	O	O
27	O	O
,	O	O
hope	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
vacation	O	O
time	O	O
.	O	O

Neil	B-PER	O
has	O	O
a	O	O
meeting	O	O
in	O	O
San	B-LOC	O
Antonio	I-LOC	B-PER
(	O	O
usually	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
in	O	O
Miami	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
San	B-LOC	O
Francisco	I-LOC	B-PER
,	O	O
Phoenix	B-LOC	O
-	O	O
not	O	O
so	O	O
great	O	O
this	O	O
year	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
officer	O	O
's	O	O
meeting	O	O
for	O	O
Enterprise	B-MISC	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
spouses	O	O
are	O	O
invited	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
means	O	O
we	O	O
wo	O	O
n't	O	O
be	O	O
in	O	O
town	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Compaq	B-ORG	O
thing	O	O
.	O	O

Figures	O	O
,	O	O
of	O	O
course	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
asking	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
watching	O	O
for	O	O
some	O	O
good	O	O
vacation	O	O
days	O	O
,	O	O
also	O	O
...	O	O

fyi	O	O
/	O	O
review	O	O
/	O	O
comment	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
questions	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
wrap	O	O
up	O	O
the	O	O
LOI	O	O
:	O	O

We	O	O
refer	O	O
to	O	O
licensed	O	O
Fuel	O	O
Cell	O	O
Energy	O	O
equipment	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
we	O	O
intend	O	O
to	O	O
reference	O	O
a	O	O
particular	O	O
manufacturer	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
should	O	O
this	O	O
be	O	O
more	O	O
generic	O	O
?	O	O

Do	O	O
we	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
attach	O	O
a	O	O
draft	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Development	O	O
Agreement	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
condition	O	O
the	O	O
final	O	O
deal	O	O
on	O	O
agreeing	O	O
to	O	O
terms	O	O
substantially	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
as	O	O
what	O	O
's	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
draft	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
concern	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
optionality	O	O
bug	O	O
could	O	O
bite	O	O
us	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
backside	O	O
with	O	O
that	O	O
one	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
we	O	O
expect	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
ONE	O	O
EPC	O	O
contract	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
several	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
confidentiality	O	O
agreement	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
may	O	O
be	O	O
in	O	O
Bart	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
files	O	O
(	O	O
have	O	O
n't	O	O
checked	O	O
closely	O	O
yet	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
anyone	O	O
has	O	O
it	O	O
handy	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
could	O	O
speed	O	O
things	O	O
up	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Kay	B-PER	O

Forget	O	O
the	O	O
ONE	O	O
or	O	O
more	O	O
contract	O	O
questions	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
see	O	O
we	O	O
expect	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
separate	O	O
contracts	O	O
for	O	O
each	O	O
project	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
questions	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
wrap	O	O
up	O	O
the	O	O
LOI	O	O
:	O	O

We	O	O
refer	O	O
to	O	O
licensed	O	O
Fuel	O	O
Cell	O	O
Energy	O	O
equipment	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
we	O	O
intend	O	O
to	O	O
reference	O	O
a	O	O
particular	O	O
manufacturer	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
should	O	O
this	O	O
be	O	O
more	O	O
generic	O	O
?	O	O

Do	O	O
we	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
attach	O	O
a	O	O
draft	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Development	O	O
Agreement	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
condition	O	O
the	O	O
final	O	O
deal	O	O
on	O	O
agreeing	O	O
to	O	O
terms	O	O
substantially	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
as	O	O
what	O	O
's	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
draft	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
concern	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
optionality	O	O
bug	O	O
could	O	O
bite	O	O
us	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
backside	O	O
with	O	O
that	O	O
one	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
we	O	O
expect	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
ONE	O	O
EPC	O	O
contract	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
several	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
confidentiality	O	O
agreement	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
may	O	O
be	O	O
in	O	O
Bart	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
files	O	O
(	O	O
have	O	O
n't	O	O
checked	O	O
closely	O	O
yet	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
anyone	O	O
has	O	O
it	O	O
handy	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
could	O	O
speed	O	O
things	O	O
up	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Kay	B-PER	O

On	O	O
the	O	O
issue	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
contracts	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
draft	O	O
says	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
170	O	O
m	O	O
is	O	O
paid	O	O
when	O	O
the	O	O
EPC	O	O
contract	O	O
is	O	O
signed	O	O
.	O	O

Are	O	O
we	O	O
expecting	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
portion	O	O
attributable	O	O
to	O	O
each	O	O
project	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
paid	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
individual	O	O
EPC	O	O
contracts	O	O
are	O	O
signed	O	O
?	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Kay	B-PER	O

1	O	O
.	O	O
The	O	O
pricing	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
given	O	O
CRRA	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
specific	O	O
to	O	O
FuelCell	B-ORG	O
Energy	I-ORG	O
and	O	O
would	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
meaningful	O	O
without	O	O
listing	O	O
the	O	O
manufacturer	O	O
(	O	O
i.e.	O	O
,	O	O
ONSI	B-ORG	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
more	O	O
money	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Hence	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
think	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
reference	O	O
the	O	O
manufacturer	O	O
.	O	O

2	O	O
.	O	O
The	O	O
attachment	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Development	O	O
Agreement	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
Jeff	B-PER	O
question	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
order	O	O
to	O	O
mark	O	O
any	O	O
2000	O	O
income	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
CRRA	B-ORG	O
to	O	O
execute	O	O
the	O	O
Development	O	O
Agreement	O	O
in	O	O
2000	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
my	O	O
opinion	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
should	O	O
show	O	O
CRRA	B-ORG	O
a	O	O
copy	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
LOI	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
assumption	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
Development	O	O
Agreement	O	O
is	O	O
attached	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
actually	O	O
send	O	O
them	O	O
the	O	O
draft	O	O
Development	O	O
Agreement	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
days	O	O
after	O	O
the	O	O
LOI	O	O
.	O	O

Based	O	O
on	O	O
how	O	O
CRRA	B-ORG	O
reacts	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
would	O	O
make	O	O
an	O	O
ultimate	O	O
determination	O	O
if	O	O
the	O	O
agreement	O	O
needs	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
attached	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
LOI	O	O
.	O	O

3	O	O
.	O	O
I	O	O
expect	O	O
at	O	O
least	O	O
one	O	O
EPC	O	O
contract	O	O
per	O	O
project	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
condition	O	O
the	O	O
acceptance	O	O
of	O	O
one	O	O
project	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
performance	O	O
of	O	O
another	O	O
project	O	O
.	O	O

Performance	O	O
tests	O	O
will	O	O
either	O	O
be	O	O
performed	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
project	O	O
basis	O	O
or	O	O
a	O	O
unit	O	O
by	O	O
unit	O	O
basis	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
given	O	O
project	O	O
.	O	O

Remarkably	O	O
clear	O	O
explanation	O	O
.	O	O

Sent	O	O
by	O	O
:	O	O
Ben	B-PER	O
Jacoby@ECT	I-PER	O

FYI	O	O
,	O	O
see	O	O
below	O	O
.	O	O

Mom	O	O
's	O	O
birthday	O	O
is	O	O
tommorow	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
are	O	O
we	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
her	O	O
?	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

That	O	O
is	O	O
some	O	O
good	O	O
stuff	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
hear	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
coming	O	O
our	O	O
way	O	O
soon	O	O
.	O	O

Look	O	O
forward	O	O
to	O	O
drinking	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
beers	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Michael	B-PER	O
McDermott	I-PER	O
<	O	O
Michael.McDermott@spectrongroup.com	B-PER	O
>	O	O
on	O	O
06/01/2000	O	O
06:00:56	O	O
AM	O	O

Yo	O	O
Mama	O	O
`s	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
....	O	O

Your	O	O
mama	O	O
is	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
:	O	O
When	O	O
she	O	O
hauls	O	O
ass	O	O
she	O	O
has	O	O
to	O	O
make	O	O
two	O	O
trips	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
she	O	O
dances	O	O
she	O	O
makes	O	O
the	O	O
band	O	O
skip	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
she	O	O
was	O	O
diagnosed	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
flesh	O	O
eating	O	O
disease	O	O
the	O	O
doctor	O	O
gave	O	O
her	O	O
13	O	O
years	O	O
to	O	O
live	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
puts	O	O
mayonnaise	O	O
on	O	O
aspirin	O	O
.	O	O
(	O	O
<-	O	O
clearly	O	O
the	O	O
winner	O	O
)	O	O

Her	O	O
cereal	O	O
bowl	O	O
came	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
lifeguard	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
she	O	O
goes	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
zoo	O	O
the	O	O
elephants	O	O
throw	O	O
her	O	O
peanuts	O	O
.	O	O

Her	O	O
high	O	O
school	O	O
graduation	O	O
picture	O	O
was	O	O
an	O	O
aerial	O	O
photograph	O	O
.	O	O

Her	O	O
driver	O	O
`s	O	O
license	O	O
says	O	O
"	O	O
Picture	O	O
continued	O	O
on	O	O
other	O	O
side	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

She	O	O
has	O	O
to	O	O
iron	O	O
her	O	O
pants	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
driveway	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
back	O	O
of	O	O
her	O	O
neck	O	O
looks	O	O
like	O	O
a	O	O
pack	O	O
of	O	O
hot	O	O
dogs	O	O
.	O	O

Yo	O	O
mama	O	O
`s	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
,	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
restaurants	O	O
in	O	O
town	O	O
have	O	O
signs	O	O
that	O	O
say	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
Maximum	O	O
Occupancy	O	O
:	O	O
240	O	O
Patrons	O	O
OR	O	O
Yo	O	O
Mama	O	O
"	O	O
Yo	O	O
mama	O	O
`s	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
,	O	O
when	O	O
she	O	O
ran	O	O
away	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
had	O	O
to	O	O
use	O	O
all	O	O
four	O	O
sides	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
milk	O	O
carton	O	O
.	O	O

Yo	O	O
mama	O	O
`s	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
,	O	O
instead	O	O
of	O	O
Levis	B-ORG	B-PER
501	O	O
jeans	O	O
,	O	O
she	O	O
wears	O	O
Levi`s	B-ORG	B-PER
1002`s	O	O
.	O	O

Yo	O	O
mama	O	O
`s	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
,	O	O
when	O	O
she	O	O
gets	O	O
in	O	O
an	O	O
elevator	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
HAS	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
down	O	O
.	O	O

Yo	O	O
mama	O	O
`s	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
,	O	O
she	O	O
was	O	O
born	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
silver	O	O
shovel	O	O
in	O	O
her	O	O
mouth	O	O
.	O	O

Yo	O	O
mama	O	O
`s	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
,	O	O
she	O	O
`s	O	O
got	O	O
smaller	O	O
fat	O	O
women	O	O
orbiting	O	O
around	O	O
her	O	O
.	O	O

Yo	O	O
mama	O	O
`s	O	O
so	O	O
fat	O	O
,	O	O
she	O	O
could	O	O
sell	O	O
shade	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
will	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
wait	O	O
and	O	O
see	O	O
:-)	O	O

Done	O	O
!	O	O

Expect	O	O
a	O	O
call	O	O
from	O	O
Paul	B-PER	O
tonight	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

What	O	O
are	O	O
some	O	O
good	O	O
interview	O	O
questions	O	O
?	O	O

Poll	O	O
your	O	O
co-workers	O	O
.	O	O

cd	B-PER	O

I	O	O
told	O	O
Paul	B-PER	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
called	O	O
him	O	O
yesterday	O	O
so	O	O
abruptly	O	O
because	O	O
you	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
waste	O	O
his	O	O
time	O	O
while	O	O
you	O	O
got	O	O
tests	O	O
done	O	O
for	O	O
arthritis	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
told	O	O
him	O	O
I	O	O
told	O	O
you	O	O
to	O	O
call	O	O
him	O	O
back	O	O
and	O	O
at	O	O
least	O	O
hear	O	O
what	O	O
he	O	O
has	O	O
to	O	O
say	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
said	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
people	O	O
and	O	O
based	O	O
on	O	O
what	O	O
I	O	O
told	O	O
him	O	O
an	O	O
interview	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
formality	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Is	O	O
that	O	O
Microwave	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
gave	O	O
Dan	B-PER	O
really	O	O
expensive	O	O
?	O	O

All	O	O
the	O	O
guys	O	O
at	O	O
work	O	O
are	O	O
saying	O	O
I	O	O
should	O	O
n't	O	O
bother	O	O
having	O	O
it	O	O
fixed	O	O
I	O	O
should	O	O
just	O	O
buy	O	O
a	O	O
new	O	O
one	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Jai	B-PER	O
Hawker	I-PER	O
974-6721	O	O

I	O	O
wo	O	O
n't	O	O
forget	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
I	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
cross	O	O
reference	O	O
the	O	O
deals	O	O
in	O	O
my	O	O
model	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
deals	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
system	O	O
or	O	O
did	O	O
you	O	O
already	O	O
do	O	O
that	O	O
?	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Kathy	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
take	O	O
that	O	O
deal	O	O
out	O	O
until	O	O
I	O	O
look	O	O
at	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
mine	O	O
but	O	O
I	O	O
forgot	O	O
to	O	O
write	O	O
it	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
blue	O	O
FX	O	O
book	O	O
(	O	O
I	O	O
only	O	O
wrote	O	O
it	O	O
in	O	O
my	O	O
red	O	O
book	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Thanx	O	O
,	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Just	O	O
a	O	O
reminder	O	O
to	O	O
send	O	O
me	O	O
a	O	O
currency	O	O
report	O	O
.	O	O

Thanx	O	O
,	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Paul	B-PER	O
called	O	O
me	O	O
today	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
in	O	O
Calgary	B-LOC	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
weeks	O	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
interview	O	O
you	O	O
then	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

You	O	O
should	O	O
reply	O	O
ASAP	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
make	O	O
Peters	B-ORG	B-PER
and	I-ORG	O
Co.	I-ORG	O
wait	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

I	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
chance	O	O
to	O	O
talk	O	O
to	O	O
Paul	B-PER	O
today	O	O
.	O	O

Give	O	O
him	O	O
a	O	O
call	O	O
tommorow	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Will	O	O
you	O	O
please	O	O
run	O	O
a	O	O
June	O	O
NX3	O	O
/	O	O
NX1	O	O
for	O	O
our	O	O
book	O	O
.	O	O

Paul	B-PER	O

How	O	O
about	O	O
meeting	O	O
at	O	O
11:30	O	O
or	O	O
12	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
office	O	O
so	O	O
give	O	O
me	O	O
a	O	O
call	O	O
.	O	O

CD	B-PER	O
3-1663	O	O

The	O	O
deed	O	O
is	O	O
done	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Find	O	O
attached	O	O
resume	O	O
and	O	O
cover	O	O
letter	O	O
.	O	O

Hopefully	O	O
he	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
spel	O	O
anyting	O	O
incorrectly	O	O
.	O	O

Dan	B-PER	O
is	O	O
really	O	O
smart	O	O
and	O	O
a	O	O
hard	O	O
worker	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
he	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
good	O	O
fit	O	O
.	O	O

Give	O	O
me	O	O
a	O	O
call	O	O
Tuesday	O	O
afternoon	O	O
to	O	O
discuss	O	O
(	O	O
gone	O	O
to	O	O
Kelowna	B-LOC	O
golfing	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
weekend	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Cheers	O	O
,	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
n't	O	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
chance	O	O
to	O	O
send	O	O
it	O	O
yet	O	O
.	O	O

Paul	B-PER	O
is	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
office	O	O
today	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
n't	O	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
chance	O	O
to	O	O
talk	O	O
to	O	O
him	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'll	O	O
send	O	O
it	O	O
as	O	O
soon	O	O
as	O	O
you	O	O
resond	O	O
wether	O	O
I	O	O
should	O	O
or	O	O
not	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Are	O	O
you	O	O
guys	O	O
still	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
an	O	O
analyst	O	O
?	O	O

Should	O	O
I	O	O
send	O	O
the	O	O
resume	O	O
to	O	O
Dawn	B-PER	O
or	O	O
you	O	O
directly	O	O
?	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
Canada	I-ORG	B-LOC
Corp.	I-ORG	O
Suite	O	O
1100	O	O
,	O	O
70	O	O
York	B-LOC	B-LOC
Street	I-LOC	O
Toronto	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
Ontario	B-LOC	O
M5J	O	O
1S9	O	O
416-865-3700	O	O

Paul	B-PER	O
DeVries	I-PER	O
-	O	O
Director	O	O
416-865-3703	O	O

Jan	B-PER	O
Wilson	I-PER	O
-	O	O
Manager	O	O
416-865-3704	O	O

Attached	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
forecast	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
rest	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
summer	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
X	O	O
(	O	O
NWP	O	O
and	O	O
PGT	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
should	O	O
try	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
conference	O	O
call	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
west	O	O
desk	O	O
to	O	O
discuss	O	O
as	O	O
soon	O	O
as	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

See	O	O
you	O	O
there	O	O
!	O	O

CD	B-PER	O

Sushi	O	O
tonight	O	O
?	O	O

Ryan	B-PER	O
Watt	I-PER	O
says	O	O
high	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
attend	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O

Mike	B-PER	O
Jordan	I-PER	O

26/09/2000	O	O
14:14	O	O

Fernley	B-PER	O
/	O	O
Sally	B-PER	O

Off	O	O
and	O	O
on	O	O
(	O	O
with	O	O
Jackie	B-PER	O
Gentle	I-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
help	O	O
)	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
pulled	O	O
together	O	O
a	O	O
one	O	O
page	O	O
communication	O	O
note	O	O
on	O	O
our	O	O
fundamental	O	O
operating	O	O
standards	O	O
(	O	O
itself	O	O
a	O	O
one	O	O
page	O	O
summary	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
final	O	O
stages	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
process	O	O
-	O	O
where	O	O
we	O	O
draft	O	O
a	O	O
cover	O	O
letter	O	O
for	O	O
John	B-PER	O
which	O	O
will	O	O
introduce	O	O
this	O	O
for	O	O
inclusion	O	O
within	O	O
Globalflash	B-MISC	O
(	O	O
the	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
Europe	I-ORG	B-LOC
newsletter	O	O
)	O	O

Have	O	O
you	O	O
any	O	O
thoughts	O	O
on	O	O
draft	O	O
or	O	O
cover	O	O
note	O	O
?	O	O

Mike	B-PER	O

Late	O	O
Jan	O	O
sounds	O	O
great	O	O
.	O	O

Meagan	B-PER	O
does	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
big	O	O
things	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
weekend	O	O
in	O	O
January	O	O
--	O	O
National	B-ORG	O
Charity	I-ORG	O
League	I-ORG	O
Senior	O	O
Presentation	O	O
(	O	O
big	O	O
dance	O	O
that	O	O
she	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
are	O	O
committed	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
with	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
Bearkadette	B-MISC	B-ORG
Ball	I-MISC	O
and	O	O
a	O	O
winter	O	O
party	O	O
for	O	O
Cotillion	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
believe	O	O
that	O	O
these	O	O
are	O	O
three	O	O
weekends	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
row	O	O
,	O	O
January	O	O
6	O	O
,	O	O
13	O	O
and	O	O
20th	O	O
.	O	O

So	O	O
the	O	O
last	O	O
weekend	O	O
in	O	O
January	O	O
would	O	O
work	O	O
well	O	O
(	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
need	O	O
a	O	O
rest	O	O
from	O	O
formal	O	O
affairs	O	O
!	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Does	O	O
that	O	O
work	O	O
for	O	O
you	O	O
?	O	O

And	O	O
do	O	O
you	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
it	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
Saturday	O	O
or	O	O
Sunday	O	O
?	O	O

Saturday	O	O
probably	O	O
works	O	O
better	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
,	O	O
just	O	O
so	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
back	O	O
in	O	O
Houston	B-LOC	O
and	O	O
doing	O	O
laundry	O	O
by	O	O
Sunday	O	O
afternoon	O	O
!!	O	O

Hi	O	O
...	O	O

Talked	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
little	O	O
mother	O	O
-	O	O
to	O	O
-	O	O
be	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
said	O	O
a	O	O
shower	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
grand	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
has	O	O
some	O	O
big	O	O
presentation	O	O
mid-January	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
does	O	O
late	O	O
January	O	O
sound	O	O
to	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

Should	O	O
we	O	O
set	O	O
a	O	O
date	O	O
now	O	O
?	O	O

Am	O	O
I	O	O
turning	O	O
into	O	O
Mother	O	O
?	O	O

Cindy	B-PER	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
that	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
idea	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
some	O	O
press	O	O
regarding	O	O
our	O	O
fundamental	O	O
operating	O	O
standards	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
I	O	O
wonder	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
most	O	O
appropriate	O	O
timing	O	O
,	O	O
enough	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
global	O	O
message	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
means	O	O
of	O	O
delivery	O	O
.	O	O

On	O	O
the	O	O
means	O	O
of	O	O
delivery	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
not	O	O
sure	O	O
from	O	O
your	O	O
note	O	O
whether	O	O
or	O	O
not	O	O
I	O	O
fully	O	O
understand	O	O
the	O	O
intent	O	O
.	O	O

Is	O	O
there	O	O
an	O	O
article	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
included	O	O
in	O	O
an	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
publication	O	O
and	O	O
in	O	O
addition	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
letter	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
sent	O	O
under	O	O
John	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
name	O	O
(	O	O
if	O	O
so	O	O
,	O	O
to	O	O
whom	O	O
will	O	O
the	O	O
letter	O	O
be	O	O
sent	O	O
)	O	O
?	O	O

Or	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
letter	O	O
from	O	O
John	B-PER	O
an	O	O
introduction	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
included	O	O
as	O	O
a	O	O
lead	O	O
in	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
article	O	O
?	O	O

With	O	O
regard	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
global	O	O
message	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
think	O	O
that	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
key	O	O
points	O	O
around	O	O
fundamental	O	O
operating	O	O
standards	O	O
are	O	O
that	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
intended	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
global	O	O
in	O	O
nature	O	O
,	O	O
applied	O	O
to	O	O
every	O	O
commodity	O	O
and	O	O
every	O	O
location	O	O
where	O	O
we	O	O
engage	O	O
in	O	O
trading	O	O
activities	O	O
.	O	O

With	O	O
these	O	O
operating	O	O
standards	O	O
implemented	O	O
worldwide	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
know	O	O
as	O	O
operations	O	O
professionals	O	O
that	O	O
risk	O	O
is	O	O
being	O	O
mitigated	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
ensure	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
top	O	O
management	O	O
that	O	O
there	O	O
is	O	O
consistency	O	O
in	O	O
operating	O	O
standards	O	O
worldwide	O	O
.	O	O

These	O	O
global	O	O
standards	O	O
also	O	O
should	O	O
enable	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
to	O	O
expand	O	O
its	O	O
business	O	O
reach	O	O
more	O	O
quickly	O	O
,	O	O
with	O	O
well	O	O
defined	O	O
requirements	O	O
with	O	O
regard	O	O
to	O	O
trading	O	O
operations	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
not	O	O
sure	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
article	O	O
as	O	O
written	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
global	O	O
nature	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
effort	O	O
comes	O	O
across	O	O
.	O	O

Finally	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
question	O	O
regarding	O	O
timing	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
last	O	O
I	O	O
knew	O	O
after	O	O
you	O	O
and	O	O
Brent	B-PER	O
drafted	O	O
this	O	O
starting	O	O
point	O	O
for	O	O
fundamental	O	O
operating	O	O
standards	O	O
was	O	O
that	O	O
this	O	O
was	O	O
being	O	O
circulated	O	O
(	O	O
Shona	B-PER	O
took	O	O
this	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
after	O	O
Brent	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
return	O	O
to	O	O
Houston	B-LOC	O
)	O	O
for	O	O
comments	O	O
to	O	O
all	O	O
business	O	O
controllers	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
believe	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
quite	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
point	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
say	O	O
that	O	O
all	O	O
business	O	O
controllers	O	O
worldwide	O	O
have	O	O
reviewed	O	O
,	O	O
understand	O	O
and	O	O
have	O	O
implemented	O	O
these	O	O
standards	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
not	O	O
to	O	O
belittle	O	O
the	O	O
process	O	O
of	O	O
creating	O	O
the	O	O
standards	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
tough	O	O
part	O	O
(	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
real	O	O
meat	O	O
behind	O	O
this	O	O
)	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
an	O	O
effective	O	O
exception	O	O
report	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
global	O	O
basis	O	O
against	O	O
these	O	O
standards	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
commitment	O	O
to	O	O
Rick	B-PER	O
Causey	I-PER	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
have	O	O
that	O	O
global	O	O
report	O	O
in	O	O
production	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
end	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
year	O	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
is	O	O
much	O	O
work	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
in	O	O
defining	O	O
the	O	O
content	O	O
and	O	O
regularity	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
report	O	O
and	O	O
even	O	O
more	O	O
work	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
to	O	O
identify	O	O
reliable	O	O
sources	O	O
of	O	O
data	O	O
for	O	O
compiling	O	O
the	O	O
report	O	O
.	O	O

Shona	B-PER	O
has	O	O
commissioned	O	O
Mike	B-PER	O
Moscoso	I-PER	O
to	O	O
work	O	O
on	O	O
this	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
believe	O	O
that	O	O
Mike	B-PER	O
has	O	O
already	O	O
been	O	O
working	O	O
with	O	O
James	B-PER	O
New	I-PER	O
.	O	O

So	O	O
I	O	O
question	O	O
whether	O	O
or	O	O
not	O	O
you	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
publish	O	O
info	O	O
about	O	O
fundamental	O	O
standards	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
not	O	O
yet	O	O
report	O	O
against	O	O
.	O	O

Would	O	O
a	O	O
more	O	O
appropriate	O	O
time	O	O
be	O	O
after	O	O
the	O	O
Global	O	O
Operations	O	O
Controller	O	O
meeting	O	O
in	O	O
October	O	O
when	O	O
we	O	O
should	O	O
have	O	O
worldwide	O	O
buy	O	O
-	O	O
in	O	O
and	O	O
commitment	O	O
to	O	O
these	O	O
standards	O	O
and	O	O
(	O	O
hopefully	O	O
)	O	O
our	O	O
first	O	O
draft	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
meaningful	O	O
exception	O	O
report	O	O
?	O	O

Sorry	O	O
that	O	O
this	O	O
response	O	O
looks	O	O
so	O	O
long	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
interrupted	O	O
20	O	O
times	O	O
while	O	O
responding	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
hope	O	O
that	O	O
it	O	O
makes	O	O
sense	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
sharing	O	O
this	O	O
with	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

Since	O	O
you	O	O
asked	O	O
for	O	O
input	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
hope	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
mind	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
gave	O	O
you	O	O
some	O	O
.	O	O

--	O	O
Sally	B-PER	O

David	B-PER	O
W	I-PER	O
Delainey@ECT	I-PER	O

11/10/2000	O	O
01:04	O	O
PM	O	O

Steve	B-PER	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
noticed	O	O
that	O	O
our	O	O
allocation	O	O
from	O	O
2000	O	O
to	O	O
2001	O	O
is	O	O
going	O	O
up	O	O
by	O	O
21	O	O
%	O	O
year	O	O
on	O	O
year	O	O
(	O	O
ie	O	O
)	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
13.9	O	O
M	O	O
from	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
11.5	O	O
M	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
keep	O	O
ENA	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
direct	O	O
group	O	O
expenses	O	O
flat	O	O
year	O	O
on	O	O
year	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
trying	O	O
hard	O	O
to	O	O
keep	O	O
the	O	O
corporate	O	O
allocation	O	O
flat	O	O
year	O	O
to	O	O
year	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
view	O	O
on	O	O
how	O	O
we	O	O
might	O	O
be	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
achieve	O	O
this	O	O
goal	O	O
?	O	O

Regards	O	O

Delainey	B-PER	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
worry	O	O
about	O	O
it	O	O
...	O	O
sorry	O	O
for	O	O
putting	O	O
you	O	O
back	O	O
on	O	O
speaker	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
just	O	O
wanted	O	O
Sue	B-PER	O
to	O	O
hear	O	O
(	O	O
she	O	O
enjoys	O	O
utility	O	O
bashing	O	O
so	O	O
much	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
comment	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
hearing	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
some	O	O
respects	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
think	O	O
the	O	O
first	O	O
panel	O	O
could	O	O
have	O	O
gone	O	O
much	O	O
better	O	O
;	O	O
everyone	O	O
thanked	O	O
FERC	B-ORG	O
for	O	O
intervening	O	O
(	O	O
though	O	O
for	O	O
different	O	O
reasons	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
other	O	O
staff	O	O
reports	O	O
are	O	O
also	O	O
looking	O	O
good	O	O
.	O	O

Scott	B-PER	O
Miller	I-PER	O
has	O	O
been	O	O
a	O	O
godsend	O	O
--	O	O
somebody	O	O
not	O	O
afraid	O	O
to	O	O
tell	O	O
it	O	O
like	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
.	O	O

Jeff	B-PER	O
Dasovich	I-PER	O

Sent	O	O
by	O	O
:	O	O
Jeff	B-PER	O
Dasovich	I-PER	O

11/10/2000	O	O
12:33	O	O
PM	O	O

I	O	O
apologize	O	O
if	O	O
I	O	O
offended	O	O
anyone	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
let	O	O
them	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
was	O	O
simply	O	O
quoting	O	O
the	O	O
CEO	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
large	O	O
,	O	O
regulated	O	O
utility	O	O
in	O	O
California	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
attributing	O	O
the	O	O
quote	O	O
to	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
did	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
job	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
hearing	O	O
----	O	O
it	O	O
went	O	O
decidely	O	O
downhill	O	O
after	O	O
you	O	O
left	O	O
.	O	O

Best	O	O
,	O	O

Jeff	B-PER	O

Does	O	O
she	O	O
have	O	O
any	O	O
interest	O	O
in	O	O
meeting	O	O
one	O	O
-	O	O
on	O	O
-	O	O
one	O	O
or	O	O
is	O	O
she	O	O
just	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
public	O	O
hanging	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
remain	O	O
convinced	O	O
that	O	O
if	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
just	O	O
get	O	O
the	O	O
facts	O	O
in	O	O
front	O	O
of	O	O
people	O	O
they	O	O
will	O	O
modulate	O	O
their	O	O
approach	O	O
.	O	O

Jeff	B-PER	O
Dasovich	I-PER	O

Sent	O	O
by	O	O
:	O	O
Jeff	B-PER	O
Dasovich	I-PER	O

11/10/2000	O	O
12:21	O	O
PM	O	O

Given	O	O
the	O	O
short	O	O
notice	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
politely	O	O
decline	O	O
to	O	O
participate	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
hearing	O	O
on	O	O
Monday	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
will	O	O
let	O	O
the	O	O
good	O	O
Senator	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
,	O	O
in	O	O
general	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
intend	O	O
to	O	O
engage	O	O
actively	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
process	O	O
and	O	O
plan	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
California	B-ORG	B-LOC
find	O	O
a	O	O
solution	O	O
that	O	O
works	O	O
for	O	O
everybody	O	O
.	O	O

Amen	O	O
.	O	O

See	O	O
below	O	O
.	O	O

Can	O	O
we	O	O
get	O	O
some	O	O
help	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
IBM	B-ORG	O
issues	O	O
?	O	O

Erin	B-PER	O
Rice	I-PER	O

11/10/2000	O	O
11:08	O	O
AM	O	O

Steve	B-PER	O
:	O	O

At	O	O
this	O	O
point	O	O
,	O	O
our	O	O
IT	O	O
contacts	O	O
are	O	O
backpedalling	O	O
a	O	O
bit	O	O
and	O	O
suggesting	O	O
they	O	O
can	O	O
overcome	O	O
the	O	O
TIBCO	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
Terminal	O	O
Server	O	O
problems	O	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
are	O	O
still	O	O
four	O	O
important	O	O
issues	O	O
,	O	O
however	O	O
:	O	O

IT	O	O
still	O	O
can	O	O
not	O	O
commit	O	O
to	O	O
transferring	O	O
messages	O	O
across	O	O
domains	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
means	O	O
that	O	O
messages	O	O
initiated	O	O
at	O	O
Corp	B-MISC	O
and	O	O
intended	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
entire	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
organization	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
reach	O	O
any	O	O
business	O	O
units	O	O
outside	O	O
the	O	O
Corp	B-MISC	O
domain	O	O
.	O	O

No	O	O
messages	O	O
will	O	O
reach	O	O
the	O	O
EES	B-ORG	O
organization	O	O
unless	O	O
IBM	B-ORG	O
agrees	O	O
not	O	O
to	O	O
use	O	O
their	O	O
proprietary	O	O
message	O	O
delivery	O	O
tool	O	O
,	O	O
WebSphere	B-MISC	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
use	O	O
WebLogic	B-MISC	O
instead	O	O
.	O	O

WebLogic	B-MISC	O
is	O	O
required	O	O
by	O	O
BackWeb	B-MISC	B-ORG
,	O	O
although	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
designed	O	O
by	O	O
a	O	O
separate	O	O
company	O	O
.	O	O

HR	O	O
,	O	O
intended	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
key	O	O
user	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
tool	O	O
,	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
use	O	O
BackWeb	B-MISC	B-ORG
because	O	O
survey	O	O
responses	O	O
can	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
made	O	O
anonymous	O	O
.	O	O

HR	O	O
has	O	O
already	O	O
purchased	O	O
a	O	O
tool	O	O
called	O	O
CONFIRMIT	B-MISC	O
that	O	O
can	O	O
execute	O	O
anonymous	O	O
surveys	O	O
.	O	O

Messages	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
delivered	O	O
simultaneously	O	O
to	O	O
all	O	O
users	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
domain	O	O
,	O	O
nor	O	O
will	O	O
they	O	O
be	O	O
delivered	O	O
for	O	O
two	O	O
to	O	O
five	O	O
hours	O	O
after	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
sent	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
message	O	O
administrator	O	O
.	O	O

Another	O	O
thing	O	O
to	O	O
consider	O	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
these	O	O
messages	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
set	O	O
to	O	O
expire	O	O
and	O	O
disappear	O	O
within	O	O
a	O	O
set	O	O
period	O	O
of	O	O
time	O	O
,	O	O
meaning	O	O
users	O	O
can	O	O
not	O	O
retrieve	O	O
them	O	O
and	O	O
read	O	O
them	O	O
later	O	O
(	O	O
as	O	O
they	O	O
can	O	O
with	O	O
e-mail	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
means	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
could	O	O
be	O	O
away	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
office	O	O
for	O	O
several	O	O
days	O	O
and	O	O
miss	O	O
a	O	O
message	O	O
entirely	O	O
,	O	O
because	O	O
it	O	O
would	O	O
have	O	O
expired	O	O
and	O	O
disappeared	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
time	O	O
I	O	O
returned	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
plain	O	O
fact	O	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
members	O	O
of	O	O
IT	O	O
are	O	O
pushing	O	O
this	O	O
initiative	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
they	O	O
lack	O	O
commercial	O	O
sponsorship	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
hoping	O	O
Corp	O	O
will	O	O
foot	O	O
the	O	O
bill	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
pilot	O	O
which	O	O
will	O	O
allow	O	O
them	O	O
to	O	O
fully	O	O
test	O	O
this	O	O
tool	O	O
before	O	O
implementing	O	O
it	O	O
company	O	O
-	O	O
wide	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
let	O	O
us	O	O
know	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
additional	O	O
questions	O	O
.	O	O

-	O	O
er	O	O

Steven	B-PER	O
J	I-PER	O
Kean	I-PER	O

11/09/2000	O	O
11:35	O	O
AM	O	O

Do	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
sense	O	O
for	O	O
how	O	O
many	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
reach	O	O
,	O	O
how	O	O
many	O	O
we	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
and	O	O
where	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
?	O	O

Are	O	O
whole	O	O
offices	O	O
(	O	O
eg	O	O
Tokyo	B-ORG	B-LOC
)	O	O
unreachable	O	O
or	O	O
is	O	O
it	O	O
only	O	O
those	O	O
who	O	O
have	O	O
home	O	O
offices	O	O
?	O	O

Courtney	B-PER	O
Votaw	I-PER	O

11/08/2000	O	O
11:02	O	O
AM	O	O

Mark	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Steve	B-PER	O
-	O	O

Erin	B-PER	O
Rice	I-PER	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
meet	O	O
with	O	O
you	O	O
to	O	O
discuss	O	O
the	O	O
issues	O	O
concerning	O	O
BackWeb	B-MISC	B-ORG
before	O	O
we	O	O
proceed	O	O
.	O	O

As	O	O
you	O	O
can	O	O
see	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
Design	O	O
Document	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
pretty	O	O
significant	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Courtney	B-PER	O

calendar	O	O

Paul	B-PER	O
Kaufman@ECT	I-PER	O

Sent	O	O
by	O	O
:	O	O
Lysa	B-PER	O
Akin@ECT	I-PER	O

11/10/2000	O	O
05:59	O	O
PM	O	O

Paul	B-PER	O
Kaufman	I-PER	O
has	O	O
asked	O	O
me	O	O
to	O	O
set	O	O
a	O	O
conference	O	O
call	O	O
to	O	O
review	O	O
the	O	O
FERC	B-ORG	O
Meeting	O	O
that	O	O
was	O	O
held	O	O
Thursday	O	O
,	O	O
Nov.	O	O
9th	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
be	O	O
advised	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
set	O	O
the	O	O
call	O	O
as	O	O
follows	O	O
:	O	O

Date	O	O
:	O	O
Monday	O	O
,	O	O
Nov.	O	O
13th	O	O

Time	O	O
:	O	O
11:30	O	O
am	O	O
/	O	O
1:30	O	O
pm	O	O
Central	O	O
/	O	O
2:30	O	O
pm	O	O
Eastern	O	O

Call	O	O
In	O	O
#	O	O
:	O	O
888-422-7132	O	O

Pin	O	O
#	O	O
:	O	O
411507	O	O

Pin	O	O
#	O	O
for	O	O
Paul	B-PER	O
Kaufman	I-PER	O
ONLY	O	O
:	O	O
362416	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
any	O	O
questions	O	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
call	O	O
503/464-7927	O	O
.	O	O

Lysa	B-PER	O
Akin	I-PER	O
Ass't.	O	O
to	O	O
Paul	B-PER	O
Kaufman	I-PER	O

it	O	O
's	O	O
on	O	O
tonight	O	O

it	O	O
's	O	O
did	O	O
you	O	O
watch	O	O
your	O	O
girl	O	O
on	O	O
tv	O	O
last	O	O
night	O	O
?	O	O

the	O	O
deal	O	O
number	O	O
is	O	O
814014	O	O
-	O	O
why	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
you	O	O
see	O	O
this	O	O
?	O	O

Did	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
a	O	O
deal	O	O
with	O	O
National	B-ORG	O
Fuel	I-ORG	O
Marketing	I-ORG	O
purchasing	O	O
3,500	O	O
mmbtu	O	O
on	O	O
May	O	O
30th	O	O
@	O	O
2.975	O	O
?	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
invoicing	O	O
for	O	O
this	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
have	O	O
an	O	O
invoice	O	O
for	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
give	O	O
me	O	O
the	O	O
Sitara	B-MISC	O
deal	O	O
#	O	O
?	O	O

Thanks	O	O

Darla	B-PER	O

Ok	O	O
to	O	O
book	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
and	O	O
my	O	O
husband	O	O
,	O	O
Joseph	B-PER	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
issued	O	O
a	O	O
new	O	O
corporate	O	O
American	B-ORG	B-LOCderiv
Express	I-ORG	O
card	O	O
.	O	O

Same	O	O
number	O	O
with	O	O
expiration	O	O
date	O	O
of	O	O
3/03	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
need	O	O
any	O	O
more	O	O
info	O	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
advise	O	O
.	O	O

Otherwise	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
assume	O	O
you	O	O
will	O	O
book	O	O
the	O	O
two	O	O
tickets	O	O
.	O	O

Thank	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

Actually	O	O
-	O	O
upon	O	O
second	O	O
look	O	O
the	O	O
deal	O	O
number	O	O
is	O	O
814014	O	O
-	O	O
why	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
you	O	O
see	O	O
this	O	O
?	O	O

Did	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
a	O	O
deal	O	O
with	O	O
National	B-ORG	O
Fuel	I-ORG	O
Marketing	I-ORG	O
purchasing	O	O
3,500	O	O
mmbtu	O	O
on	O	O
May	O	O
30th	O	O
@	O	O
2.975	O	O
?	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
invoicing	O	O
for	O	O
this	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
have	O	O
an	O	O
invoice	O	O
for	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
give	O	O
me	O	O
the	O	O
Sitara	B-MISC	O
deal	O	O
#	O	O
?	O	O

Thanks	O	O

Darla	B-PER	O

should	O	O
be	O	O
non	B-MISC	O
bondad	I-MISC	B-LOC

Jane	B-PER	O
,	O	O
on	O	O
deal	O	O
763736	O	O
for	O	O
May	O	O
01	O	O
sales	O	O
to	O	O
Southwest	B-ORG	O
Gas	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
pricing	O	O
discrepancy	O	O
.	O	O

Our	O	O
system	O	O
reflects	O	O
SJ	B-MISC	B-LOC
Bondad	I-MISC	B-LOC
GDP	O	O
but	O	O
SWG	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
pay	O	O
us	O	O
based	O	O
on	O	O
SJ	B-MISC	B-LOC
Non-Bondad	I-MISC	B-LOCpart
GDP	O	O
.	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
please	O	O
confirm	O	O
which	O	O
price	O	O
is	O	O
correct	O	O
and	O	O
make	O	O
the	O	O
change	O	O
in	O	O
Sitara	B-MISC	O
if	O	O
necessary	O	O
?	O	O

Thanks	O	O

Laurie	B-PER	O
Ellis	I-PER	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
Net	I-ORG	O
Works	I-ORG	O
LLC	I-ORG	O
Client	O	O
Services	O	O
Phone	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
345-9945	O	O
Fax	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
646-8420	O	O
Email	O	O
:	O	O
laurie.ellis@enron.com	B-PER	O

Sorry	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
flooding	O	O
.	O	O

Hope	O	O
you	O	O
and	O	O
your	O	O
family	O	O
survived	O	O
ok	O	O
.	O	O

Attached	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
gas	O	O
settlement	O	O
and	O	O
support	O	O
for	O	O
May	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
only	O	O
difference	O	O
we	O	O
had	O	O
was	O	O
for	O	O
package	O	O
V02	O	O
.	O	O

Mark	B-PER	O
Anderson	I-PER	O
says	O	O
that	O	O
even	O	O
though	O	O
Bondad	B-LOC	O
gas	O	O
flowed	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
was	O	O
Non-Bondad	B-MISC	B-LOCpart
.	O	O

Have	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
day	O	O
.	O	O

Nancy	B-PER	O

-	O	O
ENRON.XLS	B-MISC	O
<<	O	O
File	O	O
:	O	O
ENRON.XLS	B-MISC	O
>>	O	O

-	O	O
enrongss.xls	B-MISC	O
<<	O	O
File	O	O
:	O	O
enrongss.xls	B-MISC	O
>>	O	O

actually	O	O
-	O	O
for	O	O
volumes	O	O
flowing	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
bondad	B-LOC	O
-	O	O
which	O	O
is	O	O
deal	O	O
number	O	O
763736	O	O
price	O	O
is	O	O
bondad	B-MISC	B-LOC
gda	O	O
;	O	O
for	O	O
blanco	B-LOC	O
-	O	O
deal	O	O
number	O	O
759933	O	O
-	O	O
price	O	O
is	O	O
nonbondad	B-MISC	B-LOCpart
gda	O	O

Jane	B-PER	O
,	O	O
on	O	O
deal	O	O
763736	O	O
for	O	O
May	O	O
01	O	O
sales	O	O
to	O	O
Southwest	B-ORG	O
Gas	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
pricing	O	O
discrepancy	O	O
.	O	O

Our	O	O
system	O	O
reflects	O	O
SJ	B-MISC	B-LOC
Bondad	I-MISC	B-LOC
GDP	O	O
but	O	O
SWG	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
pay	O	O
us	O	O
based	O	O
on	O	O
SJ	B-MISC	B-LOC
Non-Bondad	I-MISC	B-LOCpart
GDP	O	O
.	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
please	O	O
confirm	O	O
which	O	O
price	O	O
is	O	O
correct	O	O
and	O	O
make	O	O
the	O	O
change	O	O
in	O	O
Sitara	B-MISC	O
if	O	O
necessary	O	O
?	O	O

Thanks	O	O

Laurie	B-PER	O
Ellis	I-PER	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
Net	I-ORG	O
Works	I-ORG	O
LLC	I-ORG	O
Client	O	O
Services	O	O
Phone	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
345-9945	O	O
Fax	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
646-8420	O	O
Email	O	O
:	O	O
laurie.ellis@enron.com	B-PER	O

Sorry	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
flooding	O	O
.	O	O

Hope	O	O
you	O	O
and	O	O
your	O	O
family	O	O
survived	O	O
ok	O	O
.	O	O

Attached	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
gas	O	O
settlement	O	O
and	O	O
support	O	O
for	O	O
May	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
only	O	O
difference	O	O
we	O	O
had	O	O
was	O	O
for	O	O
package	O	O
V02	O	O
.	O	O

Mark	B-PER	O
Anderson	I-PER	O
says	O	O
that	O	O
even	O	O
though	O	O
Bondad	B-LOC	O
gas	O	O
flowed	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
was	O	O
Non-Bondad	B-MISC	B-LOCpart
.	O	O

Have	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
day	O	O
.	O	O

Nancy	B-PER	O

-	O	O
ENRON.XLS	B-MISC	O
<<	O	O
File	O	O
:	O	O
ENRON.XLS	B-MISC	O
>>	O	O

-	O	O
enrongss.xls	B-MISC	O
<<	O	O
File	O	O
:	O	O
enrongss.xls	B-MISC	O
>>	O	O

I	O	O
talked	O	O
with	O	O
Mark	B-PER	O
at	O	O
SW	B-ORG	O
Gas	I-ORG	O
-	O	O
just	O	O
honro	O	O
his	O	O
numbers	O	O

Nancy	B-PER	O
,	O	O
can	O	O
you	O	O
please	O	O
reconfirm	O	O
with	O	O
Mark	B-PER	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
gas	O	O
at	O	O
Bondad	B-LOC	O
?	O	O

My	O	O
trader	O	O
is	O	O
supporting	O	O
her	O	O
price	O	O
of	O	O
SJ	B-MISC	B-LOC
Bondad	I-MISC	B-LOC
GDP	O	O
rather	O	O
than	O	O
SJ	B-MISC	B-LOC
Non-Bondad	I-MISC	B-LOCpart
GDP	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O

Laurie	B-PER	O
Ellis	I-PER	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
Net	I-ORG	O
Works	I-ORG	O
LLC	I-ORG	O
Client	O	O
Services	O	O
Phone	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
345-9945	O	O
Fax	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
646-8420	O	O
Email	O	O
:	O	O
laurie.ellis@enron.com	B-PER	O

actually	O	O
-	O	O
for	O	O
volumes	O	O
flowing	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
bondad	B-LOC	O
-	O	O
which	O	O
is	O	O
deal	O	O
number	O	O
763736	O	O
price	O	O
is	O	O
bondad	B-MISC	B-LOC
gda	O	O
;	O	O
for	O	O
blanco	B-LOC	O
-	O	O
deal	O	O
number	O	O
759933	O	O
-	O	O
price	O	O
is	O	O
nonbondad	B-MISC	B-LOCpart
gda	O	O

Jane	B-PER	O
,	O	O
on	O	O
deal	O	O
763736	O	O
for	O	O
May	O	O
01	O	O
sales	O	O
to	O	O
Southwest	B-ORG	O
Gas	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
pricing	O	O
discrepancy	O	O
.	O	O

Our	O	O
system	O	O
reflects	O	O
SJ	B-MISC	B-LOC
Bondad	I-MISC	B-LOC
GDP	O	O
but	O	O
SWG	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
pay	O	O
us	O	O
based	O	O
on	O	O
SJ	B-MISC	B-LOC
Non-Bondad	I-MISC	B-LOCpart
GDP	O	O
.	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
please	O	O
confirm	O	O
which	O	O
price	O	O
is	O	O
correct	O	O
and	O	O
make	O	O
the	O	O
change	O	O
in	O	O
Sitara	B-MISC	O
if	O	O
necessary	O	O
?	O	O

Thanks	O	O

Laurie	B-PER	O
Ellis	I-PER	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
Net	I-ORG	O
Works	I-ORG	O
LLC	I-ORG	O
Client	O	O
Services	O	O
Phone	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
345-9945	O	O
Fax	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
713	O	O
)	O	O
646-8420	O	O
Email	O	O
:	O	O
laurie.ellis@enron.com	B-PER	O

Sorry	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
flooding	O	O
.	O	O

Hope	O	O
you	O	O
and	O	O
your	O	O
family	O	O
survived	O	O
ok	O	O
.	O	O

Attached	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
gas	O	O
settlement	O	O
and	O	O
support	O	O
for	O	O
May	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
only	O	O
difference	O	O
we	O	O
had	O	O
was	O	O
for	O	O
package	O	O
V02	O	O
.	O	O

Mark	B-PER	O
Anderson	I-PER	O
says	O	O
that	O	O
even	O	O
though	O	O
Bondad	B-LOC	O
gas	O	O
flowed	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
was	O	O
Non-Bondad	B-MISC	B-LOCpart
.	O	O

Have	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
day	O	O
.	O	O

Nancy	B-PER	O

-	O	O
ENRON.XLS	B-MISC	O
<<	O	O
File	O	O
:	O	O
ENRON.XLS	B-MISC	O
>>	O	O

-	O	O
enrongss.xls	B-MISC	O
<<	O	O
File	O	O
:	O	O
enrongss.xls	B-MISC	O
>>	O	O

Please	O	O
find	O	O
enclosed	O	O
EES	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
request	O	O
for	O	O
Volumes	O	O
for	O	O
PGE	B-ORG	O
CityGate	B-MISC	O
delvery	O	O
effective	O	O
11/1/01	O	O
:	O	O

See	O	O
attached	O	O
spreadsheet	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
quote	O	O
the	O	O
Gas	O	O
on	O	O
an	O	O
Indexed	O	O
Basis	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
any	O	O
questions	O	O
or	O	O
comments	O	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
advise	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
not	O	O
had	O	O
the	O	O
patience	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
it	O	O
working	O	O
-	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
call	O	O
you	O	O
some	O	O
evening	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
walk	O	O
thru	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
was	O	O
your	O	O
trip	O	O
to	O	O
Des	B-LOC	O
Moines	I-LOC	O
?	O	O

Did	O	O
dthat	O	O
stuff	O	O
form	O	O
Joe	B-PER	O
help	O	O
your	O	O
car	O	O
.	O	O

Hey	O	O
Cester	B-PER	O
,	O	O

When	O	O
are	O	O
we	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
NetMeeting	B-MISC	O
going	O	O
?	O	O

How	O	O
is	O	O
Deb	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
knee	O	O
?	O	O

Did	O	O
she	O	O
ever	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
real	O	O
doctor	O	O
?	O	O

[	O	O
Tholt	B-PER	O
,	O	I-PER
Jane	I-PER	O
M.	I-PER	O
]	O	O

Yes	O	O
She	O	O
is	O	O
having	O	O
physical	O	O
theraphy	O	O
3	O	O
times	O	O
a	O	O
week	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
said	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
getting	O	O
better	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
n't	O	O
seen	O	O
her	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
weeks	O	O
and	O	O
have	O	O
only	O	O
talked	O	O
to	O	O
her	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
probably	O	O
be	O	O
calling	O	O
you	O	O
next	O	O
week	O	O
-	O	O
the	O	O
desk	O	O
wants	O	O
me	O	O
to	O	O
become	O	O
more	O	O
involved	O	O
in	O	O
regulatory	O	O
updates	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
seek	O	O
your	O	O
assistance	O	O
with	O	O
this	O	O
matter	O	O
.	O	O

Jared	B-PER	O
just	O	O
told	O	O
me	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
BUNCH	O	O
of	O	O
stuff	O	O
on	O	O
your	O	O
plate	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
think	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
about	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
much	O	O
busier	O	O
too	O	O
.	O	O

cool	O	O
by	O	O
me	O	O
!	O	O

Jared	B-PER	O
,	O	O
Ruth	B-PER	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
are	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
over	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O
activity	O	O
tomorrow	O	O
morning	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
no	O	O
one	O	O
objects	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
the	O	O
lead	O	O
coordinator	O	O
on	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O
starting	O	O
tomorrow	O	O
.	O	O

Yes	O	O
maam	O	O
,	O	O
she	O	O
's	O	O
UBS	B-ORG	O
now	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
was	O	O
just	O	O
down	O	O
here	O	O
too	O	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O
,	O	O

I	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
remember	O	O
if	O	O
your	O	O
email	O	O
mentioned	O	O
Judy	B-PER	O
.	O	O

Did	O	O
she	O	O
make	O	O
it	O	O
?	O	O

Cindy	B-PER	O
Franklin	I-PER	O
Transportation	O	O
Services	O	O
Work	O	O
:	O	O
832.676.3177	O	O
Fax	O	O
:	O	O
832.676.1329	O	O
Pager	O	O
:	O	O
1.888.509.3736	O	O

******************************************************************	O	O

******************************************************************	O	O

Jared	B-PER	O
,	O	O
Ruth	B-PER	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
are	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
over	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O
activity	O	O
tomorrow	O	O
morning	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
no	O	O
one	O	O
objects	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
the	O	O
lead	O	O
coordinator	O	O
on	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O
starting	O	O
tomorrow	O	O
.	O	O

OK	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
never	O	O
get	O	O
to	O	O
talk	O	O
to	O	O
Ruth	B-PER	O
because	O	O
SHE	O	O
IS	O	O
ALWAYS	O	O
ON	O	O
THE	O	O
PHONE	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
I	O	O
bet	O	O
she	O	O
's	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
phone	O	O
with	O	O
Shemin	B-PER	O
too	O	O
!!!	O	O

Should	O	O
we	O	O
all	O	O
get	O	O
together	O	O
and	O	O
make	O	O
a	O	O
conference	O	O
call	O	O
to	O	O
Dominion	B-ORG	O
like	O	O
we	O	O
did	O	O
before	O	O
or	O	O
should	O	O
I	O	O
just	O	O
call	O	O
Jeff	B-PER	O
Davis	I-PER	O
myself	O	O
?	O	O

Our	O	O
last	O	O
call	O	O
was	O	O
Iris	B-PER	O
Kind	I-PER	O
,	O	O
Bill	B-PER	O
Savier	I-PER	O
(	O	O
sp	O	O
?	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
Jeff	B-PER	O
Davis	I-PER	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
forget	O	O
about	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
still	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
find	O	O
out	O	O
what	O	O
it	O	O
will	O	O
take	O	O
to	O	O
move	O	O
gas	O	O
on	O	O
and	O	O
ENA	B-ORG	O
tabs	O	O
agreement	O	O
.	O	O

No	O	O
transportation	O	O
at	O	O
this	O	O
point	O	O
,	O	O
just	O	O
a	O	O
tabs	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
much	O	O
easier	O	O
for	O	O
you	O	O
guys	O	O
to	O	O
monitor	O	O
because	O	O
most	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
deals	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
monthly	O	O
.	O	O

Steve	B-PER	O
,	O	O
everything	O	O
looks	O	O
good	O	O
with	O	O
one	O	O
exception	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
rate	O	O
schedule	O	O
on	O	O
Tennessee	B-LOC	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
either	O	O
NET	O	O
-	O	O
2	O	O
or	O	O
NET	O	O
-	O	O
284	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
wo	O	O
n't	O	O
find	O	O
out	O	O
until	O	O
Monday	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
review	O	O
and	O	O
approve	O	O
it	O	O
,	O	O
keep	O	O
it	O	O
on	O	O
your	O	O
desk	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
come	O	O
over	O	O
and	O	O
make	O	O
the	O	O
change	O	O
at	O	O
your	O	O
desk	O	O
on	O	O
Monday	O	O
.	O	O

Then	O	O
I	O	O
'll	O	O
take	O	O
it	O	O
to	O	O
Ed	B-PER	O
for	O	O
his	O	O
approval	O	O
.	O	O

By	O	O
the	O	O
way	O	O
,	O	O
Cullen	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Dykman	B-PER	O
is	O	O
sending	O	O
copies	O	O
of	O	O
what	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
doing	O	O
to	O	O
Melanie	B-PER	O
Gray	I-PER	O
.	O	O

Chris	B-PER	O
:	O	O

Per	O	O
our	O	O
conversation	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
minutes	O	O
ago	O	O
,	O	O
attached	O	O
please	O	O
find	O	O
the	O	O
revised	O	O
Stipulation	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
document	O	O
has	O	O
been	O	O
modified	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
changes	O	O
that	O	O
were	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
mark	O	O
-	O	O
up	O	O
you	O	O
faxed	O	O
to	O	O
Toni	B-PER	O
Donohue	I-PER	O
here	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
hours	O	O
ago	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
also	O	O
deleted	O	O
"	O	O
subject	O	O
to	O	O
recall	O	O
"	O	O
based	O	O
on	O	O
our	O	O
discussion	O	O
,	O	O
assuming	O	O
you	O	O
get	O	O
approval	O	O
for	O	O
that	O	O
revision	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
informed	O	O
me	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
would	O	O
discuss	O	O
this	O	O
with	O	O
your	O	O
attorney	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
,	O	O
as	O	O
I	O	O
mentioned	O	O
to	O	O
you	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
faxed	O	O
your	O	O
mark	O	O
-	O	O
up	O	O
to	O	O
Melanie	B-PER	O
Gray	I-PER	O
at	O	O
Weil	B-ORG	B-PER
Gotschal	I-ORG	B-PER
in	O	O
Houston	B-LOC	O
to	O	O
keep	O	O
her	O	O
informed	O	O
.	O	O

(	O	O
Her	O	O
voice	O	O
mail	O	O
says	O	O
she	O	O
's	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
office	O	O
until	O	O
Monday	O	O
.	O	O
)	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
all	O	O
your	O	O
help	O	O
on	O	O
this	O	O
.	O	O

David	B-PER	O
T.	I-PER	O
Metcalfe	I-PER	O
Cullen	B-ORG	B-PER
and	I-ORG	O
Dykman	I-ORG	B-PER
LLP	I-ORG	O
177	O	O
Montague	B-LOC	O
Street	I-LOC	O
Brooklyn	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
New	B-LOC	O
York	I-LOC	O
11201	O	O
phone	O	O
:	O	O
718-780-0046	O	O
fax	O	O
:	O	O
718-780-0276	O	O
e-mail	O	O
:	O	O
dmetcalfe@cullenanddykman.com	B-PER	O

____________________________________________________	O	O

This	O	O
email	O	O
may	O	O
contain	O	O
material	O	O
that	O	O
is	O	O
confidential	O	O
,	O	O
privileged	O	O
and	O	O
/	O	O
or	O	O
attorney	O	O
work	O	O
product	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
sole	O	O
use	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
intended	O	O
recipient	O	O
(	O	O
s	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Any	O	O
review	O	O
,	O	O
reliance	O	O
or	O	O
distribution	O	O
by	O	O
others	O	O
or	O	O
forwarding	O	O
without	O	O
express	O	O
permission	O	O
is	O	O
strictly	O	O
prohibited	O	O
.	O	O

<<	O	O
Stipulation	B-MISC	O
-ECT-KEDNE	I-MISC	O
re	I-MISC	O
IGTS	I-MISC	O
&	I-MISC	O
Tennessee	I-MISC	O
Cap	I-MISC	I-MISC
Releases	I-MISC	O
-FINAL.doc	I-MISC	O
>>	O	O

<<	O	O
BLACKLINE	B-MISC	O
-Stip	I-MISC	O
-ECT-KEDNE	I-MISC	O
re	I-MISC	O
Cap	I-MISC	O
Releases	I-MISC	O
-2-F.doc	I-MISC	O
>>	O	O

-	O	O
Stipulation	B-MISC	O
-ECT-KEDNE	I-MISC	O
re	I-MISC	O
IGTS	I-MISC	O
&	I-MISC	O
Tennessee	I-MISC	O
Cap	I-MISC	O
Releases	I-MISC	O
-FINAL.doc	I-MISC	O
-	O	O
BLACKLINE	B-MISC	O
-Stip	I-MISC	O
-ECT-KEDNE	I-MISC	O
re	I-MISC	O
Cap	I-MISC	O
Releases	I-MISC	O
-2-F.doc	I-MISC	O

A	O	O
heartwarming	O	O
story	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
advances	O	O
of	O	O
women	O	O
in	O	O
achieving	O	O
equality	O	O
throughout	O	O
the	O	O
world	O	O
.	O	O

Barbara	B-PER	O
Walters	I-PER	O
did	O	O
a	O	O
story	O	O
on	O	O
gender	O	O
roles	O	O
in	O	O
Kuwait	B-LOC	O
several	O	O
years	O	O
before	O	O
the	O	O
Gulf	B-MISC	B-LOC
War	I-MISC	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
noted	O	O
then	O	O
that	O	O
women	O	O
customarily	O	O
walked	O	O
about	O	O
10	O	O
feet	O	O
behind	O	O
their	O	O
husbands	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
returned	O	O
to	O	O
Kuwait	B-LOC	O
recently	O	O
and	O	O
observed	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
men	O	O
now	O	O
walked	O	O
several	O	O
yards	O	O
behind	O	O
their	O	O
wives	O	O
.	O	O

Ms.	O	O
Walters	B-PER	O
approached	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
women	O	O
and	O	O
said	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
This	O	O
is	O	O
marvelous	O	O
.	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
tell	O	O
the	O	O
free	O	O
world	O	O
just	O	O
what	O	O
enabled	O	O
women	O	O
here	O	O
to	O	O
achieve	O	O
this	O	O
reversal	O	O
of	O	O
roles	O	O
?	O	O
"	O	O

"	O	O
Land	O	O
mines	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
said	O	O
the	O	O
Kuwaiti	B-LOCderiv	O
woman	O	O
.	O	O

Cullen	B-ORG	B-PER
and	I-ORG	O
Dykman	I-ORG	B-PER
(	O	O
attorneys	O	O
for	O	O
Boston	B-ORG	B-LOC
Gas	I-ORG	O
Company	I-ORG	O
)	O	O
approved	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
our	O	O
changes	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
agreement	O	O
to	O	O
release	O	O
the	O	O
Tenn	B-LOC	O
and	O	O
Iroq	B-ORG	O
space	O	O
back	O	O
to	O	O
Boston	B-ORG	B-LOC
Gas	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
also	O	O
made	O	O
one	O	O
other	O	O
change	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
taking	O	O
out	O	O
the	O	O
"	O	O
subject	O	O
to	O	O
recall	O	O
"	O	O
language	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
bottom	O	O
of	O	O
page	O	O
2	O	O
under	O	O
item	O	O
#	O	O
1	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
sending	O	O
the	O	O
revised	O	O
document	O	O
to	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
deliver	O	O
it	O	O
to	O	O
you	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
approval	O	O
.	O	O

Maybe	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
go	O	O
drinking	O	O
too	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
fun	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'll	O	O
be	O	O
at	O	O
your	O	O
house	O	O
around	O	O
10:30	O	O
or	O	O
11	O	O
tonight	O	O
.	O	O

YOU	O	O
REALLY	O	O
DO	O	O
NOT	O	O
HAVE	O	O
TO	O	O
GO	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
KNOW	O	O
YOU	O	O
HAVE	O	O
A	O	O
LOT	O	O
GOING	O	O
ON	O	O
WITH	O	O
YOU	O	O
AND	O	O
THE	O	O
LITTLE	O	O
WOMAN	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
CAN	O	O
HANDLE	O	O
THE	O	O
TRACTOR	O	O
.	O	O

love	O	O
TO	O	O
HAVE	O	O
YOU	O	O
ALONG	O	O
FOR	O	O
THE	O	O
COMPANY	O	O
,	O	O
BUT	O	O
IT	O	O
IS	O	O
NOT	O	O
NECESSARY	O	O
.	O	O

YOU	O	O
HAVE	O	O
A	O	O
LOT	O	O
ON	O	O
YOU	O	O
PLATE	O	O
,	O	O
DAD	O	O
.	O	O

Chris.Germany@enron.com	B-PER	O
on	O	O
01/25/2002	O	O
03:13:58	O	O
PM	O	O

Funny	O	O
.	O	O

No	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
feel	O	O
guilty	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
garage	O	O
sale	O	O
,	O	O
that	O	O
's	O	O
why	O	O
I	O	O
was	O	O
annoyed	O	O
-	O	O
being	O	O
notified	O	O
at	O	O
10:00	O	O
at	O	O
night	O	O
GRRRRRRR	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
do	O	O
feel	O	O
guilty	O	O
about	O	O
you	O	O
doing	O	O
all	O	O
this	O	O
work	O	O
.	O	O

So	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
going	O	O
with	O	O
you	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
pay	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
gas	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
twinkies	O	O
.	O	O

Correction	O	O
,	O	O

Jack	B-PER	O
welch	I-PER	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
CEO	O	O
of	O	O
GE	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
not	O	O
GM	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O
Kaminski	I-PER	O

The	O	O
eThink	B-ORG	O
Team	O	O

We	O	O
recently	O	O
asked	O	O
you	O	O
to	O	O
create	O	O
an	O	O
eSpeak	B-MISC	O
"	O	O
wish	O	O
list	O	O
"	O	O
for	O	O
us	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
response	O	O
was	O	O
tremendous	O	O
and	O	O
,	O	O
in	O	O
some	O	O
cases	O	O
,	O	O
very	O	O
creative	O	O
.	O	O

Your	O	O
fellow	O	O
employees	O	O
asked	O	O
for	O	O
everyone	O	O
from	O	O
Britney	B-PER	O
Spears	I-PER	O
to	O	O
George	B-PER	O
Bush	I-PER	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
all	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
received	O	O
requests	O	O
for	O	O
61	O	O
persons	O	O
outside	O	O
of	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
to	O	O
host	O	O
an	O	O
eSpeak	B-MISC	O
event	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
thought	O	O
you	O	O
might	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
know	O	O
who	O	O
your	O	O
colleagues	O	O
find	O	O
interesting	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
we	O	O
've	O	O
provided	O	O
a	O	O
sampling	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
suggestions	O	O
below	O	O
.	O	O

Here	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
top	O	O
ten	O	O
most	O	O
requested	O	O
eSpeakers	B-MISCderiv	O
.	O	O

10	O	O
.	O	O
Jack	B-PER	O
Welch	I-PER	O
,	O	O
CEO	O	O
,	O	O
General	B-ORG	O
Motors	I-ORG	O

9	O	O
.	O	O
Scott	B-PER	O
McNeally	I-PER	O
,	O	O
CEO	O	O
,	O	O
Sun	B-ORG	O
Microsystems	I-ORG	O

8	O	O
.	O	O
Satisfied	O	O
Enron	I-ORG	O
Customers	O	O

7	O	O
.	O	O
Stephen	B-PER	O
Covey	I-PER	O
,	O	O
author	O	O
,	O	O
The	B-MISC	O
Seven	I-MISC	O
Habits	I-MISC	O
of	I-MISC	O
Highly	I-MISC	O
Effective	I-MISC	O
People	I-MISC	O

6	O	O
.	O	O
Oprah	B-PER	O
Winfrey	I-PER	O
,	O	O
talkshow	O	O
host	O	O

5	O	O
.	O	O
General	O	O
Colin	B-PER	O
Powell	I-PER	O
,	O	O
former	O	O
Chairman	O	O
,	O	O
Joint	B-ORG	O
Chiefs	I-ORG	O
of	I-ORG	O
Staff	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
U.S.A	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

4	O	O
.	O	O
Alan	B-PER	O
Greenspan	I-PER	O
,	O	O
Chairman	O	O
,	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	O
Reserve	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
U.S.A	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

3	O	O
.	O	O
Former	O	O
U.S.	B-LOCderiv	O
President	O	O
George	B-PER	O
Bush	I-PER	O

2	O	O
.	O	O
Bill	B-PER	O
Gates	I-PER	O
,	O	O
CEO	O	O
,	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O

1	O	O
.	O	O
Texas	B-LOC	O
Governor	O	O
George	B-PER	O
W.	I-PER	O
Bush	I-PER	O

While	O	O
we	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
make	O	O
any	O	O
promises	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
do	O	O
our	O	O
best	O	O
to	O	O
bring	O	O
in	O	O
at	O	O
least	O	O
some	O	O
of	O	O
these	O	O
special	O	O
guests	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
any	O	O
contacts	O	O
who	O	O
could	O	O
help	O	O
us	O	O
get	O	O
in	O	O
touch	O	O
with	O	O
these	O	O
guest	O	O
speakers	O	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
let	O	O
us	O	O
know	O	O
at	O	O
ethink@enron.com	B-MISC	O
.	O	O

Everybody	O	O
needs	O	O
a	O	O
little	O	O
help	O	O
now	O	O
and	O	O
then	O	O
,	O	O
even	O	O
eSpeak	B-MISC	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
were	O	O
plenty	O	O
of	O	O
internal	O	O
speakers	O	O
requested	O	O
,	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
.	O	O

Those	O	O
requests	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
somewhat	O	O
easier	O	O
to	O	O
meet	O	O
,	O	O
although	O	O
scheduling	O	O
time	O	O
with	O	O
some	O	O
of	O	O
our	O	O
colleagues	O	O
can	O	O
be	O	O
quite	O	O
a	O	O
task	O	O
!	O	O

Thank	O	O
you	O	O
all	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
participation	O	O
.	O	O

Dale	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Confirmed	O	O
.	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Vince	B-PER	O
:	O	O

7	O	O
am	O	O
at	O	O
Hyatt	B-ORG	B-PER
Regency	I-ORG	O
Downtown	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
perfect	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
see	O	O
you	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
lobby	O	O
at	O	O
7	O	O
am	O	O
.	O	O

Best	O	O
regards	O	O
,	O	O

Dale	B-PER	O

Dale	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Friday	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
bad	O	O
day	O	O
(	O	O
Performance	O	O
Review	O	O
Committee	O	O
all	O	O
day	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
about	O	O
7:00	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
office	O	O
or	O	O
breakfast	O	O
meeting	O	O
at	O	O
7:00	O	O
?	O	O

We	O	O
can	O	O
meet	O	O
at	O	O
Hyatt	B-ORG	B-PER
Regency	I-ORG	O
Downtown	O	O
(	O	O
Smith	B-LOC	B-PER
Street	I-LOC	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Vince	B-PER	O
:	O	O

Can	O	O
we	O	O
get	O	O
together	O	O
Friday	O	O
morning	O	O
July	O	O
7	O	O
at	O	O
800	O	O
am	O	O
at	O	O
your	O	O
office	O	O
?	O	O

That	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
particularly	O	O
convenient	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
leave	O	O
downtown	O	O
at	O	O
about	O	O
945	O	O
to	O	O
catch	O	O
a	O	O
plane	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
will	O	O
ensure	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
wo	O	O
nt	O	O
take	O	O
up	O	O
too	O	O
much	O	O
of	O	O
your	O	O
time	O	O
!!	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
efforts	O	O
here	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
thanks	O	O
for	O	O
being	O	O
patient	O	O
with	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

Dale	B-PER	O
Nesbitt	I-PER	O

FYI	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O
sold	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
'll	O	O
initiate	O	O
the	O	O
call	O	O
.	O	O

Ed	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Thursday	O	O
works	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
about	O	O
10:30	O	O
my	O	O
time	O	O
?	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Please	O	O
respond	O	O
to	O	O
<	O	O
ekrapels@esaibos.com	B-PER	O
>	O	O

how	O	O
about	O	O
Thursday	O	O
,	O	O
July	O	O
6	O	O
?	O	O

Ed	B-PER	O
,	O	O

A	O	O
correction	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
shall	O	O
spend	O	O
an	O	O
entire	O	O
day	O	O
at	O	O
PRC	B-ORG	O
(	O	O
performance	O	O
review	O	O
)	O	O
on	O	O
Friday	O	O
,	O	O
July	O	O
7	O	O
.	O	O

Can	O	O
we	O	O
do	O	O
on	O	O
another	O	O
day	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Please	O	O
respond	O	O
to	O	O
<	O	O
ekrapels@esaibos.com	B-PER	O
>	O	O

I	O	O
'll	O	O
still	O	O
be	O	O
here	O	O
in	O	O
Boston	B-LOC	O
so	O	O
we	O	O
'd	O	O
do	O	O
it	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
phone	O	O
.	O	O

OK	O	O
?	O	O

Ed	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Will	O	O
you	O	O
be	O	O
in	O	O
Houston	B-LOC	O
on	O	O
that	O	O
day	O	O
or	O	O
we	O	O
shall	O	O
do	O	O
it	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
phone	O	O
?	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Please	O	O
respond	O	O
to	O	O
<	O	O
ekrapels@esaibos.com	B-PER	O
>	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O
,	O	O

How	O	O
about	O	O
a	O	O
pre-meeting	O	O
web	O	O
site	O	O
cruise	O	O
on	O	O
Friday	O	O
,	O	O
July	O	O
7	O	O
at	O	O
11	O	O
AM	O	O
EDT	O	O
?	O	O

Ed	B-PER	O

Ed	B-PER	O
,	O	O

July	O	O
12	O	O
,	O	O
2:30	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
the	O	O
pre-meeting	O	O
site	O	O
cruise	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
can	O	O
we	O	O
arrange	O	O
it	O	O
?	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Please	O	O
respond	O	O
to	O	O
<	O	O
ekrapels@esaibos.com	B-PER	O
>	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O
,	O	O

We	O	O
're	O	O
all	O	O
set	O	O
for	O	O
2:30	O	O
on	O	O
July	O	O
12	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
about	O	O
a	O	O
pre-meeting	O	O
web	O	O
site	O	O
cruise	O	O
on	O	O
Friday	O	O
,	O	O
July	O	O
7	O	O
at	O	O
11	O	O
AM	O	O
EDT	O	O
?	O	O

Ed	B-PER	O

Ed	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Wednesday	O	O
,	O	O
July	O	O
12	O	O
,	O	O
2:300	O	O
will	O	O
work	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
shall	O	O
be	O	O
glad	O	O
to	O	O
review	O	O
your	O	O
website	O	O
--	O	O
www.weathereffects.com	B-MISC	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
shall	O	O
invite	O	O
some	O	O
people	O	O
who	O	O
work	O	O
on	O	O
electricity	O	O
in	O	O
my	O	O
group	O	O
to	O	O
join	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

Please	O	O
respond	O	O
to	O	O
<	O	O
ekrapels@esaibos.com	B-PER	O
>	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Good	O	O
to	O	O
hear	O	O
from	O	O
you	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
glad	O	O
you	O	O
're	O	O
available	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
is	O	O
Wednesday	O	O
at	O	O
2:30	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
did	O	O
look	O	O
at	O	O
EOL	O	O
and	O	O
am	O	O
not	O	O
surprised	O	O
to	O	O
see	O	O
its	O	O
quality	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
unable	O	O
to	O	O
say	O	O
much	O	O
about	O	O
it	O	O
in	O	O
my	O	O
Risk	B-MISC	O
Electricity	I-MISC	O
Hedging	I-MISC	O
and	I-MISC	O
Trading	I-MISC	O
report	O	O
because	O	O
of	O	O
deadline	O	O
pressures	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
site	O	O
doing	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
intrigued	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
competition	O	O
for	O	O
trading	O	O
platforms	O	O
and	O	O
was	O	O
astonished	O	O
to	O	O
hear	O	O
that	O	O
Goldman	B-ORG	B-PER
,	O	O
Morgan	B-ORG	B-PER
,	O	O
BP	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
Shell	B-ORG	O
were	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
launch	O	O
a	O	O
site	O	O
to	O	O
compete	O	O
with	O	O
yours	O	O
.	O	O

Talk	O	O
about	O	O
a	O	O
shotgun	O	O
marriage	O	O
!	O	O

If	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
time	O	O
next	O	O
week	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
could	O	O
step	O	O
you	O	O
through	O	O
our	O	O
website	O	O
--	O	O
www.weathereffects.com	B-MISC	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
very	O	O
proud	O	O
of	O	O
what	O	O
we	O	O
've	O	O
done	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
give	O	O
out	O	O
a	O	O
password	O	O
yet	O	O
but	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
happy	O	O
to	O	O
walk	O	O
through	O	O
the	O	O
site	O	O
with	O	O
you	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
phone	O	O
using	O	O
my	O	O
password	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
ambitious	O	O
site	O	O
--	O	O
with	O	O
state	O	O
-	O	O
of	O	O
-	O	O
the	O	O
-	O	O
art	O	O
WSI	B-ORG	O
weather	O	O
(	O	O
seasonal	O	O
,	O	O
6	O	O
-	O	O
10	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
day	O	O
to	O	O
day	O	O
)	O	O
driving	O	O
a	O	O
good	O	O
load	O	O
model	O	O
for	O	O
PJM	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
NEPOOL	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

ESAI	B-ORG	O
contributes	O	O
oil	O	O
and	O	O
gas	O	O
input	O	O
price	O	O
forecasts	O	O
,	O	O
capacity	O	O
judgments	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
"	O	O
herding	O	O
"	O	O
ideas	O	O
to	O	O
develop	O	O
power	O	O
price	O	O
forecasts	O	O
for	O	O
same	O	O
time	O	O
periods	O	O
.	O	O

After	O	O
one	O	O
month	O	O
's	O	O
full	O	O
-	O	O
bore	O	O
effort	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
pleased	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
results	O	O
(	O	O
e.g.	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
forecast	O	O
Nepool	B-ORG	O
onpeak	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
43	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
turned	O	O
out	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
46	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Have	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
weekend	O	O
.	O	O

Ed	B-PER	O

Ed	B-PER	O
,	O	O

I	O	O
shall	O	O
be	O	O
available	O	O
on	O	O
both	O	O
days	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
about	O	O
Wednesday	O	O
,	O	O
July	O	O
12	O	O
,	O	O
between	O	O
1:30	O	O
and	O	O
4:00	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
,	O	O
let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
what	O	O
time	O	O
would	O	O
work	O	O
for	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
nice	O	O
to	O	O
see	O	O
you	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

Vince	B-PER	O

P.S.	O	O
By	O	O
the	O	O
way	O	O
,	O	O
did	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
chance	O	O
to	O	O
take	O	O
a	O	O
look	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
EOL	O	O
?	O	O

Please	O	O
respond	O	O
to	O	O
ekrapels@esaibos.com	B-PER	O

Caroline	B-PER	O
Abramo@ENRON	I-PER	O

03/02/2001	O	O
10:46	O	O
AM	O	O

what	O	O
do	O	O
you	O	O
think	O	O
?	O	O

Joe_Lardy@cargill.com	B-PER	O
on	O	O
03/02/2001	O	O
10:39:03	O	O
AM	O	O

Currently	O	O
Cargill	B-ORG	B-PER
and	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
15	O	O
MM	O	O
collateral	O	O
threshold	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
possible	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
think	O	O
the	O	O
cleanest	O	O
way	O	O
to	O	O
run	O	O
this	O	O
biz	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
to	O	O
put	O	O
a	O	O
box	O	O
around	O	O
the	O	O
prime	O	O
broker	O	O
biz	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
would	O	O
still	O	O
operate	O	O
under	O	O
the	O	O
master	O	O
isda	B-ORGderiv	O
but	O	O
could	O	O
set	O	O
up	O	O
a	O	O
mutually	O	O
agreeable	O	O
credit	O	O
support	O	O
annex	O	O
for	O	O
this	O	O
biz	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
would	O	O
still	O	O
keep	O	O
the	O	O
20,000,000	O	O
line	O	O
referenced	O	O
in	O	O
Schedule	O	O
B	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
POA	O	O
agreement	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
line	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
POA	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
seperate	O	O
and	O	O
distinct	O	O
measure	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
daily	O	O
collateral	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
20	O	O
mill	O	O
reflects	O	O
gross	O	O
exposure	O	O
.	O	O

Let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
think	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
reasonable	O	O
and	O	O
workable	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
too	O	O
,	O	O
are	O	O
open	O	O
to	O	O
suggestion	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
Global	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
Enron	B-ORG	O
relationships	O	O
are	O	O
very	O	O
important	O	O
and	O	O
a	O	O
high	O	O
priority	O	O
to	O	O
us	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O

Joe	B-PER	O

Joe	B-PER	O
-	O	O

a	O	O
few	O	O
things	O	O
regading	O	O
the	O	O
POA	O	O
/	O	O
Cargill	B-ORG	B-PER
line	O	O
..	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
find	O	O
out	O	O
how	O	O
much	O	O
line	O	O
we	O	O
currently	O	O
have	O	O
available	O	O
...	O	O
you	O	O
probably	O	O
already	O	O
have	O	O
this	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
should	O	O
allocate	O	O
a	O	O
piece	O	O
to	O	O
Global	B-ORG	O
which	O	O
would	O	O
solve	O	O
the	O	O
problem	O	O
of	O	O
other	O	O
Cargill	B-ORG	B-PER
people	O	O
using	O	O
the	O	O
line	O	O
,	O	O
putting	O	O
us	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
limit	O	O
,	O	O
without	O	O
me	O	O
knowing	O	O
...	O	O

We	O	O
could	O	O
change	O	O
the	O	O
language	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
POA	O	O
to	O	O
this	O	O
...	O	O

we	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
go	O	O
over	O	O
Global	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
piece	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Cargill	B-ORG	B-PER
line	O	O
...	O	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
this	O	O
would	O	O
solve	O	O
our	O	O
main	O	O
concern	O	O
...	O	O

Please	O	O
let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
...	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
eager	O	O
to	O	O
keep	O	O
trading	O	O
with	O	O
Global	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
yourselves	O	O
...	O	O

Regards	O	O
,	O	O

Caroline	B-PER	O

Dee	B-PER	O
:	O	O

Let	O	O
me	O	O
know	O	O
if	O	O
we	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
discuss	O	O
anything	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
hopeful	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
ready	O	O
to	O	O
prepare	O	O
execution	O	O
copies	O	O
.	O	O

Regards	O	O
.	O	O

Sara	B-PER	O
Shackleton	I-PER	O

Susan	B-PER	O
Bailey	I-PER	O

02/27/2001	O	O
08:23	O	O
AM	O	O

Dee	B-PER	O
,	O	O

Attached	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
review	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
blacklined	O	O
version	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
:	O	O
(	O	O
a	O	O
)	O	O
Schedule	O	O
and	O	O
(	O	O
b	O	O
)	O	O
Paragraph	O	O
13	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
ISDA	B-ORG	O
Master	O	O
Agreement	O	O
.	O	O
