Extremely	O	O
bad	O	O
customer	O	O
service	O	O

They	O	O
did	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
bad	O	O
job	O	O
with	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
and	O	O
were	O	O
extremely	O	O
rude	O	O
when	O	O
I	O	O
went	O	O
back	O	O
to	O	O
ask	O	O
them	O	O
why	O	O
it	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
work	O	O
for	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
.	O	O

Cj	B-PER	O
and	O	O
company	O	O
did	O	O
all	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
ask	O	O
and	O	O
10	O	O
times	O	O
more	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
food	O	O
was	O	O
out	O	O
standing	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
again	O	O
Saucey	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

Mark	B-PER	O

Excellent	O	O
Tattoo	O	O
Shop	O	O

I	O	O
recently	O	O
got	O	O
a	O	O
tattoo	O	O
done	O	O
at	O	O
Aztec	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
could	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
happier	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
came	O	O
out	O	O
better	O	O
than	O	O
I	O	O
even	O	O
imagined	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
shop	O	O
was	O	O
great	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
service	O	O
was	O	O
excellent	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
employees	O	O
were	O	O
fun	O	O
guys	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
highly	O	O
recommend	O	O
this	O	O
shop	O	O
to	O	O
anyone	O	O
looking	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
quality	O	O
tattoo	O	O
done	O	O
.	O	O

Good	O	O
and	O	O
Bad	O	O

I	O	O
had	O	O
to	O	O
take	O	O
care	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
ants	O	O
myself	O	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
I	O	O
found	O	O
the	O	O
location	O	O
wonderful	O	O
and	O	O
found	O	O
the	O	O
neighbors	O	O
very	O	O
kind	O	O
.	O	O

Never	O	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
problem	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
staff	O	O
and	O	O
found	O	O
them	O	O
very	O	O
helpful	O	O
when	O	O
something	O	O
went	O	O
wrong	O	O
.	O	O

Loved	O	O
the	O	O
pool	O	O
and	O	O
BBQ	O	O
.	O	O

Because	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
ants	O	O
I	O	O
dropped	O	O
them	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
3	O	O
star	O	O
.	O	O

Great	O	O
pet	O	O
care	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
used	O	O
Just	B-ORG	O
Like	I-ORG	O
Family	I-ORG	O
several	O	O
times	O	O
now	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
have	O	O
provided	O	O
great	O	O
care	O	O
for	O	O
my	O	O
two	O	O
dogs	O	O
.	O	O

Lynda	B-PER	O
is	O	O
professional	O	O
and	O	O
has	O	O
great	O	O
compassion	O	O
for	O	O
animals	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
real	O	O
testament	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
in	O	O
how	O	O
much	O	O
she	O	O
likes	O	O
your	O	O
animals	O	O
but	O	O
how	O	O
much	O	O
they	O	O
like	O	O
her	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
highly	O	O
recommend	O	O
her	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
found	O	O
Bright	B-ORG	O
Star	I-ORG	O
Tours	I-ORG	O
and	I-ORG	O
Travels	I-ORG	O
and	O	O
Best	O	O
and	O	O
Affordable	O	O
Tour	O	O
Operators	O	O
and	O	O
Tours	O	O
Agents	O	O
in	O	O
Chennai	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
India	B-LOC	O
offered	O	O
me	O	O
Student	B-MISC	O
Tour	I-MISC	O
India	I-MISC	B-LOC
Package	I-MISC	O
for	O	O
very	O	O
less	O	O
price	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
enjoyed	O	O
my	O	O
tour	O	O
and	O	O
i	O	O
am	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
adventure	O	O
tour	O	O
and	O	O
India	B-LOC	O
heritage	O	O
tours	O	O
for	O	O
valuable	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
Bright	B-ORG	O
Star	I-ORG	O
Tours	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

these	O	O
guys	O	O
were	O	O
fantastic	O	O
!	O	O

GREAT	O	O
JOB	O	O
GUYS	O	O
!	O	O

A	O	O
+	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
rate	O	O
Fran	B-ORG	O
pcs	I-ORG	O
an	O	O
A	O	O
+	O	O
because	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
was	O	O
lower	O	O
than	O	O
everyone	O	O
else	O	O
,	O	O
i	O	O
got	O	O
my	O	O
computer	O	O
back	O	O
the	O	O
next	O	O
day	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
professionalism	O	O
he	O	O
showed	O	O
was	O	O
great	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
took	O	O
the	O	O
time	O	O
to	O	O
explain	O	O
things	O	O
to	O	O
me	O	O
about	O	O
my	O	O
computer	O	O
,	O	O
i	O	O
would	O	O
recommend	O	O
you	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
him	O	O
.	O	O

David	B-PER	O

KB	B-PER	O

FAST	O	O
and	O	O
reasonable	O	O
$	B-MISC	O

We	O	O
went	O	O
to	O	O
Kobey	B-ORG	B-PER
s	I-ORG	I-PER
on	O	O
Saturday	O	O
and	O	O
had	O	O
our	O	O
whole	O	O
team	O	O
s	O	O
uniforms	O	O
done	O	O
!	O	O

He	O	O
was	O	O
less	O	O
than	O	O
half	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
cheapest	O	O
quote	O	O
we	O	O
got	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
his	O	O
work	O	O
was	O	O
top	O	O
notch	O	O
.	O	O

Down	O	O
to	O	O
earth	O	O
and	O	O
fast	O	O
service	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
love	O	O
Little	B-ORG	O
Farmer	I-ORG	O

We	O	O
attend	O	O
LFTD	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
our	O	O
children	O	O
LOVE	O	O
it	O	O
!!	O	O

They	O	O
even	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
school	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
weekends	O	O
!!	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
preparing	O	O
my	O	O
older	O	O
son	O	O
for	O	O
kindergarten	O	O
and	O	O
looks	O	O
forward	O	O
to	O	O
seeing	O	O
his	O	O
teacher	O	O
and	O	O
friends	O	O
every	O	O
day	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
infant	O	O
is	O	O
content	O	O
every	O	O
day	O	O
when	O	O
I	O	O
drop	O	O
off	O	O
and	O	O
pick	O	O
up	O	O
.	O	O

PAT	O	O
testing	O	O
quick	O	O
&	O	O
efficient	O	O

Fantastic	O	O
,	O	O
quick	O	O
and	O	O
efficient	O	O
service	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
rare	O	O
!	O	O

Well	O	O
done	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
favorite	O	O
florist	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
came	O	O
to	O	O
La	B-LOC	O
Crosse	I-LOC	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
college	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
my	O	O
mom	O	O
would	O	O
send	O	O
me	O	O
birthday	O	O
flowers	O	O
though	O	O
here	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
were	O	O
beautiful	O	O
and	O	O
lasted	O	O
forever	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
went	O	O
from	O	O
a	O	O
pain	O	O
scale	O	O
of	O	O
8	O	O
-	O	O
9	O	O
to	O	O
0	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
was	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
run	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
Crim	B-MISC	B-ORG
just	O	O
a	O	O
week	O	O
later	O	O
!!	O	O

happy	O	O
customer	O	O

Mr.	B-ORG	O
Squeege	I-ORG	O
is	O	O
THE	O	O
BEST	O	O
.	O	O

Prompt	O	O
,	O	O
Clean	O	O
Windows	B-MISC	O
.	O	O

Affordable	O	O
pricing	O	O
.	O	O

Friendly	O	O
responses	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
else	O	O
can	O	O
excellent	O	O
be	O	O
described	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
business	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
sort	O	O
?	O	O

They	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
my	O	O
only	O	O
"	O	O
go	O	O
-	O	O
to	O	O
"	O	O
resource	O	O
since	O	O
we	O	O
first	O	O
did	O	O
business	O	O
together	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
will	O	O
find	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
true	O	O
for	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

Fantastic	O	O
Place	O	O
to	O	O
buy	O	O
your	O	O
next	O	O
vehicle	O	O

This	O	O
is	O	O
car	O	O
number	O	O
3	O	O
we	O	O
've	O	O
purchased	O	O
through	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
trust	O	O
and	O	O
appreciate	O	O
Scott	B-PER	O
Larson	I-PER	O
and	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
he	O	O
will	O	O
always	O	O
take	O	O
good	O	O
care	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
and	O	O
listen	O	O
to	O	O
our	O	O
needs	O	O
!	O	O

Thank	O	O
you	O	O
again	O	O
for	O	O
great	O	O
customer	O	O
service	O	O
!	O	O

Range	B-MISC	O
Rover	I-MISC	O
Sport	I-MISC	O
Window	O	O
Tints	O	O

Mark	B-PER	O
at	O	O
Tintman	B-ORG	B-PER
Nationwide	I-ORG	O
tints	I-ORG	O
Ltd	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
did	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
Professional	O	O
job	O	O
very	O	O
quick	O	O
,	O	O
no	O	O
fuss	O	O
,	O	O
deliverd	O	O
the	O	O
car	O	O
to	O	O
me	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
drove	O	O
him	O	O
back	O	O
home	O	O
,	O	O
Great	O	O
arrangement	O	O
Great	O	O
price	O	O
!!	O	O

Highly	O	O
recommended	O	O
!!	O	O

Thanks	O	O
Mark	B-PER	O
.	O	O

Steve	B-PER	O
....	O	O
proud	O	O
Range	B-MISC	O
Rover	I-MISC	O
Sport	I-MISC	O
owner	O	O
(	O	O
with	O	O
rear	O	O
tints	O	O
)	O	O

In	O	O
this	O	O
hard	O	O
economic	O	O
times	O	O
is	O	O
very	O	O
important	O	O
to	O	O
save	O	O
money	O	O
Very	O	O
reasonable	O	O
prices	O	O
top	O	O
quality	O	O
work	O	O
The	O	O
owner	O	O
operator	O	O
he	O	O
does	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
the	O	O
work	O	O
with	O	O
Helpers	O	O
very	O	O
friendly	O	O
I	O	O
definitely	O	O
recommend	O	O
this	O	O
this	O	O
guys	O	O
Do	O	O
n't	O	O
get	O	O
jack	O	O
by	O	O
big	O	O
companies	O	O
that	O	O
they	O	O
pay	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
of	O	O
money	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
on	O	O
top	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
list	O	O
Thanks	O	O

awful	O	O
awful	O	O
awful	O	O

This	O	O
store	O	O
is	O	O
by	O	O
far	O	O
the	O	O
worst	O	O
Verizon	B-ORG	O
store	O	O
I	O	O
've	O	O
been	O	O
in	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
salespeople	O	O
are	O	O
never	O	O
available	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
lines	O	O
are	O	O
always	O	O
too	O	O
long	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
people	O	O
want	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
sale	O	O
.	O	O

Incredibly	O	O
rude	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
return	O	O
to	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Is	O	O
there	O	O
no	O	O
other	O	O
Verizon	B-ORG	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
around	O	O
Downtown	B-LOC	O
/	O	O
Dupont	B-LOC	B-PER
Circle	I-LOC	O
1?!?!?	O	O

Great	O	O
graphic	O	O
design	O	O
work	O	O
!	O	O

Fresh	B-ORG	O
Design	I-ORG	O
Studio	I-ORG	O
helped	O	O
jump	O	O
-	O	O
start	O	O
my	O	O
own	O	O
business	O	O
by	O	O
providing	O	O
affordable	O	O
and	O	O
effective	O	O
marketing	O	O
materials	O	O
:	O	O
logo	O	O
,	O	O
flyers	O	O
,	O	O
posters	O	O
ad	O	O
design	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
more	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
have	O	O
unbeatable	O	O
price	O	O
in	O	O
town	O	O
and	O	O
deliver	O	O
on	O	O
time	O	O
.	O	O

Great	O	O
Surgeon	O	O

I	O	O
needed	O	O
wisdom	O	O
teeth	O	O
taken	O	O
out	O	O
.	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Wallen	B-PER	O
and	O	O
staff	O	O
was	O	O
excellent	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
were	O	O
accomdating	O	O
with	O	O
my	O	O
scheduled	O	O
and	O	O
work	O	O
with	O	O
my	O	O
insurance	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
payment	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
surgery	O	O
.	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Wallen	B-PER	O
explained	O	O
the	O	O
procedure	O	O
in	O	O
detail	O	O
and	O	O
took	O	O
his	O	O
time	O	O
with	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

Staff	O	O
explained	O	O
insurance	O	O
procedures	O	O
and	O	O
was	O	O
very	O	O
helpful	O	O
.	O	O

Everyone	O	O
was	O	O
very	O	O
nice	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
best	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
area	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
've	O	O
been	O	O
to	O	O
quite	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
tattoo	O	O
shops	O	O
around	O	O
this	O	O
area	O	O
and	O	O
Stainless	B-ORG	O
Steel	I-ORG	O
is	O	O
by	O	O
far	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
very	O	O
pleased	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
tattoos	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
revived	O	O
from	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
artwork	O	O
is	O	O
excellent	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
prices	O	O
are	O	O
very	O	O
reasonable	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
recommend	O	O
this	O	O
shop	O	O
to	O	O
anyone	O	O
looking	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
tattoo	O	O
.	O	O

Cathy	B-PER	O
******	O	O
Five	O	O
Stars	O	O
for	O	O
Lake	B-ORG	B-LOC
Forest	I-ORG	I-LOC
Tots	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
program	O	O
has	O	O
been	O	O
a	O	O
postive	O	O
experience	O	O
for	O	O
my	O	O
children	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
had	O	O
all	O	O
three	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
children	O	O
attend	O	O
Lake	B-ORG	B-LOC
Forest	I-ORG	I-LOC
Tots	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
program	O	O
is	O	O
well	O	O
established	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
extremely	O	O
satisfied	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
teachers	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
programs	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
director	O	O
.	O	O

Good	O	O
job	O	O
,	O	O
Lake	B-ORG	B-LOC
Forest	I-ORG	I-LOC
Tots	I-ORG	O
!	O	O

Great	O	O
Wine	O	O
&	O	O
Service	O	O

The	O	O
employees	O	O
make	O	O
you	O	O
feel	O	O
very	O	O
comfortable	O	O
and	O	O
are	O	O
very	O	O
helpful	O	O
,	O	O
whether	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
very	O	O
knowledgeable	O	O
or	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
know	O	O
anything	O	O
at	O	O
all	O	O
about	O	O
wine	O	O
.	O	O

A	O	O
+	O	O

Excellent	O	O
customer	O	O
service	O	O
and	O	O
honest	O	O
feedback	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
team	O	O
at	O	O
Bradley	B-ORG	B-PER
Chevron	I-ORG	O
kept	O	O
my	O	O
car	O	O
running	O	O
for	O	O
well	O	O
past	O	O
its	O	O
expected	O	O
death	O	O
!	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
honest	O	O
about	O	O
'	O	O
immediate	O	O
'	O	O
concerns	O	O
versus	O	O
'	O	O
recommended	O	O
'	O	O
repairs	O	O
and	O	O
have	O	O
very	O	O
fair	O	O
prices	O	O
.	O	O

Such	O	O
a	O	O
convenient	O	O
location	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
with	O	O
coffee	O	O
shop	O	O
and	O	O
bradley	O	O
food	O	O
and	O	O
beverage	O	O
right	O	O
around	O	O
corner	O	O
.	O	O

Needs	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
business	O	O

They	O	O
close	O	O
whenever	O	O
they	O	O
feel	O	O
like	O	O
it	O	O
,	O	O
often	O	O
well	O	O
before	O	O
their	O	O
listed	O	O
closing	O	O
time	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
take	O	O
coupons	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
credit	O	O
card	O	O
minimum	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
place	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
opposite	O	O
of	O	O
QuikTrip	B-ORG	O
:	O	O
crappy	O	O
in	O	O
every	O	O
way	O	O
.	O	O

Baffled	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
one	O	O
-	O	O
star	O	O
reviews	O	O

I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
get	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
place	O	O
is	O	O
awesome	O	O
,	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
ambiance	O	O
and	O	O
cool	O	O
décor	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
food	O	O
is	O	O
scrumptious	O	O
(	O	O
and	O	O
especially	O	O
their	O	O
signature	O	O
banana	O	O
split	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Sure	O	O
,	O	O
some	O	O
items	O	O
are	O	O
a	O	O
little	O	O
pricey	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
c'm	O	O
on	O	O
...	O	O
have	O	O
you	O	O
ever	O	O
been	O	O
out	O	O
to	O	O
eat	O	O
in	O	O
Seattle	B-LOC	O
before	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
highly	O	O
recommend	O	O
Debi	B-PER	O
,	O	O
she	O	O
does	O	O
an	O	O
amazing	O	O
job	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
"	O	O
love	O	O
"	O	O
the	O	O
way	O	O
she	O	O
cuts	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
,	O	O
extremely	O	O
thorough	O	O
and	O	O
cross	O	O
checks	O	O
her	O	O
work	O	O
to	O	O
make	O	O
sure	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
is	O	O
perfect	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
always	O	O
leave	O	O
loving	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
style	O	O
.	O	O

Pure	O	O
Pilates	O	O
!!	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
real	O	O
thing	O	O
-	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
practicing	O	O
Pilates	O	O
for	O	O
over	O	O
7	O	O
years	O	O
and	O	O
would	O	O
not	O	O
go	O	O
anywhere	O	O
else	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
phoned	O	O
this	O	O
company	O	O
for	O	O
advice	O	O
on	O	O
our	O	O
office	O	O
refurb	O	O
and	O	O
although	O	O
we	O	O
did	O	O
not	O	O
use	O	O
them	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
end	O	O
(	O	O
as	O	O
our	O	O
building	O	O
contractor	O	O
carried	O	O
out	O	O
the	O	O
electrical	O	O
work	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
provided	O	O
me	O	O
with	O	O
plenty	O	O
of	O	O
useful	O	O
information	O	O
over	O	O
an	O	O
hour	O	O
phone	O	O
call	O	O
and	O	O
subsequently	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
now	O	O
using	O	O
PJC	B-ORG	O
as	O	O
our	O	O
electrical	O	O
maintenance	O	O
contractor	O	O
.	O	O

Thoroughly	O	O
recommended	O	O

They	O	O
really	O	O
go	O	O
above	O	O
and	O	O
beyond	O	O
!	O	O

For	O	O
example	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
actually	O	O
forgot	O	O
to	O	O
feed	O	O
my	O	O
cat	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
went	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
their	O	O
way	O	O
to	O	O
take	O	O
care	O	O
of	O	O
him	O	O
.	O	O

Additionally	O	O
,	O	O
when	O	O
there	O	O
was	O	O
confusion	O	O
(	O	O
my	O	O
fault	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
left	O	O
me	O	O
flowers	O	O
along	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
personalized	O	O
gift	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
100	O	O
%	O	O
reliable	O	O
and	O	O
professional	O	O
.	O	O

Definitely	O	O
recommend	O	O
!	O	O

heating	O	O
system	O	O
Angels	O	O

BAD	O	O
COFFEE	O	O
,	O	O
DO	O	O
NT	O	O
BOTHER	O	O
!	O	O

Ca	O	O
n't	O	O
you	O	O
make	O	O
a	O	O
decent	O	O
cup	O	O
of	O	O
coffee	O	O
?	O	O

You	O	O
charge	O	O
SO	O	O
MUCH	O	O
,	O	O
yet	O	O
you	O	O
use	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
grounds	O	O
over	O	O
and	O	O
over	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
coffee	O	O
taste	O	O
BURNT	O	O
and	O	O
very	O	O
bitter	O	O
.	O	O

No	O	O
amount	O	O
of	O	O
sugar	O	O
and	O	O
milk	O	O
can	O	O
mask	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

CHANGE	O	O
THE	O	O
PROCESS	O	O
,	O	O
PPL	O	O
!	O	O

Westfield	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
Rt	B-ORG	O
1	I-ORG	O
do	O	O
it	O	O
well	O	O
,	O	O
WHY	O	O
CA	O	O
NT	O	O
U	O	O
????	O	O

Home	O	O
made	O	O
product	O	O

I	O	O
sometimes	O	O
go	O	O
into	O	O
this	O	O
store	O	O
just	O	O
for	O	O
something	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
sunday	O	O
afternoon	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
love	O	O
the	O	O
people	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
product	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
service	O	O
!	O	O

The	O	O
Brick	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
Ikea	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
Leon	B-PER	B-PER
's	I-ORG	I-PER
have	O	O
their	O	O
place	O	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
furniture	O	O
like	O	O
this	O	O
will	O	O
truly	O	O
be	O	O
around	O	O
forever	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
internet	O	O
here	O	O
is	O	O
terrible	O	O
.	O	O

Like	O	O
the	O	O
previous	O	O
poster	O	O
said	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
com	O	O
lines	O	O
are	O	O
split	O	O
between	O	O
the	O	O
entire	O	O
building	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
's	O	O
3	O	O
x	O	O
worse	O	O
than	O	O
Qwest	B-ORG	O
DSL	I-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
lowest	O	O
speed	O	O
offering	O	O
!	O	O

The	O	O
outward	O	O
appearance	O	O
makes	O	O
you	O	O
think	O	O
this	O	O
place	O	O
is	O	O
nice	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
everything	O	O
inside	O	O
is	O	O
cheap	O	O
cheap	O	O
cheap	O	O
.	O	O

Moving	O	O
out	O	O
as	O	O
soon	O	O
as	O	O
our	O	O
lease	O	O
is	O	O
up	O	O
.	O	O

http://www.speedtest.net/result/1155244347.png	B-MISC	O

Awesome	O	O
!!!!	O	O

Yes	O	O
my	O	O
G	B-MISC	O
1	I-MISC	O
screen	O	O
is	O	O
back	O	O
working	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
was	O	O
about	O	O
to	O	O
Charge	O	O
me	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
129	O	O
...	O	O

But	O	O
i	O	O
paid	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
100	O	O
.	O	O

they	O	O
save	O	O
me	O	O
from	O	O
having	O	O
to	O	O
deal	O	O
with	O	O
Tmobile	B-ORG	O
...	O	O

Tmobile	B-ORG	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
Send	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
phone	O	O
and	O	O
i	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
thru	O	O
that	O	O
...	O	O

3	O	O
Days	O	O
For	O	O
get	O	O
that	O	O
...	O	O

Great	O	O
service	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
recommend	O	O
them	O	O
to	O	O
anyone	O	O
..	O	O

Great	O	O
out	O	O
night	O	O
!	O	O

And	O	O
then	O	O
wait	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

Not	O	O
organised	O	O
.	O	O

Hair	B-ORG	O
By	I-ORG	O
Nivine	I-ORG	B-PER
in	O	O
eastgardens	B-LOC	O
fixed	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
after	O	O
i	O	O
had	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
cut	O	O
and	O	O
colored	O	O
at	O	O
another	O	O
salon	O	O
i	O	O
felt	O	O
more	O	O
confident	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
girls	O	O
are	O	O
fantastic	O	O
and	O	O
i	O	O
ve	O	O
been	O	O
going	O	O
there	O	O
now	O	O
for	O	O
2	O	O
years	O	O
always	O	O
happy	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
care	O	O
about	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
had	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
done	O	O
for	O	O
my	O	O
wedding	O	O
it	O	O
looked	O	O
fabolous	O	O
!	O	O

and	O	O
there	O	O
prices	O	O
are	O	O
really	O	O
good	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
end	O	O
up	O	O
buying	O	O
my	O	O
car	O	O
here	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
I	O	O
did	O	O
think	O	O
the	O	O
guy	O	O
who	O	O
worked	O	O
with	O	O
me	O	O
was	O	O
pretty	O	O
cool	O	O
-	O	O
he	O	O
was	O	O
willing	O	O
to	O	O
budge	O	O
a	O	O
little	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
which	O	O
means	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
to	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
they	O	O
will	O	O
fill	O	O
your	O	O
tires	O	O
with	O	O
air	O	O
and	O	O
other	O	O
small	O	O
maintenance	O	O
tasks	O	O
for	O	O
free	O	O
,	O	O
even	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
buy	O	O
your	O	O
car	O	O
there	O	O
!	O	O

The	O	O
Best	O	O
Deals	O	O
in	O	O
Town	O	O

Their	O	O
selection	O	O
is	O	O
random	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
what	O	O
they	O	O
have	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
given	O	O
week	O	O
might	O	O
never	O	O
be	O	O
available	O	O
again	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
store	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
love	O	O
it	O	O
for	O	O
discounted	O	O
beauty	O	O
items	O	O
and	O	O
household	O	O
appliances	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
service	O	O
at	O	O
Instep	B-ORG	O
was	O	O
great	O	O
!!	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
recommend	O	O
them	O	O
to	O	O
anyone	O	O
!	O	O

Outstanding	O	O
service	O	O
&	O	O
quality	O	O
at	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
affordable	O	O
price	O	O
!	O	O

This	O	O
place	O	O
is	O	O
top	O	O
notch	O	O
and	O	O
highly	O	O
affordable	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
recommend	O	O
it	O	O
hands	O	O
down	O	O
and	O	O
am	O	O
a	O	O
loyal	O	O
customer	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
've	O	O
also	O	O
sent	O	O
over	O	O
a	O	O
number	O	O
of	O	O
friends	O	O
to	O	O
use	O	O
the	O	O
services	O	O
here	O	O
and	O	O
everyone	O	O
is	O	O
extraordinarily	O	O
pleased	O	O
!	O	O

Thanks	O	O
for	O	O
doing	O	O
such	O	O
great	O	O
work	O	O
on	O	O
my	O	O
important	O	O
pieces	O	O
of	O	O
clothing	O	O
that	O	O
always	O	O
look	O	O
great	O	O
!	O	O

Tried	O	O
Crust	B-ORG	O
on	O	O
Broad	B-LOC	O
on	O	O
3	O	O
occasions	O	O
.	O	O

Twice	O	O
for	O	O
dinner	O	O
and	O	O
once	O	O
for	O	O
lunch	O	O
Absolutely	O	O
rude	O	O
service	O	O
every	O	O
time	O	O
!	O	O

The	O	O
staff	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
even	O	O
answer	O	O
the	O	O
phone	O	O
for	O	O
take	O	O
out	O	O
.	O	O

Tonight	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
called	O	O
several	O	O
times	O	O
with	O	O
no	O	O
answer	O	O
(	O	O
Btwn	O	O
5:30	O	O
and	O	O
6	O	O
pm	O	O
)	O	O
and	O	O
finally	O	O
drove	O	O
there	O	O
to	O	O
place	O	O
my	O	O
order	O	O
in	O	O
person	O	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
was	O	O
not	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
found	O	O
.	O	O

Since	O	O
then	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
decided	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
them	O	O
manage	O	O
our	O	O
other	O	O
investment	O	O
properties	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
as	O	O
we	O	O
getting	O	O
older	O	O
and	O	O
can	O	O
no	O	O
longer	O	O
perform	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
inquires	O	O
.	O	O

Great	O	O
help	O	O
!	O	O

We	O	O
just	O	O
got	O	O
our	O	O
sunroom	O	O
built	O	O
by	O	O
Patio	B-ORG	O
World	I-ORG	O
and	O	O
can	O	O
say	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
extremely	O	O
happy	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
whole	O	O
thing	O	O
.	O	O

From	O	O
the	O	O
amount	O	O
of	O	O
time	O	O
spent	O	O
with	O	O
us	O	O
to	O	O
explain	O	O
things	O	O
during	O	O
the	O	O
initial	O	O
quote	O	O
,	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
communication	O	O
through	O	O
the	O	O
approval	O	O
process	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
actual	O	O
workmanship	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
build	O	O
itself	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
nothing	O	O
bad	O	O
to	O	O
say	O	O
.	O	O

Very	O	O
glad	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
went	O	O
with	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O

No	O	O
Customer	O	O
Service	O	O

Employees	O	O
seemed	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
having	O	O
a	O	O
good	O	O
time	O	O
chatting	O	O
and	O	O
laughing	O	O
with	O	O
each	O	O
other	O	O
,	O	O
while	O	O
myself	O	O
and	O	O
other	O	O
customers	O	O
were	O	O
completely	O	O
ignored	O	O
.	O	O

Another	O	O
person	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
store	O	O
stood	O	O
there	O	O
with	O	O
an	O	O
item	O	O
and	O	O
repeatedly	O	O
tried	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
sales	O	O
person	O	O
s	O	O
attention	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
n't	O	O
until	O	O
he	O	O
gave	O	O
up	O	O
and	O	O
walked	O	O
out	O	O
the	O	O
door	O	O
that	O	O
someone	O	O
asked	O	O
Can	O	O
I	O	O
help	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

do	O	O
NOT	O	O
bring	O	O
your	O	O
car	O	O
here	O	O

Yes	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
accepted	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

However	O	O
,	O	O
during	O	O
the	O	O
test	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
did	O	O
whatever	O	O
they	O	O
can	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
my	O	O
test	O	O
failed	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
called	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
Friday	O	O
at	O	O
12:30	O	O
complaining	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
severe	O	O
toothache	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
had	O	O
been	O	O
a	O	O
patient	O	O
of	O	O
Dr.	O	O
Olbina	B-PER	O
for	O	O
9	O	O
years	O	O
and	O	O
had	O	O
spent	O	O
thousands	O	O
of	O	O
dollars	O	O
on	O	O
crowns	O	O
etc	O	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
are	O	O
plenty	O	O
of	O	O
good	O	O
dentists	O	O
in	O	O
Fernandina	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
Amelia	B-ORG	B-PER
Gentle	I-ORG	O
Dentistry	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

Make	O	O
You	O	O
Feel	O	O
Like	O	O
a	O	O
Number	O	O

Stay	O	O
away	O	O
from	O	O
Kids	B-ORG	O
First	I-ORG	O
West	I-ORG	B-LOC
Chester	I-ORG	I-LOC
.	O	O

You	O	O
NEVER	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
human	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
phone	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
impossible	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
an	O	O
appointment	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
get	O	O
caught	O	O
in	O	O
traffic	O	O
and	O	O
are	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
minutes	O	O
late	O	O
they	O	O
make	O	O
you	O	O
re-schedule	O	O
...	O	O
for	O	O
6	O	O
weeks	O	O
later	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
worst	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
your	O	O
child	O	O
feels	O	O
like	O	O
a	O	O
number	O	O
not	O	O
a	O	O
patient	O	O
.	O	O

Go	O	O
somewhere	O	O
else	O	O
.	O	O

Rcommended	O	O
by	O	O
bees	O	O
,	O	O
too	O	O
!	O	O

Highly	O	O
recommended	O	O
.	O	O

No	O	O
spraying	O	O
of	O	O
pesticides	O	O
!	O	O

Very	O	O
professional	O	O
.	O	O

Reasonable	O	O
rate	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
highly	O	O
recommend	O	O
Joe	B-PER	O
and	O	O
his	O	O
wasp	O	O
removal	O	O
service	O	O
to	O	O
individual	O	O
home	O	O
owners	O	O
and	O	O
condos	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
knows	O	O
his	O	O
bees	O	O
!	O	O

Suzanne	B-PER	O
,	O	O
Vancouver	B-LOC	O

Very	O	O
Accomodating	O	O

GREAT	O	O
SERVICE	O	O
AND	O	O
PEOPLE	O	O
!!	O	O

Deb	B-PER	O
Watson	I-PER	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
contact	O	O
person	O	O
and	O	O
she	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
rest	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
staff	O	O
were	O	O
great	O	O
!!!	O	O

She	O	O
continues	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
me	O	O
when	O	O
needed	O	O
even	O	O
if	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
service	O	O
question	O	O
.	O	O

Since	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
usually	O	O
at	O	O
work	O	O
late	O	O
Deb	B-PER	O
has	O	O
stayed	O	O
around	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
me	O	O
out	O	O
when	O	O
needed	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
was	O	O
after	O	O
I	O	O
brought	O	O
the	O	O
car	O	O
!!!!	O	O
!	O	O

Service	O	O
does	O	O
not	O	O
get	O	O
any	O	O
better	O	O
!!!!	O	O

Hidden	O	O
Gem	O	O
in	O	O
Alpharetta	B-LOC	O

Le	B-ORG	O
petit	I-ORG	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
place	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
your	O	O
nails	O	O
done	O	O
!	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
very	O	O
clean	O	O
,	O	O
staff	O	O
is	O	O
friendly	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
never	O	O
waited	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
go	O	O
every	O	O
other	O	O
week	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
shallac	O	O
/	O	O
gel	O	O
manicure	O	O
which	O	O
is	O	O
only	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
25	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
truly	O	O
lasts	O	O
2	O	O
weeks	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
love	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Pedicures	O	O
are	O	O
also	O	O
great	O	O
.	O	O

Try	O	O
this	O	O
place	O	O
out	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
promise	O	O
you	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
disappointed	O	O
!	O	O

Amazing	O	O
Pictures	O	O
at	O	O
an	O	O
Amazing	O	O
Price	O	O

Rendy	B-PER	O
is	O	O
totally	O	O
amazing	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
gave	O	O
me	O	O
amazing	O	O
pictures	O	O
at	O	O
an	O	O
amazing	O	O
price	O	O
and	O	O
made	O	O
my	O	O
wedding	O	O
day	O	O
so	O	O
memorable	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
was	O	O
way	O	O
easy	O	O
to	O	O
work	O	O
with	O	O
and	O	O
made	O	O
my	O	O
wedding	O	O
day	O	O
so	O	O
easy	O	O
and	O	O
she	O	O
got	O	O
some	O	O
amazing	O	O
pictures	O	O
,	O	O
not	O	O
only	O	O
of	O	O
me	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
family	O	O
and	O	O
friends	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
is	O	O
amazing	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
recommend	O	O
her	O	O
to	O	O
anyone	O	O
!	O	O

So	O	O
very	O	O
delicious	O	O
!	O	O

Excellent	O	O
!	O	O

November	O	O
7	O	O
,	O	O
2010	O	O
First	O	O
time	O	O
eating	O	O
at	O	O
Caffe	B-ORG	O
Bella	I-ORG	O
Italia	I-ORG	B-LOC
and	O	O
it	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
wonderful	O	O
experience	O	O
.	O	O

From	O	O
the	O	O
delectable	O	O
Antipasto	O	O
Misto	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
Spaghetti	O	O
alla	O	O
Barese	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
Parmigiana	O	O
and	O	O
ending	O	O
with	O	O
gelato	O	O
,	O	O
all	O	O
was	O	O
mouth	O	O
watering	O	O
.	O	O

Too	O	O
bad	O	O
they	O	O
were	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Chocolate	O	O
Lava	O	O
Cake	O	O
.	O	O

Maybe	O	O
next	O	O
time	O	O
they	O	O
will	O	O
have	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Service	O	O
was	O	O
excellent	O	O
!	O	O

Sandy	B-PER	O

Excellent	O	O
Physiotherapists	O	O
!	O	O

Kusal	B-PER	O
Goonewardena	I-PER	O
and	O	O
his	O	O
team	O	O
of	O	O
Physios	O	O
are	O	O
unbelievable	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
suffering	O	O
from	O	O
back	O	O
pain	O	O
for	O	O
over	O	O
12	O	O
years	O	O
and	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
to	O	O
numerous	O	O
specialists	O	O
,	O	O
physios	O	O
,	O	O
osteos	O	O
and	O	O
chiros	O	O
with	O	O
no	O	O
help	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
took	O	O
the	O	O
Vigor	B-ORG	O
team	O	O
only	O	O
4	O	O
visits	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
me	O	O
feeling	O	O
normal	O	O
!	O	O

Thanks	O	O
guys	O	O
!	O	O

They	O	O
must	O	O
have	O	O
read	O	O
these	O	O
reviews	O	O
and	O	O
improved	O	O
!	O	O

My	O	O
husband	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
happened	O	O
in	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
whim	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
sat	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
front	O	O
dining	O	O
area	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
was	O	O
very	O	O
cozy	O	O
and	O	O
pleasant	O	O
.	O	O

Our	O	O
server	O	O
was	O	O
quite	O	O
attentive	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
food	O	O
was	O	O
fantastic	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
husband	O	O
has	O	O
been	O	O
a	O	O
professional	O	O
chef	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
he	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
good	O	O
judge	O	O
of	O	O
quality	O	O
food	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
flavorful	O	O
,	O	O
enjoyable	O	O
meal	O	O
for	O	O
both	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
.	O	O

brought	O	O
dog	O	O
home	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
s	O	O
all	O	O
choppy	O	O
now	O	O
!	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
helpful	O	O
to	O	O
know	O	O
a	O	O
quite	O	O
a	O	O
bit	O	O
about	O	O
bull	O	O
fighting	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
watch	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
of	O	O
fights	O	O
(	O	O
youtube	B-ORG	O
)	O	O
and	O	O
research	O	O
some	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
history	O	O
(	O	O
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bullfighting	B-MISC	O
)	O	O
you	O	O
will	O	O
find	O	O
yourself	O	O
enjoying	O	O
it	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
more	O	O
!	O	O

Also	O	O
after	O	O
seeing	O	O
a	O	O
handful	O	O
of	O	O
bullfights	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
say	O	O
that	O	O
they	O	O
're	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
more	O	O
enjoyable	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
're	O	O
smashed	O	O
(	O	O
BAC	O	O
>=	O	O
.15	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

All	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
say	O	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
glad	O	O
I	O	O
went	O	O
in	O	O
!	O	O

This	O	O
place	O	O
is	O	O
about	O	O
healing	O	O
,	O	O
not	O	O
making	O	O
a	O	O
buck	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
followup	O	O
visit	O	O
is	O	O
FREE	O	O
!!	O	O

After	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
hospital	O	O
and	O	O
paying	O	O
ER	O	O
prices	O	O
...	O	O
there	O	O
is	O	O
no	O	O
way	O	O
I	O	O
wo	O	O
n't	O	O
be	O	O
back	O	O
here	O	O
!!	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
back	O	O
and	O	O
telling	O	O
EVERYONE	O	O
about	O	O
this	O	O
clinic	O	O
.	O	O

THANK	O	O
YOU	O	O
!!	O	O

I	O	O
just	O	O
like	O	O
the	O	O
fact	O	O
that	O	O
he	O	O
was	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
the	O	O
specific	O	O
type	O	O
of	O	O
repair	O	O
I	O	O
wanted	O	O
(	O	O
a	O	O
reball	O	O
)	O	O
and	O	O
give	O	O
me	O	O
the	O	O
longest	O	O
warranty	O	O
and	O	O
even	O	O
a	O	O
lower	O	O
price	O	O
.	O	O

Someone	O	O
else	O	O
I	O	O
found	O	O
that	O	O
said	O	O
they	O	O
could	O	O
do	O	O
it	O	O
but	O	O
wanted	O	O
to	O	O
charge	O	O
me	O	O
more	O	O
and	O	O
give	O	O
me	O	O
less	O	O
warranty	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
no	O	O
brainer	O	O
really	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
choose	O	O
Console	B-ORG	O
Pros	I-ORG	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
happy	O	O
I	O	O
did	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
place	O	O
is	O	O
bad	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
dark	O	O
,	O	O
dingy	O	O
&	O	O
dirty	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
place	O	O
may	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
something	O	O
sometime	O	O
;	O	O
but	O	O
it	O	O
way	O	O
past	O	O
it	O	O
"	O	O
sell	O	O
by	O	O
date	O	O
"	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
eaten	O	O
here	O	O
twice	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
past	O	O
year	O	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
go	O	O
back	O	O
and	O	O
can	O	O
not	O	O
recommend	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Ham	B-ORG	O
s	I-ORG	O
on	O	O
Friendly	B-LOC	O
...	O	O
RIP	O	O

This	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
original	O	O
Ham	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
restaurant	O	O
,	O	O
expanded	O	O
into	O	O
a	O	O
regional	O	O
chain	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
late	O	O
80's	O	O
--	O	O
but	O	O
this	O	O
one	O	O
is	O	O
no	O	O
more	O	O
.	O	O

Victim	O	O
of	O	O
hard	O	O
times	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
suspect	O	O
failing	O	O
corporate	O	O
management	O	O
.	O	O

According	O	O
to	O	O
news	O	O
accounts	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
company	O	O
is	O	O
struggling	O	O
.	O	O

So	O	O
long	O	O
Ham	B-ORG	O
s	I-ORG	O
...	O	O
you	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
missed	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
very	O	O
pleased	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
services	O	O
of	O	O
First	B-ORG	O
Glass	I-ORG	O
Window	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

Our	O	O
window	O	O
panes	O	O
were	O	O
so	O	O
dirty	O	O
that	O	O
they	O	O
needed	O	O
a	O	O
specialist	O	O
to	O	O
come	O	O
and	O	O
clean	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
called	O	O
few	O	O
companies	O	O
before	O	O
we	O	O
decide	O	O
to	O	O
hire	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
came	O	O
on	O	O
time	O	O
and	O	O
completed	O	O
their	O	O
work	O	O
quickly	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
were	O	O
very	O	O
happy	O	O
how	O	O
clean	O	O
looked	O	O
our	O	O
windows	O	O
.	O	O

Great	O	O
help	O	O
even	O	O
near	O	O
closing	O	O
time	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
came	O	O
in	O	O
to	O	O
town	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
week	O	O
and	O	O
forgot	O	O
my	O	O
trainers	O	O
!	O	O

Oh	O	O
no	O	O
!!	O	O

I	O	O
came	O	O
in	O	O
30	O	O
min	O	O
before	O	O
close	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
staff	O	O
was	O	O
super	O	O
helpful	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
spent	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
of	O	O
time	O	O
with	O	O
me	O	O
and	O	O
got	O	O
me	O	O
into	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
pair	O	O
of	O	O
shoes	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
they	O	O
may	O	O
even	O	O
be	O	O
better	O	O
than	O	O
the	O	O
pair	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
using	O	O
this	O	O
past	O	O
year	O	O
!	O	O

Thanks	O	O
Run	B-ORG	O
on	I-ORG	O
!	O	O

Great	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
gone	O	O
there	O	O
time	O	O
and	O	O
time	O	O
again	O	O
whenever	O	O
I	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
done	O	O
or	O	O
when	O	O
I	O	O
want	O	O
a	O	O
haircut	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
I	O	O
get	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
done	O	O
there	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
use	O	O
enough	O	O
hairstyling	O	O
products	O	O
while	O	O
it	O	O
does	O	O
not	O	O
ruin	O	O
your	O	O
hair	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
service	O	O
is	O	O
great	O	O
and	O	O
during	O	O
weekends	O	O
it	O	O
tends	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
busy	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
the	O	O
wait	O	O
is	O	O
worthwhile	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
highly	O	O
recommend	O	O
her	O	O
.	O	O

Best	O	O
Store	O	O
In	O	O
Boothbay	B-LOC	O
Harbor	I-LOC	O

What	O	O
a	O	O
fantastic	O	O
store	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
love	O	O
this	O	O
place	O	O
.	O	O

Not	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
old	O	O
stuff	O	O
that	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
other	O	O
stores	O	O
have	O	O
.	O	O

Their	O	O
items	O	O
are	O	O
very	O	O
unique	O	O
,	O	O
great	O	O
quality	O	O
,	O	O
great	O	O
prices	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
also	O	O
have	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
tea	O	O
I	O	O
ever	O	O
had	O	O
,	O	O
not	O	O
at	O	O
all	O	O
like	O	O
the	O	O
junk	O	O
you	O	O
get	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
grocery	O	O
stores	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
stock	O	O
up	O	O
when	O	O
ever	O	O
there	O	O
because	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
closed	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
winter	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
BEST	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Aster	B-PER	O
and	O	O
her	O	O
team	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
a	O	O
strong	O	O
advocate	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
health	O	O
of	O	O
both	O	O
my	O	O
daughters	O	O
.	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Aster	B-PER	O
is	O	O
very	O	O
kind	O	O
an	O	O
gentle	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
children	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
also	O	O
positive	O	O
and	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
point	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
parents	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
is	O	O
and	O	O
excellent	O	O
doctor	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
on	O	O
one	O	O
's	O	O
team	O	O
.	O	O

Real	O	O
pros	O	O

I	O	O
've	O	O
had	O	O
writer	O	O
friends	O	O
describe	O	O
horror	O	O
stories	O	O
with	O	O
their	O	O
printers	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
tell	O	O
them	O	O
:	O	O
why	O	O
not	O	O
just	O	O
go	O	O
with	O	O
these	O	O
guys	O	O
?	O	O

Already	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
considering	O	O
future	O	O
projects	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
assure	O	O
you	O	O
that	O	O
for	O	O
my	O	O
printing	O	O
needs	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
choosing	O	O
no	O	O
other	O	O
than	O	O
Atlanta	B-ORG	B-LOC
Paperback	I-ORG	O
Book	I-ORG	O
Printing	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
called	O	O
them	O	O
for	O	O
an	O	O
estimate	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
INSULTED	O	O
ME	O	O
WHEN	O	O
I	O	O
ASK	O	O
THEM	O	O
QUESTIONS	O	O
.	O	O

THEY	O	O
ARE	O	O
VERY	O	O
RUDE	O	O
AND	O	O
NASTY	O	O
.	O	O

PLEASE	O	O
DO	O	O
N'T	O	O
USE	O	O
THIS	O	O
MOVING	O	O
COMPANY	O	O
IF	O	O
YOU	O	O
DO	O	O
N'T	O	O
WANT	O	O
TO	O	O
:	O	O
CRY	O	O
,	O	O
HAVE	O	O
TROUBLE	O	O
AND	O	O
A	O	O
BAD	O	O
EXPERIENCE	O	O
ON	O	O
THE	O	O
DAY	O	O
OF	O	O
YOUR	O	O
MOVE	O	O
.	O	O

THEY	O	O
WILL	O	O
GIVE	O	O
YOU	O	O
A	O	O
LOW	O	O
PRICE	O	O
OVER	O	O
THE	O	O
PHONE	O	O
AND	O	O
ON	O	O
THE	O	O
DAY	O	O
OF	O	O
YOUR	O	O
MOVE	O	O
THEY	O	O
WILL	O	O
CHANGE	O	O
THE	O	O
PRICE	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
GUARANTEE	O	O
IT	O	O
.	O	O

You	B-ORG	O
've	I-ORG	O
Got	I-ORG	O
Maids	I-ORG	O
did	O	O
a	O	O
fabulous	O	O
job	O	O
cleaning	O	O
my	O	O
home	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
hiring	O	O
them	O	O
to	O	O
come	O	O
once	O	O
a	O	O
week	O	O
now	O	O
that	O	O
they	O	O
got	O	O
my	O	O
house	O	O
to	O	O
where	O	O
they	O	O
can	O	O
maintain	O	O
it	O	O
for	O	O
only	O	O
an	O	O
hour	O	O
and	O	O
a	O	O
half	O	O
every	O	O
two	O	O
weeks	O	O
!	O	O

Satisfactory	O	O
for	O	O
sure	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
sercvice	O	O
!	O	O

Beats	O	O
having	O	O
one	O	O
"	O	O
cleaning	O	O
lady	O	O
"	O	O
who	O	O
took	O	O
twice	O	O
as	O	O
long	O	O
and	O	O
did	O	O
not	O	O
do	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
through	O	O
job	O	O
like	O	O
the	O	O
"	O	O
maids	O	O
"	O	O
did	O	O
!	O	O

This	O	O
place	O	O
has	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
baby	O	O
and	O	O
children	O	O
s	O	O
clothes	O	O
.	O	O

Especially	O	O
high	O	O
end	O	O
keep	O	O
sake	O	O
sort	O	O
of	O	O
clothing	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
just	O	O
ca	O	O
nt	O	O
find	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
of	O	O
stores	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
all	O	O
very	O	O
unique	O	O
and	O	O
you	O	O
wo	O	O
nt	O	O
find	O	O
any	O	O
other	O	O
baby	O	O
wearing	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
stuff	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
spent	O	O
quite	O	O
a	O	O
bit	O	O
because	O	O
I	O	O
spoil	O	O
my	O	O
little	O	O
princess	O	O
.	O	O

Antique	O	O
Lighting	O	O
,	O	O
Fixtures	O	O
,	O	O
Chicago	B-LOC	O

Great	O	O
place	O	O
for	O	O
Antique	O	O
Lighting	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
visited	O	O
their	O	O
huge	O	O
Chicago	B-LOC	O
lighting	O	O
showroom	O	O
and	O	O
all	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
say	O	O
is	O	O
WOW	O	O
!!	O	O

Lots	O	O
of	O	O
collections	O	O
,	O	O
many	O	O
antique	O	O
light	O	O
fixtures	O	O
,	O	O
Chandeliers	O	O
,	O	O
custom	O	O
lighting	O	O
etc	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
think	O	O
they	O	O
have	O	O
the	O	O
largest	O	O
collection	O	O
for	O	O
Chandeliers	O	O
Chicago	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

Antiques	O	O
,	O	O
Vintage	O	O
,	O	O
Contemporary	O	O
&	O	O
Modern	O	O
Chandeliers	O	O
.	O	O

DO	O	O
NOT	O	O
GO	O	O
HERE	O	O
!!!	O	O

I	O	O
went	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
my	O	O
nails	O	O
filled	O	O
Friday	O	O
,	O	O
by	O	O
Monday	O	O
2	O	O
were	O	O
broken	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
not	O	O
happy	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
way	O	O
they	O	O
looked	O	O
,	O	O
very	O	O
wavy	O	O
,	O	O
uneven	O	O
edges	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
exception	O	O
of	O	O
1	O	O
,	O	O
there	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
dip	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
center	O	O
of	O	O
each	O	O
nail	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
also	O	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
pedicure	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
cut	O	O
my	O	O
nails	O	O
too	O	O
short	O	O
,	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
big	O	O
toes	O	O
looks	O	O
like	O	O
it	O	O
s	O	O
getting	O	O
infected	O	O
.	O	O

No	O	O
way	O	O
.	O	O

Cold	O	O
,	O	O
slimy	O	O
,	O	O
tasteless	O	O
however	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
in	O	O
all	O	O
languages	O	O
and	O	O
foods	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
do	O	O
these	O	O
places	O	O
stay	O	O
in	O	O
business	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
town	O	O
needs	O	O
some	O	O
food	O	O
soul	O	O
and	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Worth	O	O
Every	O	O
Penny	O	O

My	O	O
girlfriend	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
ate	O	O
at	O	O
The	O	O
Grill	B-ORG	O
last	O	O
night	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
our	O	O
experience	O	O
was	O	O
amazing	O	O
.	O	O

Everything	O	O
we	O	O
ordered	O	O
was	O	O
prepared	O	O
to	O	O
perfection	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
was	O	O
presented	O	O
perfectly	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
asparagus	O	O
,	O	O
seared	O	O
tuna	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
lobster	O	O
tail	O	O
were	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
we	O	O
ever	O	O
had	O	O
.	O	O

Then	O	O
the	O	O
desserts	O	O
came	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
were	O	O
hands	O	O
down	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
dessert	O	O
we	O	O
ever	O	O
had	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
sum	O	O
it	O	O
up	O	O
with	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
was	O	O
worth	O	O
every	O	O
penny	O	O
!	O	O

BEST	O	O
CHINESE	B-LOCderiv	O
RESTAURANT	O	O
EVER	O	O
!!!	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
Chinese	B-LOCderiv	O
food	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
ever	O	O
had	O	O
.	O	O

All	O	O
the	O	O
food	O	O
tasted	O	O
excellent	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
new	O	O
renovation	O	O
of	O	O
chairs	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
bathroom	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
awesome	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
people	O	O
working	O	O
their	O	O
are	O	O
also	O	O
extremely	O	O
polite	O	O
and	O	O
friendly	O	O
.	O	O

Every	O	O
time	O	O
I	O	O
go	O	O
,	O	O
Kevin	B-PER	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
manager	O	O
,	O	O
will	O	O
always	O	O
remember	O	O
my	O	O
family	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
family	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
thank	O	O
you	O	O
!!!!!!!!!!	O	O

Professional	O	O
and	O	O
inspiring	O	O

Nigel	B-PER	O
from	O	O
Nidd	B-ORG	O
Design	I-ORG	O
has	O	O
always	O	O
provided	O	O
a	O	O
first	O	O
class	O	O
service	O	O
,	O	O
from	O	O
his	O	O
advice	O	O
and	O	O
professionalism	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
quality	O	O
of	O	O
his	O	O
design	O	O
drawings	O	O
and	O	O
planning	O	O
applications	O	O
.	O	O

His	O	O
knowledge	O	O
and	O	O
expertise	O	O
help	O	O
smooth	O	O
the	O	O
way	O	O
with	O	O
any	O	O
planning	O	O
application	O	O
,	O	O
ensuring	O	O
compliance	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
building	O	O
regulations	O	O
.	O	O

Once	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
met	O	O
Nigel	B-PER	O
you	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
work	O	O
with	O	O
anyone	O	O
else	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
really	O	O
does	O	O
turn	O	O
your	O	O
dreams	O	O
into	O	O
reality	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
home	O	O
!	O	O

Got	O	O
the	O	O
crab	O	O
rangoon	O	O
which	O	O
was	O	O
great	O	O
,	O	O
tofu	O	O
with	O	O
cabbage	O	O
which	O	O
was	O	O
spicy	O	O
but	O	O
good	O	O
and	O	O
shrimp	O	O
satay	O	O
which	O	O
was	O	O
also	O	O
good	O	O
.	O	O

Def	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
come	O	O
back	O	O
and	O	O
try	O	O
this	O	O
place	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

Bea	B-PER	O
was	O	O
really	O	O
nice	O	O
and	O	O
asked	O	O
how	O	O
the	O	O
food	O	O
was	O	O
.	O	O

Cute	O	O
place	O	O
also	O	O

However	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
still	O	O
like	O	O
this	O	O
place	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
.	O	O

Esp.	O	O
the	O	O
mole	O	O
,	O	O
tortilla	O	O
soup	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
guacamole	O	O
.	O	O

Margaritas	O	O
are	O	O
alright	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
only	O	O
complaint	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
QUESO	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
used	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
fabulous	O	O
,	O	O
why	O	O
did	O	O
you	O	O
guys	O	O
change	O	O
it	O	O
??	O	O

Queso	O	O
should	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
watery	O	O
:(	O	O
.....	O	O

***	O	O
update	O	O
***	O	O
NEVER	O	O
MIND	O	O
!	O	O

They	O	O
fixed	O	O
the	O	O
queso	O	O
!	O	O

Thank	O	O
you	O	O
thank	O	O
you	O	O

I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
recommend	O	O
this	O	O
place	O	O
.	O	O

Skylight	O	O
repair	O	O

My	O	O
skylight	O	O
was	O	O
making	O	O
a	O	O
horrible	O	O
noise	O	O
when	O	O
the	O	O
wind	O	O
blew	O	O
.	O	O

James	B-PER	O
Bateman	I-PER	O
came	O	O
the	O	O
day	O	O
I	O	O
called	O	O
and	O	O
fixed	O	O
the	O	O
problem	O	O
quickly	O	O
and	O	O
efficiently	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
also	O	O
inspected	O	O
my	O	O
entie	O	O
roof	O	O
to	O	O
see	O	O
if	O	O
there	O	O
was	O	O
anything	O	O
else	O	O
that	O	O
needed	O	O
attention	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
called	O	O
the	O	O
next	O	O
day	O	O
to	O	O
see	O	O
if	O	O
everything	O	O
was	O	O
to	O	O
my	O	O
satisfaction	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
the	O	O
next	O	O
hailstorm	O	O
blows	O	O
through	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
will	O	O
not	O	O
hesitate	O	O
to	O	O
contact	O	O
James	B-PER	O
at	O	O
Team	B-ORG	O
Texas	I-ORG	B-LOC
Construction	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

tricky	O	O
short	O	O
guy	O	O

The	O	O
new	O	O
management	O	O
is	O	O
tricky	O	O
and	O	O
talk	O	O
you	O	O
into	O	O
getting	O	O
video	O	O
rental	O	O
agreement	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
did	O	O
it	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
..	O	O
no	O	O
more	O	O
Raina	B-ORG	B-PER
's	I-ORG	I-PER
.	O	O

Besides	O	O
parking	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
pain	O	O
..	O	O
cramped	O	O
and	O	O
un-ruly	O	O
with	O	O
Kumon	B-ORG	O
Parents	O	O
next	O	O
door	O	O
....	O	O
gives	O	O
me	O	O
heebee	O	O
gee	O	O
bees'	O	O

Small	O	O
Firm	O	O
with	O	O
Great	O	O
Service	O	O

I	O	O
much	O	O
preferred	O	O
the	O	O
one	O	O
-	O	O
on	O	O
-	O	O
one	O	O
service	O	O
here	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
experiences	O	O
I	O	O
've	O	O
had	O	O
with	O	O
bigger	O	O
offices	O	O
and	O	O
firms	O	O
.	O	O

While	O	O
I	O	O
hope	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
have	O	O
any	O	O
need	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
lawyer	O	O
anytime	O	O
soon	O	O
,	O	O
if	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
I	O	O
'll	O	O
definitely	O	O
use	O	O
this	O	O
firm	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

Used	O	O
their	O	O
service	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
first	O	O
time	O	O
and	O	O
was	O	O
immediately	O	O
impressed	O	O
by	O	O
their	O	O
professionalism	O	O
(	O	O
received	O	O
a	O	O
phone	O	O
call	O	O
soon	O	O
after	O	O
order	O	O
was	O	O
placed	O	O
to	O	O
confirm	O	O
details	O	O
)	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
subsequent	O	O
delivery	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
gift	O	O
(	O	O
To	O	O
Split	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
Croatia	B-LOC	O
)	O	O
was	O	O
as	O	O
requested	O	O
.	O	O

Danny	B-PER	O
(	O	O
Australia	B-LOC	O
)	O	O

I	O	O
LOVE	O	O
MY	O	O
GYM	O	O
!	O	O

FITNESS	B-ORG	O
UNLIMITED	I-ORG	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
second	O	O
home	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
gym	O	O
members	O	O
who	O	O
work	O	O
out	O	O
daily	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
serious	O	O
about	O	O
working	O	O
out	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
non-commercial	O	O
like	O	O
atmosphere	O	O
then	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
chosen	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
place	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
.	O	O

Secondly	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
enchladas	O	O
did	O	O
not	O	O
come	O	O
with	O	O
enchilada	O	O
sauce	O	O
..	O	O
but	O	O
chili	O	O
...	O	O
like	O	O
Hormel	B-ORG	B-PER
's	I-ORG	I-PER
chili	O	O
..	O	O
the	O	O
cheese	O	O
was	O	O
American	B-LOCderiv	O
cheese	O	O
!	O	O

The	O	O
Chili	O	O
Relleno	O	O
..	O	O
had	O	O
no	O	O
batter	O	O
on	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
very	O	O
happy	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
customer	O	O
service	O	O
and	O	O
even	O	O
more	O	O
please	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
portion	O	O
size	O	O
,	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
box	O	O
set	O	O
up	O	O
and	O	O
quality	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
food	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
very	O	O
happy	O	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
definitely	O	O
dine	O	O
in	O	O
and	O	O
carry	O	O
out	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
pizza	O	O
is	O	O
usually	O	O
pretty	O	O
good	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
only	O	O
bad	O	O
one	O	O
we	O	O
got	O	O
was	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
Friday	O	O
night	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
just	O	O
needed	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
cooked	O	O
a	O	O
little	O	O
more	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
it	O	O
was	O	O
still	O	O
good	O	O
.	O	O

Their	O	O
BBQ	O	O
chicken	O	O
pizza	O	O
is	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
better	O	O
ones	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
ever	O	O
had	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
very	O	O
rude	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
phone	O	O
and	O	O
in	O	O
person	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
NEVER	O	O
do	O	O
business	O	O
with	O	O
Sun	B-ORG	O
Toyota	I-ORG	B-ORG
again	O	O
.	O	O

this	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
good	O	O
place	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
here	O	O
before	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
service	O	O
was	O	O
absoulutely	O	O
great	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
great	O	O
selection	O	O
of	O	O
colors	O	O
to	O	O
choose	O	O
from	O	O
and	O	O
their	O	O
seats	O	O
are	O	O
super	O	O
comfty	O	O
.	O	O

Give	O	O
yourself	O	O
the	O	O
gift	O	O
of	O	O
trying	O	O
this	O	O
place	O	O
,	O	O
to	O	O
see	O	O
if	O	O
it	O	O
fits	O	O
you	O	O
...	O	O

Went	O	O
there	O	O
yesterday	O	O
:	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
decide	O	O
between	O	O
two	O	O
different	O	O
Honda	B-ORG	O
models	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
we	O	O
wanted	O	O
to	O	O
test	O	O
-	O	O
drive	O	O
both	O	O
back	O	O
to	O	O
back	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
salesperson	O	O
refused	O	O
!	O	O

Claimed	O	O
he	O	O
was	O	O
too	O	O
busy	O	O
for	O	O
two	O	O
test	O	O
drives	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
were	O	O
the	O	O
only	O	O
customers	O	O
there	O	O
!	O	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
waste	O	O
time	O	O
,	O	O
just	O	O
drive	O	O
10	O	O
minutes	O	O
more	O	O
down	O	O
to	O	O
Stevens	B-LOC	B-PER
Creek	I-LOC	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
actually	O	O
do	O	O
try	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
their	O	O
customers	O	O
there	O	O
!	O	O

ATE	O	O
HERE	O	O
A	O	O
COUPLE	O	O
TIMES	O	O
.	O	O

IT	O	O
IS	O	O
NOT	O	O
A	O	O
HIGH	O	O
END	O	O
STEAK	O	O
HOUSE	O	O
,	O	O
MORE	O	O
OF	O	O
THE	O	O
CUISINE	O	O
BRETT	B-PER	O
ENJOYS	O	O
IN	O	O
MISSISSIPPI	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

SO	O	O
,	O	O
IF	O	O
YOU	O	O
WANT	O	O
A	O	O
BURGER	O	O
AND	O	O
FRIES	O	O
,	O	O
WELL	O	O
,	O	O
IT	O	O
IS	O	O
OK	O	O
.	O	O

IF	O	O
YOU	O	O
WANT	O	O
A	O	O
LITTLE	O	O
CAJUNISH	B-MISCderiv	O
FOOD	O	O
-	O	O
IT	O	O
IS	O	O
GOOD	O	O
.	O	O

Eulogic	B-ORG	O

Good	O	O
place	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
Sunday	O	O
Night	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
beers	O	O
were	O	O
good	O	O
,	O	O
nice	O	O
choice	O	O
of	O	O
beers	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
as	O	O
usual	O	O
the	O	O
mussels	O	O
were	O	O
great	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
place	O	O
upstairs	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
nice	O	O
addition	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
bar	O	O
downstairs	O	O
.	O	O

Filled	O	O
up	O	O
on	O	O
too	O	O
much	O	O
beer	O	O
and	O	O
hence	O	O
can	O	O
not	O	O
comment	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
food	O	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
the	O	O
menu	O	O
had	O	O
standard	O	O
stuff	O	O
that	O	O
one	O	O
would	O	O
get	O	O
at	O	O
a	O	O
Belgian	B-ORG	B-LOCderiv
Tavern	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
a	O	O
handcraft	O	O
beer	O	O
person	O	O
,	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
fantastic	O	O
place	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
.	O	O

Perfect	O	O
Location	O	O
plus	O	O

I	O	O
moved	O	O
into	O	O
the	O	O
Tanglewood	B-ORG	O
Apartments	I-ORG	O
in	O	O
late	O	O
2008	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
's	O	O
been	O	O
a	O	O
refreshing	O	O
change	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
used	O	O
to	O	O
live	O	O
at	O	O
Meadowrun	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
that	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
nightmare	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
manager	O	O
-	O	O
Tiffany	B-PER	O
-	O	O
is	O	O
actually	O	O
very	O	O
nice	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
'm	O	O
a	O	O
bit	O	O
surprised	O	O
by	O	O
other	O	O
comments	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
's	O	O
very	O	O
reachable	O	O
and	O	O
she	O	O
has	O	O
always	O	O
responded	O	O
quickly	O	O
to	O	O
any	O	O
questions	O	O
or	O	O
requests	O	O
.	O	O

One	O	O
guy	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
little	O	O
surley	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
who	O	O
gives	O	O
a	O	O
crap	O	O
as	O	O
long	O	O
as	O	O
your	O	O
car	O	O
's	O	O
work	O	O
is	O	O
outstanding	O	O
.	O	O

Overall	O	O
-	O	O
good	O	O
stuff	O	O
.	O	O

Another	O	O
great	O	O
business	O	O
bites	O	O
the	O	O
dust	O	O
!	O	O

The	O	O
best	O	O
cakes	O	O
EVER	O	O
!	O	O

A	O	O
bit	O	O
pricey	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
go	O	O
very	O	O
often	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
it	O	O
was	O	O
always	O	O
a	O	O
treat	O	O
when	O	O
I	O	O
did	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
prices	O	O
were	O	O
worth	O	O
what	O	O
I	O	O
got	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
assuming	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
completely	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
business	O	O
since	O	O
I	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
find	O	O
any	O	O
contact	O	O
information	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
hoping	O	O
the	O	O
bakers	O	O
continue	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
their	O	O
baking	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
another	O	O
place	O	O
,	O	O
because	O	O
it	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
shame	O	O
not	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
these	O	O
cakes	O	O
any	O	O
longer	O	O
.	O	O

Super	O	O
nice	O	O
people	O	O
,	O	O
really	O	O
good	O	O
food	O	O

What	O	O
I	O	O
love	O	O
most	O	O
about	O	O
this	O	O
place	O	O
,	O	O
other	O	O
than	O	O
the	O	O
food	O	O
,	O	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
eating	O	O
here	O	O
makes	O	O
you	O	O
feel	O	O
like	O	O
you	O	O
're	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
small	O	O
town	O	O
rather	O	O
than	O	O
Baltimore	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
owners	O	O
are	O	O
really	O	O
nice	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
serve	O	O
good	O	O
food	O	O
at	O	O
a	O	O
good	O	O
price	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
option	O	O
to	O	O
eat	O	O
outside	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
deck	O	O
(	O	O
esp	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
weekend	O	O
whether	O	O
there	O	O
is	O	O
hardly	O	O
any	O	O
traffic	O	O
)	O	O
is	O	O
great	O	O
.	O	O

One	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
top	O	O
5	O	O
places	O	O
to	O	O
eat	O	O
in	O	O
Baltimore	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

Overpriced	O	O

This	O	O
place	O	O
is	O	O
identical	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
Youngstown	B-ORG	B-LOC
Sports	I-ORG	O
Grille	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
imagine	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
owned	O	O
/	O	O
operated	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
people	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
food	O	O
is	O	O
mediocre	O	O
at	O	O
best	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
largely	O	O
overpriced	O	O
given	O	O
the	O	O
portion	O	O
size	O	O
and	O	O
quality	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
even	O	O
get	O	O
me	O	O
started	O	O
on	O	O
how	O	O
expensive	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
to	O	O
drink	O	O
there	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
ate	O	O
here	O	O
3	O	O
times	O	O
since	O	O
they	O	O
first	O	O
opened	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
service	O	O
has	O	O
been	O	O
poor	O	O
each	O	O
time	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
staff	O	O
always	O	O
comes	O	O
across	O	O
as	O	O
somewhat	O	O
rude	O	O
and	O	O
slow	O	O
.	O	O

Apps	O	O
4	O	O
Salad	O	O
3	O	O
Entree	O	O
3.5	O	O
Wine	O	O
5	O	O
(	O	O
NOV	O	O
07	O	O
)	O	O

Enjoyed	O	O
this	O	O
cozy	O	O
little	O	O
spot	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
group	O	O
of	O	O
8	O	O
folks	O	O
.	O	O

Service	O	O
was	O	O
excellent	O	O
.	O	O

Food	O	O
was	O	O
excellent	O	O
.	O	O

Wine	O	O
was	O	O
excellent	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
feeling	O	O
the	O	O
need	O	O
for	O	O
some	O	O
fish	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
had	O	O
the	O	O
salmon	O	O
which	O	O
was	O	O
very	O	O
good	O	O
but	O	O
the	O	O
steaks	O	O
looked	O	O
amazing	O	O
and	O	O
if	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
in	O	O
town	O	O
again	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
'll	O	O
definitely	O	O
order	O	O
a	O	O
steak	O	O
.	O	O

A	O	O
perfect	O	O
place	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
romantic	O	O
dinner	O	O
.	O	O

Lots	O	O
of	O	O
"	O	O
pretty	O	O
people	O	O
"	O	O
dining	O	O
inside	O	O
.	O	O

Great	O	O
experience	O	O
-	O	O
consider	O	O
checking	O	O
out	O	O
their	O	O
puppies	O	O
before	O	O
buying	O	O
from	O	O
a	O	O
breeder	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
adopted	O	O
a	O	O
3.5	O	O
month	O	O
old	O	O
yellow	O	O
lab	O	O
last	O	O
winter	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
Dumb	B-ORG	O
Friends	I-ORG	O
League	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
staff	O	O
was	O	O
very	O	O
helpful	O	O
in	O	O
finding	O	O
the	O	O
right	O	O
dog	O	O
for	O	O
me	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
care	O	O
my	O	O
pup	O	O
received	O	O
was	O	O
outstanding	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
pup	O	O
has	O	O
a	O	O
wonderful	O	O
temperment	O	O
and	O	O
has	O	O
been	O	O
a	O	O
wonderful	O	O
addition	O	O
to	O	O
my	O	O
family	O	O
!	O	O

Food	O	O
good	O	O
,	O	O
service	O	O
poor	O	O

Had	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
the	O	O
the	O	O
bus	O	O
boy	O	O
s	O	O
station	O	O
ourselves	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
napkins	O	O
.	O	O

Con	O	O
Garage	O	O

I	O	O
brought	O	O
my	O	O
car	O	O
in	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
simple	O	O
emissions	O	O
test	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
guess	O	O
they	O	O
figured	O	O
me	O	O
for	O	O
an	O	O
easy	O	O
mark	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
tried	O	O
to	O	O
explain	O	O
that	O	O
my	O	O
car	O	O
would	O	O
n't	O	O
pass	O	O
unless	O	O
I	O	O
replaced	O	O
a	O	O
hose	O	O
.	O	O

Ten	O	O
minutes	O	O
later	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
took	O	O
my	O	O
car	O	O
down	O	O
the	O	O
street	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
passed	O	O
the	O	O
emissions	O	O
test	O	O
with	O	O
flying	O	O
colors	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
're	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
herpes	O	O
,	O	O
being	O	O
ripped	O	O
off	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
child	O	O
molesters	O	O
,	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
garage	O	O
for	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
not	O	O
,	O	O
go	O	O
somewhere	O	O
else	O	O
.	O	O

Rude	O	O
service	O	O

even	O	O
though	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
never	O	O
tried	O	O
hoa	B-ORG	O
salon	I-ORG	O
but	O	O
I	O	O
agree	O	O
with	O	O
other	O	O
reviewers	O	O
that	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
rude	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
told	O	O
us	O	O
to	O	O
stop	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
salon	O	O
and	O	O
then	O	O
he	O	O
will	O	O
tell	O	O
us	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
kind	O	O
of	O	O
rude	O	O
service	O	O
is	O	O
that	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
waste	O	O
my	O	O
time	O	O
with	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O

Top	O	O
notch	O	O
eats	O	O
!	O	O

So	O	O
here	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
in	O	O
Manson	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

Manson	B-LOC	O
?	O	O

Yes	O	O
,	O	O
Manson	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

Right	O	O
near	O	O
Chelan	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

Aka	O	O
Nowheresville	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
this	O	O
litttle	O	O
gem	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
7	O	O
-	O	O
table	O	O
restaurant	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
complete	O	O
and	O	O
utterly	O	O
wonderful	O	O
surprise	O	O
.	O	O

A	O	O
short	O	O
but	O	O
wide	O	O
-	O	O
ranging	O	O
menu	O	O
executed	O	O
with	O	O
innovative	O	O
perfection	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
cozy	O	O
hole	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
wall	O	O
just	O	O
off	O	O
the	O	O
main	O	O
street	O	O
.	O	O

A	O	O
great	O	O
place	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
for	O	O
dinner	O	O
after	O	O
a	O	O
day	O	O
of	O	O
wine	O	O
tasting	O	O
.	O	O

Boutique	O	O
stores	O	O
dealing	O	O
in	O	O
children	O	O
's	O	O
clothing	O	O
/	O	O
gifts	O	O
are	O	O
often	O	O
outrageously	O	O
priced	O	O
(	O	O
who	O	O
wants	O	O
to	O	O
pay	O	O
40	O	O
dollars	B-MISC	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
newborn	O	O
onesie	O	O
?	O	O
)	O	O

but	O	O
I	O	O
was	O	O
pleasantly	O	O
surprised	O	O
to	O	O
find	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
Purple	B-ORG	O
Goose	I-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
prices	O	O
are	O	O
reasonable	O	O
(	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
SAME	O	O
products	O	O
found	O	O
at	O	O
other	O	O
area	O	O
boutiques	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
prices	O	O
were	O	O
20	O	O
-	O	O
25	O	O
%	O	O
cheaper	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
service	O	O
was	O	O
also	O	O
excellent	O	O
-	O	O
friendly	O	O
,	O	O
helpful	O	O
and	O	O
informative	O	O
without	O	O
being	O	O
overbearing	O	O
.	O	O

Will	O	O
definitely	O	O
return	O	O
.	O	O

Consistantly	O	O
poor	O	O

A	O	O
lack	O	O
of	O	O
organisation	O	O
,	O	O
coupled	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
distain	O	O
for	O	O
its	O	O
customers	O	O
,	O	O
makes	O	O
this	O	O
the	O	O
worst	O	O
rental	O	O
agency	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
used	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
must	O	O
use	O	O
them	O	O
,	O	O
be	O	O
vigilant	O	O
and	O	O
be	O	O
ready	O	O
to	O	O
push	O	O
,	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
can	O	O
go	O	O
elsewhere	O	O
then	O	O
I	O	O
would	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
s	O	O
been	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
years	O	O
since	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
to	O	O
Ipanema	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
my	O	O
wife	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
first	O	O
went	O	O
there	O	O
thinking	O	O
it	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
Brazilian	B-LOCderiv	O
food	O	O
(	O	O
think	O	O
lots	O	O
of	O	O
meat	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
it	O	O
turned	O	O
out	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
vegan	O	O
restaurant	O	O
!	O	O

And	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
say	O	O
,	O	O
this	O	O
was	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
favorite	O	O
places	O	O
to	O	O
eat	O	O
in	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
Richmond	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

Amazing	O	O
!	O	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
let	O	O
the	O	O
nondescript	O	O
building	O	O
entrance	O	O
fool	O	O
you	O	O
,	O	O
these	O	O
are	O	O
some	O	O
creative	O	O
and	O	O
talented	O	O
chefs	O	O
...	O	O
two	O	O
thumbs	O	O
way	O	O
,	O	O
way	O	O
up	O	O
!	O	O

FANTASTIC	O	O
STORE	O	O
!!!	O	O

I	O	O
came	O	O
upon	O	O
this	O	O
store	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
building	O	O
caught	O	O
my	O	O
eye	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
located	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
huge	O	O
HONKA	B-ORG	O
Log	I-ORG	O
Homes	I-ORG	O
building	O	O
,	O	O
by	O	O
Walmart	B-ORG	O
off	O	O
of	O	O
Evergreen	B-LOC	O
Parkway	I-LOC	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
store	O	O
was	O	O
decorated	O	O
with	O	O
furnishings	O	O
&	O	O
accessories	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
friendly	O	O
crew	O	O
working	O	O
was	O	O
great	O	O
&	O	O
very	O	O
helpful	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
store	O	O
is	O	O
what	O	O
Colorado	B-LOC	O
is	O	O
all	O	O
about	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
purchased	O	O
some	O	O
furniture	O	O
last	O	O
year	O	O
and	O	O
all	O	O
has	O	O
been	O	O
great	O	O
!	O	O

Lovely	O	O
People	O	O
,	O	O
Great	O	O
Hats	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
saddened	O	O
to	O	O
see	O	O
the	O	O
reviews	O	O
that	O	O
claimed	O	O
World	B-ORG	O
Hats	I-ORG	O
Mart	I-ORG	O
has	O	O
poor	O	O
service	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
led	O	O
me	O	O
to	O	O
believe	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
reviewers	O	O
simply	O	O
had	O	O
difficulty	O	O
tolerating	O	O
people	O	O
with	O	O
strongly	O	O
-	O	O
accented	O	O
English	B-LOCderiv	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
have	O	O
had	O	O
many	O	O
conversations	O	O
with	O	O
them	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
have	O	O
always	O	O
been	O	O
extremely	O	O
patient	O	O
with	O	O
me	O	O
as	O	O
I	O	O
tried	O	O
on	O	O
multiple	O	O
hats	O	O
in	O	O
search	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
right	O	O
costumes	O	O
for	O	O
my	O	O
magic	O	O
act	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
recommend	O	O
them	O	O
highly	O	O
!	O	O

DO	O	O
NT	O	O
ever	O	O
go	O	O
there	O	O
,	O	O
not	O	O
even	O	O
if	O	O
your	O	O
car	O	O
flips	O	O
.	O	O

Their	O	O
service	O	O
sucks	O	O
to	O	O
start	O	O
off	O	O
with	O	O
,	O	O
people	O	O
are	O	O
cruel	O	O
and	O	O
ignorant	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
compeltly	O	O
dissatisfied	O	O
with	O	O
their	O	O
service	O	O
and	O	O
their	O	O
products	O	O
.	O	O

DO	O	O
NOT	O	O
EVER	O	O
GO	O	O
HERE	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
prefer	O	O
Advanced	O	O
auto	O	O
parts	O	O
over	O	O
this	O	O
crappy	O	O
place	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
meanest	O	O
people	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
they	O	O
THRIVE	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
.	O	O

DO	O	O
NOT	O	O
go	O	O
here	O	O
..	O	O
thank	O	O
you	O	O

Horrible	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
growing	O	O
my	O	O
hair	O	O
out	O	O
for	O	O
1	O	O
year	O	O
plus	O	O
and	O	O
went	O	O
in	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
1	O	O
inch	O	O
taken	O	O
off	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
walked	O	O
out	O	O
with	O	O
5	O	O
inch	O	O
long	O	O
hair	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
top	O	O
,	O	O
2	O	O
inch	O	O
long	O	O
hair	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
sides	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
1.5	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
back	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
hair	O	O
is	O	O
uneven	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
looks	O	O
rediculous	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
woman	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
working	O	O
in	O	O
supercuts	O	O
...	O	O
if	O	O
that	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
terrible	O	O
experience	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
hope	O	O
that	O	O
no	O	O
one	O	O
else	O	O
goes	O	O
through	O	O
that	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
your	O	O
self	O	O
a	O	O
favor	O	O
and	O	O
do	O	O
not	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
this	O	O
establishment	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
worst	O	O
Burger	B-ORG	O
King	I-ORG	O
restaurant	O	O
!!!	O	O

I	O	O
generally	O	O
like	O	O
the	O	O
BK	B-ORG	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
other	O	O
fast	O	O
serving	O	O
restaurants	O	O
;	O	O
however	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
regreted	O	O
to	O	O
visit	O	O
this	O	O
restaurant	O	O
at	O	O
my	O	O
town	O	O
.	O	O

HORRIBLE	O	O
!!!!	O	O
!	O	O

This	O	O
has	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
some	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
worst	O	O
pizza	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
ever	O	O
had	O	O
the	O	O
misfortune	O	O
of	O	O
ordering	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
crust	O	O
was	O	O
lopsided	O	O
,	O	O
thicker	O	O
on	O	O
one	O	O
side	O	O
than	O	O
the	O	O
other	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
actually	O	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
hole	O	O
in	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
slices	O	O
.	O	O

best	O	O
quote	O	O
ever	O	O
My	O	O
gate	O	O
was	O	O
stuck	O	O
halfway	O	O
open	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
called	O	O
A	B-ORG	O
CLASS	I-ORG	O
Garage	I-ORG	O
Doors	I-ORG	O
Dr	I-ORG	O
Services	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
came	O	O
to	O	O
my	O	O
house	O	O
in	O	O
no	O	O
time	O	O
and	O	O
started	O	O
working	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
gate	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
were	O	O
very	O	O
friendly	O	O
and	O	O
were	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
explain	O	O
me	O	O
exactly	O	O
what	O	O
was	O	O
wrong	O	O
with	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Once	O	O
they	O	O
fixed	O	O
it	O	O
they	O	O
answetred	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
questions	O	O
with	O	O
no	O	O
hesitations	O	O
and	O	O
then	O	O
gave	O	O
me	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
quote	O	O
ever	O	O
.	O	O
