the	O	O
industry	O	O
of	O	O
Marriage	O	O
and	O	O
Kids	O	O
,	O	O
you	O	O
heard	O	O
me	O	O
.	O	O

Marriage	O	O
is	O	O
,	O	O
in	O	O
and	O	O
of	O	O
itself	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
noble	O	O
concept	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
it	O	O
too	O	O
often	O	O
leads	O	O
to	O	O
kids	O	O
and	O	O
kids	O	O
flat	O	O
out	O	O
suck	O	O
.	O	O

How	O	O
can	O	O
I	O	O
say	O	O
such	O	O
an	O	O
abomination	O	O
,	O	O
ask	O	O
you	O	O
?	O	O

Look	O	O
around	O	O
you	O	O
and	O	O
notice	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
mind	O	O
numbing	O	O
trailor	O	O
trash	O	O
cretins	O	O
out	O	O
there	O	O
who	O	O
should	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
procreating	O	O
,	O	O
yet	O	O
they	O	O
do	O	O
.	O	O

These	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
people	O	O
who	O	O
keep	O	O
Jerry	B-PER	O
springer	I-PER	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
air	O	O
.	O	O

These	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
kids	O	O
who	O	O
will	O	O
destroy	O	O
society	O	O
,	O	O
because	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
crapfest	O	O
the	O	O
American	B-LOCderiv	O
family	O	O
has	O	O
become	O	O
under	O	O
the	O	O
post	O	O
hippie	O	O
culture	O	O
,	O	O
you	O	O
heard	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
you	O	O
might	O	O
think	O	O
by	O	O
reading	O	O
this	O	O
I	O	O
blame	O	O
the	O	O
kids	O	O
.....	O	O

Not	O	O
so	O	O
,	O	O
Kids	O	O
are	O	O
what	O	O
kids	O	O
are	O	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
do	O	O
what	O	O
they	O	O
do	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
literally	O	O
monkey	O	O
see	O	O
and	O	O
monkey	O	O
do	O	O
with	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
will	O	O
likely	O	O
never	O	O
change	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
the	O	O
bad	O	O
parents	O	O
out	O	O
there	O	O
who	O	O
fuck	O	O
up	O	O
their	O	O
lives	O	O
and	O	O
do	O	O
nt	O	O
seem	O	O
to	O	O
understand	O	O
that	O	O
once	O	O
you	O	O
decide	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
kids	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
indeed	O	O
time	O	O
to	O	O
grow	O	O
up	O	O
and	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
responsible	O	O
role	O	O
model	O	O
for	O	O
those	O	O
kids	O	O
.	O	O

Very	O	O
few	O	O
parents	O	O
do	O	O
this	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
direct	O	O
result	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Politically	O	O
correct	O	O
,	O	O
permissive	O	O
,	O	O
time	O	O
out	O	O
granting	O	O
bullshit	O	O
liberal	O	O
culture	O	O
that	O	O
has	O	O
caused	O	O
this	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
you	O	O
blame	O	O
it	O	O
all	O	O
on	O	O
society	O	O
,	O	O
there	O	O
's	O	O
noone	O	O
to	O	O
to	O	O
take	O	O
responsibility	O	O
and	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
sudden	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
generation	O	O
of	O	O
fucked	O	O
up	O	O
kids	O	O
who	O	O
are	O	O
likley	O	O
smoking	O	O
,	O	O
drinking	O	O
,	O	O
doing	O	O
drugs	O	O
,	O	O
fucking	O	O
the	O	O
neighbor	O	O
or	O	O
some	O	O
internet	O	O
perv	O	O
just	O	O
because	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
too	O	O
lazy	O	O
to	O	O
see	O	O
waht	O	O
they	O	O
're	O	O
doing	O	O
.	O	O

People	O	O
like	O	O
this	O	O
will	O	O
never	O	O
have	O	O
my	O	O
sympathy	O	O
,	O	O
nor	O	O
do	O	O
they	O	O
deserve	O	O
my	O	O
sympathy	O	O
.	O	O

Look	O	O
inside	O	O
yourselves	O	O
parents	O	O
,	O	O
is	O	O
this	O	O
you	O	O
?	O	O

Probably	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
.	O	O

Fuck	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

Stop	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
pawn	O	O
your	O	O
brats	O	O
off	O	O
on	O	O
others	O	O
to	O	O
"	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
break	O	O
"	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
made	O	O
a	O	O
choice	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
mommy	O	O
,	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
nt	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
break	O	O
until	O	O
they	O	O
move	O	O
out	O	O
,	O	O
that	O	O
s	O	O
the	O	O
choice	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
madea	O	O
and	O	O
that	O	O
's	O	O
life	O	O
.	O	O

Tough	O	O
shit	O	O
.	O	O

Just	O	O
because	O	O
you	O	O
're	O	O
stuck	O	O
,	O	O
does	O	O
nt	O	O
give	O	O
you	O	O
the	O	O
right	O	O
to	O	O
drag	O	O
down	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
singles	O	O
around	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

Another	O	O
time	O	O
I	O	O
'll	O	O
segueway	O	O
into	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
fun	O	O
work	O	O
related	O	O
instances	O	O
where	O	O
"	O	O
Mommies	O	O
"	O	O
get	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
doing	O	O
work	O	O
and	O	O
hiding	O	O
behind	O	O
childcare	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
reason	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
insidious	O	O
conspiracy	O	O
I	O	O
call	O	O
"	O	O
Mommism	O	O
"	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
must	O	O
be	O	O
stamped	O	O
out	O	O
.	O	O

[	O	O
http://www.newsday.com/news/opinion/ny-vpnasa054135614feb05,0,5979821.story?coll=ny-editorials-headlines	B-MISC	O
]	O	O

(	O	O
Newsday.com	B-MISC	O
)	O	O

It	O	O
looks	O	O
like	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
ready	O	O
to	O	O
sour	O	O
again	O	O
after	O	O
it's	O	O
devastating	O	O
loss	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
Columbia	B-MISC	B-LOC
accident	O	O
which	O	O
occurred	O	O
nearly	O	O
two	O	O
years	O	O
ago	O	O
.	O	O

Now	O	O
,	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
engineers	O	O
and	O	O
astronauts	O	O
are	O	O
almost	O	O
giddy	O	O
with	O	O
"	O	O
go	O	O
"	O	O
fever	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
tentative	O	O
date	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
first	O	O
launch	O	O
since	O	O
the	O	O
Columbia	B-MISC	B-LOC
disaster	O	O
approaches	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
most	O	O
important	O	O
question	O	O
is	O	O
n't	O	O
whether	O	O
Discovery	B-MISC	O
is	O	O
technically	O	O
ready	O	O
to	O	O
fly	O	O
with	O	O
new	O	O
safety	O	O
features	O	O
and	O	O
emergency	O	O
procedures	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
whether	O	O
the	O	O
agency	O	O
itself	O	O
has	O	O
learned	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
crucial	O	O
errors	O	O
most	O	O
common	O	O
to	O	O
Challenger	B-MISC	O
and	O	O
Columbia	B-MISC	B-LOC
,	O	O
errors	O	O
that	O	O
grew	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
management	O	O
culture	O	O
that	O	O
discouraged	O	O
criticism	O	O
and	O	O
sacrificed	O	O
safety	O	O
for	O	O
image	O	O
-	O	O
puffing	O	O
and	O	O
budget	O	O
-	O	O
cutting	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
hope	O	O
so	O	O
.	O	O

Seeing	O	O
another	O	O
"	O	O
Columbia	B-MISC	B-LOC
"	O	O
incident	O	O
can	O	O
be	O	O
quite	O	O
frightening	O	O
(	O	O
I	O	O
woke	O	O
up	O	O
to	O	O
it	O	O
early	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
morning	O	O
when	O	O
I	O	O
was	O	O
in	O	O
Texas	B-LOC	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
need	O	O
another	O	O
incident	O	O
as	O	O
exploring	O	O
the	O	O
cosmos	O	O
is	O	O
something	O	O
that	O	O
keeps	O	O
our	O	O
imagination	O	O
going	O	O
as	O	O
a	O	O
species	O	O
.	O	O

Maybe	O	O
one	O	O
day	O	O
they	O	O
will	O	O
allow	O	O
space	O	O
tourism	O	O
,	O	O
(	O	O
hopefully	O	O
that	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
near	O	O
future	O	O
)	O	O
although	O	O
I	O	O
would	O	O
recommend	O	O
that	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
build	O	O
new	O	O
shuttles	O	O
instead	O	O
of	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
preserve	O	O
the	O	O
older	O	O
ones	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
do	O	O
have	O	O
to	O	O
give	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
credit	O	O
on	O	O
some	O	O
things	O	O
as	O	O
they	O	O
have	O	O
eliminated	O	O
the	O	O
"	O	O
fear	O	O
of	O	O
reporting	O	O
failure	O	O
"	O	O
culture	O	O
that	O	O
probably	O	O
led	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
lack	O	O
of	O	O
reporting	O	O
defects	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
Columbia	B-MISC	B-LOC
shuttle	O	O
.	O	O

Instead	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
encouraging	O	O
everyone	O	O
to	O	O
come	O	O
forward	O	O
if	O	O
they	O	O
see	O	O
any	O	O
potential	O	O
problems	O	O
(	O	O
as	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
clear	O	O
that	O	O
overlooked	O	O
problems	O	O
could	O	O
result	O	O
in	O	O
unnecessary	O	O
losses	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
supporters	O	O
are	O	O
pointing	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
good	O	O
things	O	O
out	O	O
:	O	O

Clearly	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
agency	O	O
has	O	O
worked	O	O
hard	O	O
at	O	O
tackling	O	O
the	O	O
technical	O	O
challenges	O	O
posed	O	O
by	O	O
a	O	O
superb	O	O
and	O	O
surprisingly	O	O
independent	O	O
-	O	O
minded	O	O
investigative	O	O
panel	O	O
.	O	O

A	O	O
few	O	O
weeks	O	O
ago	O	O
,	O	O
shuttle	O	O
workers	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
Kennedy	B-ORG	B-PER
Space	I-ORG	O
Center	I-ORG	O
received	O	O
a	O	O
rocket	O	O
-	O	O
like	O	O
boost	O	O
in	O	O
morale	O	O
with	O	O
two	O	O
important	O	O
deliveries	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
next	O	O
shuttle	O	O
to	O	O
carry	O	O
.	O	O

One	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
special	O	O
tool	O	O
to	O	O
detect	O	O
damage	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
thermal	O	O
-	O	O
protective	O	O
tile	O	O
while	O	O
in	O	O
orbit	O	O
-	O	O
something	O	O
the	O	O
Columbia	B-MISC	B-LOC
crew	O	O
would	O	O
have	O	O
welcomed	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
other	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
new	O	O
fuel	O	O
tank	O	O
"	O	O
guaranteed	O	O
"	O	O
by	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
not	O	O
to	O	O
shed	O	O
potentially	O	O
fatal	O	O
hunks	O	O
of	O	O
insulation	O	O
.	O	O

NASA	B-ORG	O
has	O	O
some	O	O
PR	O	O
hurdles	O	O
to	O	O
overcome	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
future	O	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
let	O	O
s	O	O
hope	O	O
for	O	O
their	O	O
sake	O	O
(	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
sake	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
space	O	O
lovers	O	O
out	O	O
there	O	O
)	O	O
that	O	O
they	O	O
can	O	O
redefine	O	O
their	O	O
image	O	O
and	O	O
rekindle	O	O
the	O	O
hope	O	O
of	O	O
space	O	O
colonization	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

--	O	O

Posted	O	O
by	O	O
Hidden	B-PER	O
Nook	I-PER	O
to	O	O
Hidden	B-MISC	O
Nook	I-MISC	O
at	O	O
2/7/2005	O	O
01:09:32	O	O
AM	O	O

Healing	O	O
the	O	O
Collective	O	O
Body	O	O

In	O	O
George	B-PER	O
Orwell	I-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
influential	O	O
novel	O	O
"	O	O
1984	B-MISC	O
"	O	O
doublethink	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
device	O	O
promoted	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
totalitarian	O	O
state	O	O
government	O	O
to	O	O
make	O	O
people	O	O
accept	O	O
two	O	O
irreconcilable	O	O
ideas	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
time	O	O
such	O	O
as	O	O
"	O	O
war	O	O
is	O	O
peace	O	O
"	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
see	O	O
the	O	O
merit	O	O
in	O	O
flowing	O	O
with	O	O
duality	O	O
.	O	O

One	O	O
of	O	O
my	O	O
most	O	O
cherished	O	O
dualities	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
understanding	O	O
that	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
both	O	O
autonomous	O	O
individuals	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
power	O	O
to	O	O
shape	O	O
our	O	O
personal	O	O
destinies	O	O
and	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
time	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
all	O	O
one	O	O
,	O	O
that	O	O
there	O	O
is	O	O
no	O	O
separation	O	O
between	O	O
you	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
all	O	O
together	O	O
in	O	O
this	O	O
thing	O	O
called	O	O
life	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
human	O	O
beings	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
birds	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
tress	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
rocks	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
sky	O	O
,	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
written	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
recently	O	O
about	O	O
healing	O	O
the	O	O
self	O	O
so	O	O
today	O	O
here	O	O
are	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
words	O	O
on	O	O
healing	O	O
our	O	O
collective	O	O
body	O	O
,	O	O
mind	O	O
and	O	O
soul	O	O
.	O	O

Think	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
life	O	O
,	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
will	O	O
,	O	O
as	O	O
one	O	O
great	O	O
choir	O	O
or	O	O
one	O	O
grand	O	O
congregation	O	O
.	O	O

Our	O	O
strength	O	O
is	O	O
in	O	O
our	O	O
unity	O	O
and	O	O
harmony	O	O
.	O	O

Any	O	O
major	O	O
dischord	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
all	O	O
suffer	O	O
.	O	O

Any	O	O
insult	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
collective	O	O
good	O	O
brings	O	O
us	O	O
all	O	O
down	O	O
.	O	O

Living	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
synch	O	O
with	O	O
nature	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
great	O	O
disease	O	O
,	O	O
from	O	O
that	O	O
flows	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
tributaries	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
come	O	O
to	O	O
think	O	O
of	O	O
as	O	O
sickness	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
only	O	O
as	O	O
strong	O	O
as	O	O
our	O	O
weakest	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
only	O	O
as	O	O
healthy	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
sickest	O	O
amongst	O	O
us	O	O
-	O	O
playing	O	O
sports	O	O
and	O	O
being	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
army	O	O
taught	O	O
me	O	O
that	O	O
lesson	O	O
before	O	O
I	O	O
was	O	O
finished	O	O
being	O	O
a	O	O
teenager	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
the	O	O
healthy	O	O
treat	O	O
the	O	O
sick	O	O
with	O	O
scorn	O	O
and	O	O
intolerance	O	O
it	O	O
brings	O	O
us	O	O
all	O	O
down	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
those	O	O
lucky	O	O
enough	O	O
not	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
Herpes	O	O
create	O	O
a	O	O
climate	O	O
of	O	O
shame	O	O
and	O	O
indignity	O	O
for	O	O
those	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
who	O	O
do	O	O
,	O	O
not	O	O
only	O	O
are	O	O
they	O	O
hurting	O	O
us	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
hurting	O	O
themselves	O	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
is	O	O
no	O	O
escape	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
collective	O	O
ocean	O	O
we	O	O
all	O	O
swim	O	O
in	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
you	O	O
project	O	O
will	O	O
always	O	O
come	O	O
back	O	O
to	O	O
either	O	O
reward	O	O
or	O	O
haunt	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
now	O	O
suffering	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
consequences	O	O
of	O	O
our	O	O
rape	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
environment	O	O
,	O	O
our	O	O
rejection	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
natural	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
industrial	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
our	O	O
embrace	O	O
of	O	O
violence	O	O
over	O	O
peace	O	O
.	O	O

Jesus	B-PER	O
said	O	O
that	O	O
what	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
the	O	O
least	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
people	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
to	O	O
him	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
are	O	O
you	O	O
doing	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
least	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
people	O	O
?	O	O

If	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
all	O	O
in	O	O
this	O	O
thing	O	O
together	O	O
,	O	O
let	O	O
's	O	O
play	O	O
nice	O	O
.	O	O

Remember	O	O
that	O	O
what	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
to	O	O
yourself	O	O
affects	O	O
me	O	O
and	O	O
everybody	O	O
else	O	O
,	O	O
remember	O	O
that	O	O
what	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
to	O	O
me	O	O
and	O	O
anyone	O	O
else	O	O
shapes	O	O
your	O	O
destiny	O	O
.	O	O

No	O	O
matter	O	O
what	O	O
progress	O	O
we	O	O
make	O	O
as	O	O
individuals	O	O
in	O	O
becoming	O	O
healthier	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
never	O	O
achieve	O	O
real	O	O
health	O	O
until	O	O
we	O	O
collectively	O	O
decide	O	O
to	O	O
create	O	O
a	O	O
healthier	O	O
reality	O	O
.	O	O

Fortunately	O	O
circumstances	O	O
will	O	O
force	O	O
our	O	O
hand	O	O
soon	O	O
since	O	O
our	O	O
collective	O	O
bad	O	O
behaviour	O	O
can	O	O
not	O	O
continue	O	O
indefinitely	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
the	O	O
near	O	O
future	O	O
collective	O	O
choices	O	O
will	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
made	O	O
.	O	O

Will	O	O
we	O	O
choose	O	O
to	O	O
live	O	O
in	O	O
harmony	O	O
with	O	O
this	O	O
planet	O	O
or	O	O
crash	O	O
and	O	O
burn	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
conflagration	O	O
of	O	O
arrogance	O	O
and	O	O
disregard	O	O
?	O	O

Will	O	O
we	O	O
choose	O	O
to	O	O
rise	O	O
about	O	O
prejudice	O	O
and	O	O
intolerance	O	O
or	O	O
go	O	O
down	O	O
kicking	O	O
and	O	O
screaming	O	O
with	O	O
holding	O	O
on	O	O
to	O	O
fear	O	O
and	O	O
anger	O	O
?	O	O

There	O	O
is	O	O
no	O	O
health	O	O
without	O	O
peace	O	O
and	O	O
no	O	O
peace	O	O
without	O	O
health	O	O
.	O	O

November	O	O
2005	O	O

Sunshine	B-LOC	O
Coast	I-LOC	O
,	O	O
British	B-LOC	B-LOCderiv
Columbia	I-LOC	B-MISC
,	O	O
Canada	B-LOC	O

Christopher	B-PER	O
Scipio	I-PER	O
Homeopath	O	O
/	O	O
Herbalist	O	O
Holistic	O	O
Viral	O	O
Specialist	O	O

One	O	O
Simple	O	O
Idea	O	O
.	O	O

One	O	O
Huge	O	O
Opportunity	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
are	O	O
you	O	O
searching	O	O
for	O	O
?	O	O

More	O	O
personal	O	O
freedom	O	O
?	O	O

More	O	O
time	O	O
with	O	O
your	O	O
family	O	O
?	O	O

Independent	O	O
wealth	O	O
?	O	O

Freedom	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
fear	O	O
of	O	O
corporate	O	O
downsizing	O	O
?	O	O

Whether	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
part	O	O
-	O	O
time	O	O
income	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
pay	O	O
off	O	O
your	O	O
debts	O	O
or	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
freedom	O	O
offered	O	O
by	O	O
working	O	O
from	O	O
home	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
full	O	O
time	O	O
basis	O	O
,	O	O
Agel	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
vehicle	O	O
that	O	O
can	O	O
make	O	O
that	O	O
happen	O	O
.	O	O

Agel	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
new	O	O
company	O	O
and	O	O
is	O	O
uniquely	O	O
positioned	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
the	O	O
next	O	O
giant	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
network	O	O
marketing	O	O
industry	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
company	O	O
has	O	O
developed	O	O
an	O	O
entirely	O	O
new	O	O
category	O	O
of	O	O
products	O	O
.	O	O

Imagine	O	O
being	O	O
part	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
next	O	O
industry	O	O
-	O	O
changing	O	O
innovation	O	O
.	O	O

Innovative	O	O
Products	O	O

Agel	B-ORG	O
introduces	O	O
an	O	O
entirely	O	O
new	O	O
category	O	O
of	O	O
products	O	O
called	O	O
Gelceuticals	B-MISC	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
company	O	O
has	O	O
developed	O	O
a	O	O
unique	O	O
and	O	O
innovative	O	O
delivery	O	O
mechanism	O	O
for	O	O
nutritional	O	O
products	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
proprietary	O	O
Gel	O	O
Suspension	O	O
technology	O	O
makes	O	O
possible	O	O
single	O	O
serving	O	O
packets	O	O
of	O	O
Gelceuticals	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
this	O	O
delivery	O	O
format	O	O
,	O	O
your	O	O
body	O	O
can	O	O
immediately	O	O
start	O	O
receiving	O	O
the	O	O
benefits	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
product	O	O
components	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
absorption	O	O
of	O	O
vitamins	O	O
,	O	O
minerals	O	O
and	O	O
nutrients	O	O
is	O	O
maximized	O	O
.	O	O

Never	O	O
before	O	O
has	O	O
such	O	O
a	O	O
convenient	O	O
method	O	O
been	O	O
available	O	O
for	O	O
consuming	O	O
nutritional	O	O
products	O	O
.	O	O

Consider	O	O
these	O	O
convenience	O	O
factors	O	O
:	O	O

No	O	O
water	O	O
needed	O	O
(	O	O
as	O	O
with	O	O
tablets	O	O
or	O	O
capsules	O	O
)	O	O

Exotic	O	O
juice	O	O
benefits	O	O
without	O	O
the	O	O
big	O	O
bottle	O	O
(	O	O
no	O	O
glass	O	O
and	O	O
water	O	O
weight	O	O
)	O	O

Single	O	O
serving	O	O
packages	O	O
(	O	O
imagine	O	O
the	O	O
sampling	O	O
capabilities	O	O
)	O	O

Perfect	O	O
for	O	O
those	O	O
with	O	O
difficulty	O	O
swallowing	O	O
tablets	O	O
or	O	O
capsules	O	O

Faster	O	O
,	O	O
more	O	O
efficient	O	O
,	O	O
delivery	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
body	O	O
Learn	O	O
More	O	O

Revolutionary	O	O
Compensation	O	O

Agel	B-ORG	O
has	O	O
created	O	O
a	O	O
new	O	O
compensation	O	O
structure	O	O
that	O	O
is	O	O
truly	O	O
revolutionary	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
our	O	O
belief	O	O
that	O	O
this	O	O
compensation	O	O
plan	O	O
will	O	O
produce	O	O
some	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
largest	O	O
checks	O	O
in	O	O
network	O	O
marketing	O	O
history	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
plan	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
be	O	O
described	O	O
as	O	O
a	O	O
binary	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
breakaway	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
unilevel	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
a	O	O
forced	O	O
matrix	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
revolutionary	O	O
hybrid	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
is	O	O
long	O	O
term	O	O
viability	O	O
?	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
just	O	O
company	O	O
longevity	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
used	O	O
to	O	O
make	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
100	O	O
k	O	O
and	O	O
now	O	O
only	O	O
make	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
30	O	O
k	O	O
,	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
long	O	O
term	O	O
viability	O	O
.	O	O

Ten	O	O
years	O	O
later	O	O
your	O	O
check	O	O
should	O	O
still	O	O
be	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
or	O	O
greater	O	O
,	O	O
fulfilling	O	O
the	O	O
promise	O	O
of	O	O
long	O	O
-	O	O
term	O	O
residual	O	O
income	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
Agel	B-ORG	O
compensation	O	O
plan	O	O
includes	O	O
the	O	O
principles	O	O
that	O	O
ensure	O	O
that	O	O
promise	O	O
can	O	O
be	O	O
fulfilled	O	O
for	O	O
those	O	O
who	O	O
work	O	O
at	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Are	O	O
you	O	O
unsure	O	O
of	O	O
Agel	B-ORG	O
?	O	O

Take	O	O
time	O	O
to	O	O
discover	O	O
the	O	O
unlimited	O	O
possibilities	O	O
with	O	O
Agel	B-ORG	O
!	O	O

The	O	O
call	O	O
will	O	O
feature	O	O
a	O	O
host	O	O
of	O	O
other	O	O
field	O	O
leaders	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
our	O	O
founder	O	O
and	O	O
CEO	O	O
,	O	O
Glen	B-PER	O
Jensen	I-PER	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
call	O	O
will	O	O
smoke	O	O
!	O	O

You	O	O
will	O	O
discover	O	O
:	O	O
·	O	O
How	O	O
to	O	O
Create	O	O
the	O	O
Security	O	O
of	O	O
Residual	O	O
Income	O	O
;	O	O
·	O	O
Why	O	O
Agel	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
Best	O	O
Vehicle	O	O
to	O	O
Live	O	O
Your	O	O
Dreams	O	O
;	O	O
·	O	O
The	O	O
Amazing	O	O
Scientific	O	O
Breakthrough	O	O
Behind	O	O
the	O	O
Products	O	O
;	O	O
·	O	O
How	O	O
the	O	O
"	O	O
Quadra	B-MISC	O
-	I-MISC	O
Plan	I-MISC	O
"	O	O
Builds	O	O
Bigger	O	O
Bonus	O	O
Checks	O	O
Faster	O	O
;	O	O
·	O	O
The	O	O
Support	O	O
System	O	O
in	O	O
Place	O	O
to	O	O
Help	O	O
You	O	O
Build	O	O
Stronger	O	O
;	O	O
and	O	O
·	O	O
The	O	O
Secret	O	O
to	O	O
Lock	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
"	O	O
Legacy	O	O
"	O	O
Position	O	O
!	O	O

Here	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
numbers	O	O
to	O	O
call	O	O
:	O	O

620-294-4000	O	O
or	O	O
620-294-3000	O	O

The	O	O
Passcode	O	O
to	O	O
participate	O	O
is	O	O
:	O	O
5107	O	O

DATE	O	O
:	O	O
Tuesday	O	O
,	O	O
November	O	O
22	O	O
,	O	O
2005	O	O

TIME	O	O
:	O	O
8:00	O	O
PM	O	O
Eastern	O	O
Standard	O	O
Time	O	O

LOCATION	O	O
:	O	O
Conference	O	O
Call	O	O

5:00	O	O
PT	O	O
**	O	O
6:00	O	O
MT	O	O
**	O	O
7:00	O	O
CT	O	O
**	O	O
8:00	O	O
ET	O	O

I	O	O
'll	O	O
see	O	O
you	O	O
there	O	O
!	O	O

Steve	B-PER	O
Fillmore	I-PER	O
612-205-9814	O	O
620-294-1909	O	O

Email	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
Dharmadeva	B-PER	O
"	O	O
<	O	O
dharmad...@gmail.com	B-PER	O
>	O	O

Namaskar	O	O

Hi	O	O
All	O	O
!	O	O

We	O	O
now	O	O
present	O	O
the	O	O
kaoshikii	O	O
dance	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
is	O	O
excellent	O	O
before	O	O
and	O	O
after	O	O
yoga	O	O
postures	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
encourage	O	O
you	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
this	O	O
dance	O	O
,	O	O
as	O	O
it	O	O
has	O	O
tremendous	O	O
positive	O	O
effects	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
dance	O	O
for	O	O
both	O	O
males	O	O
and	O	O
females	O	O
.	O	O

Dharma	B-PER	O

--	O	O

Kaoshikii	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
dance	O	O
which	O	O
was	O	O
invented	O	O
in	O	O
1978	O	O
by	O	O
Shrii	B-PER	O
Shrii	I-PER	O
A'nandamu'rti	I-PER	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
psycho-spiritual	O	O
exercise	O	O
and	O	O
benefiting	O	O
the	O	O
mind	O	O
by	O	O
developing	O	O
stamina	O	O
and	O	O
strength	O	O
.	O	O

Kaoshikii	B-MISC	O
is	O	O
especially	O	O
good	O	O
for	O	O
women	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
can	O	O
ward	O	O
off	O	O
and	O	O
cure	O	O
a	O	O
number	O	O
of	O	O
diseases	O	O
,	O	O
keeps	O	O
the	O	O
body	O	O
youthful	O	O
and	O	O
enables	O	O
an	O	O
easy	O	O
delivery	O	O
in	O	O
childbirth	O	O
.	O	O

Kaoshikii	B-MISC	O
comes	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
Sanskrit	B-MISC	O
word	O	O
'	O	O
kosa	O	O
'	O	O
meaning	O	O
shell	O	O
or	O	O
layer	O	O
of	O	O
mind	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
self	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
individual	O	O
lies	O	O
hidden	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
innermost	O	O
layers	O	O
of	O	O
existence	O	O
(	O	O
kosas	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Thus	O	O
kaoshikii	B-MISC	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
blossoming	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
microcosm	O	O
(	O	O
unit	O	O
being	O	O
)	O	O
in	O	O
its	O	O
attempt	O	O
to	O	O
attain	O	O
a	O	O
link	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
Macrocosm	O	O
(	O	O
Cosmic	O	O
Consciousness	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
attempt	O	O
is	O	O
normally	O	O
referred	O	O
to	O	O
as	O	O
mysticism	O	O
.	O	O

--	O	O

The	O	O
Benefits	O	O

Exercises	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
glands	O	O
and	O	O
limbs	O	O
from	O	O
head	O	O
to	O	O
toes	O	O
.	O	O

Increases	O	O
longevity	O	O
.	O	O

Makes	O	O
for	O	O
easy	O	O
delivery	O	O
at	O	O
childbirth	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
spine	O	O
will	O	O
become	O	O
flexible	O	O
.	O	O

Arthritis	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
spine	O	O
,	O	O
neck	O	O
,	O	O
waist	O	O
and	O	O
other	O	O
joints	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
removed	O	O
.	O	O

Gout	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
spine	O	O
,	O	O
neck	O	O
,	O	O
hands	O	O
and	O	O
waist	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
lost	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
mind	O	O
becomes	O	O
strong	O	O
and	O	O
sharp	O	O
.	O	O

Irregularities	O	O
in	O	O
menstruation	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
cured	O	O
.	O	O

Glandular	O	O
secretions	O	O
will	O	O
become	O	O
regulated	O	O
.	O	O

Troubles	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
bladder	O	O
and	O	O
urethra	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
cured	O	O
.	O	O

Gives	O	O
control	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
limbs	O	O
.	O	O

Adds	O	O
charm	O	O
and	O	O
shine	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
face	O	O
and	O	O
skin	O	O
.	O	O

Removes	O	O
wrinkles	O	O
.	O	O

Removes	O	O
lethargy	O	O
.	O	O

Cures	O	O
insomnia	O	O
.	O	O

Cures	O	O
hysteria	O	O
.	O	O

Fear	O	O
complexes	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
removed	O	O
.	O	O

Hopelessness	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
lost	O	O
.	O	O

Helps	O	O
in	O	O
self	O	O
-	O	O
expression	O	O
and	O	O
develops	O	O
one	O	O
's	O	O
potentiality	O	O
.	O	O

Spinal	O	O
pain	O	O
,	O	O
piles	O	O
,	O	O
hernia	O	O
,	O	O
hydrocele	O	O
in	O	O
men	O	O
,	O	O
nervous	O	O
pain	O	O
,	O	O
nervous	O	O
disability	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
cured	O	O
.	O	O

Cures	O	O
kidney	O	O
and	O	O
gall	O	O
bladder	O	O
troubles	O	O
,	O	O
gastric	O	O
trouble	O	O
,	O	O
dyspepsia	O	O
,	O	O
acidity	O	O
,	O	O
dysentery	O	O
,	O	O
obesity	O	O
and	O	O
liver	O	O
diseases	O	O
.	O	O

Increases	O	O
the	O	O
capacity	O	O
to	O	O
work	O	O
until	O	O
75	O	O
-	O	O
80	O	O
years	O	O
of	O	O
age	O	O
.	O	O

--	O	O

The	O	O
Dance	O	O

The	O	O
eighteen	O	O
steps	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
dance	O	O
are	O	O
done	O	O
rhythmically	O	O
.	O	O

First	O	O
the	O	O
dancer	O	O
begins	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
starting	O	O
position	O	O
:	O	O
the	O	O
hands	O	O
together	O	O
and	O	O
raised	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
head	O	O
.	O	O

Then	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
beat	O	O
of	O	O
"	O	O
dhin	O	O
,	O	O
dhin	O	O
,	O	O
...	O	O
,	O	O
ta'	O	O
,	O	O
ta'	O	O
"	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
dancers	O	O
begin	O	O
their	O	O
step	O	O
,	O	O
placing	O	O
the	O	O
big	O	O
toe	O	O
behind	O	O
the	O	O
heel	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
other	O	O
foot	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
the	O	O
final	O	O
two	O	O
steps	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
dancers	O	O
firmly	O	O
stamp	O	O
their	O	O
feet	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
ground	O	O
.	O	O

Kaoshikii	B-MISC	O
can	O	O
be	O	O
danced	O	O
for	O	O
as	O	O
many	O	O
rounds	O	O
as	O	O
you	O	O
like	O	O
.	O	O

--	O	O

The	O	O
Ideation	O	O

When	O	O
the	O	O
dancers	O	O
start	O	O
the	O	O
step	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
beat	O	O
of	O	O
"	O	O
dhin	O	O
,	O	O
dhin	O	O
...	O	O
"	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
mental	O	O
ideation	O	O
should	O	O
also	O	O
be	O	O
kept	O	O
.	O	O

Here	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
ideation	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
two	O	O
hands	O	O
when	O	O
upraised	O	O
and	O	O
folded	O	O
together	O	O
represent	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
Now	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
establish	O	O
a	O	O
link	O	O
with	O	O
Parama	O	O
Purus'a	O	O
(	O	O
Supreme	O	O
Consciousness	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

Bending	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
right	O	O
indicates	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
I	O	O
know	O	O
the	O	O
right	O	O
way	O	O
to	O	O
request	O	O
You	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

Bending	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
left	O	O
indicates	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
I	O	O
know	O	O
how	O	O
to	O	O
fulfil	O	O
Your	O	O
demands	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

Bending	O	O
forward	O	O
suggests	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
I	O	O
completely	O	O
surrender	O	O
to	O	O
You	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

Bending	O	O
backward	O	O
represents	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
ready	O	O
to	O	O
face	O	O
all	O	O
obstacles	O	O
that	O	O
may	O	O
come	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

The	O	O
last	O	O
two	O	O
steps	O	O
represent	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
O	O	O
Lord	O	O
I	O	O
repeat	O	O
Your	O	O
cosmic	O	O
rhythm	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

Quebecker	B-LOCderiv	O
wins	O	O
U.S.	B-LOCderiv	O
bravery	O	O
award	O	O

Pittsburgh	B-LOC	O
-	O	O

A	O	O
Quebec	B-LOC	O
man	O	O
was	O	O
awarded	O	O
a	O	O
Carnegie	B-MISC	B-PER
Medal	I-MISC	O
for	O	O
bravery	O	O
on	O	O
Monday	O	O
for	O	O
saving	O	O
two	O	O
friends	O	O
by	O	O
fighting	O	O
off	O	O
a	O	O
polar	O	O
bear	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
pocket	O	O
knife	O	O
two	O	O
years	O	O
ago	O	O
on	O	O
Baffin	B-LOC	O
Island	I-LOC	O

Dr.	O	O
Eric	B-PER	O
Fortier	I-PER	O
,	O	O
34	O	O
,	O	O
of	O	O
Gatineau	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
Que.	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
used	O	O
a	O	O
pocket	O	O
knife	O	O
to	O	O
attack	O	O
a	O	O
polar	O	O
bear	O	O
on	O	O
Baffin	B-LOC	O
Island	I-LOC	O
,	O	O
just	O	O
south	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Arctic	B-LOC	O
Circle	I-LOC	O
,	O	O
to	O	O
save	O	O
two	O	O
friends	O	O
who	O	O
were	O	O
being	O	O
mauled	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
All	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
research	O	O
and	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
preparation	O	O
I	O	O
did	O	O
leading	O	O
up	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
trip	O	O
gave	O	O
no	O	O
indication	O	O
that	O	O
there	O	O
were	O	O
bears	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
Soper	B-LOC	O
[	I-LOC	O
River	I-LOC	O
]	I-LOC	O
valley	I-LOC	O
where	O	O
we	O	O
were	O	O
canoeing	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
,	O	O
an	O	O
orthodontist	O	O
,	O	O
learned	O	O
there	O	O
was	O	O
at	O	O
least	O	O
one	O	O
polar	O	O
bear	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
central	O	O
region	O	O
of	O	O
Baffin	B-LOC	O
Island	I-LOC	O
in	O	O
July	O	O
2001	O	O
when	O	O
he	O	O
felt	O	O
what	O	O
he	O	O
thought	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
dog	O	O
leaning	O	O
on	O	O
his	O	O
tent	O	O
wall	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
My	O	O
first	O	O
thought	O	O
was	O	O
to	O	O
push	O	O
it	O	O
away	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
he	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
A	O	O
few	O	O
seconds	O	O
later	O	O
my	O	O
girlfriend	O	O
saw	O	O
the	O	O
shadow	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
bear	O	O
's	O	O
paw	O	O
through	O	O
the	O	O
tent	O	O
fly	O	O
and	O	O
then	O	O
it	O	O
started	O	O
ripping	O	O
through	O	O
the	O	O
ceiling	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

The	O	O
polar	O	O
bear	O	O
is	O	O
more	O	O
dangerous	O	O
than	O	O
most	O	O
other	O	O
bears	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
latter	O	O
usually	O	O
consider	O	O
human	O	O
beings	O	O
a	O	O
threat	O	O
but	O	O
the	O	O
polar	O	O
bear	O	O
considers	O	O
humans	O	O
a	O	O
snack	O	O
,	O	O
experts	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
two	O	O
screamed	O	O
to	O	O
frighten	O	O
the	O	O
bear	O	O
and	O	O
warn	O	O
their	O	O
friends	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
tent	O	O
several	O	O
metres	O	O
away	O	O
but	O	O
the	O	O
bear	O	O
ripped	O	O
into	O	O
that	O	O
tent	O	O
and	O	O
began	O	O
mauling	O	O
31	O	O
-	O	O
year	O	O
-	O	O
old	O	O
Alain	B-PER	O
Parenteau	I-PER	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
Their	O	O
screams	O	O
changed	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
I	O	O
grabbed	O	O
my	O	O
glasses	O	O
and	O	O
my	O	O
knife	O	O
and	O	O
unzipped	O	O
my	O	O
tent	O	O
and	O	O
headed	O	O
out	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

The	O	O
bear	O	O
dwarfed	O	O
the	O	O
6	O	O
-	O	O
foot	O	O
-	O	O
1	O	O
Mr.	O	O
Parenteau	B-PER	O
,	O	O
knocking	O	O
him	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
ground	O	O
,	O	O
he	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
threw	O	O
a	O	O
large	O	O
rock	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
bear	O	O
,	O	O
distracting	O	O
it	O	O
and	O	O
allowing	O	O
Parenteau	B-PER	O
to	O	O
escape	O	O
but	O	O
it	O	O
then	O	O
turned	O	O
on	O	O
25	O	O
-	O	O
year	O	O
-	O	O
old	O	O
Patricia	B-PER	O
Doyon	I-PER	O
,	O	O
who	O	O
was	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
tent	O	O
.	O	O

Again	O	O
Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
threw	O	O
rocks	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
bear	O	O
and	O	O
again	O	O
its	O	O
target	O	O
was	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
escape	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
The	O	O
bear	O	O
gave	O	O
chase	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
gave	O	O
chase	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
he	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
At	O	O
some	O	O
point	O	O
,	O	O
Patricia	B-PER	O
tripped	O	O
or	O	O
the	O	O
bear	O	O
tripped	O	O
her	O	O
and	O	O
was	O	O
at	O	O
her	O	O
back	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
beside	O	O
the	O	O
bear	O	O
's	O	O
head	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
stabbed	O	O
it	O	O
with	O	O
an	O	O
upper	O	O
cut	O	O
below	O	O
the	O	O
jaw	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
neck	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
times	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

The	O	O
bear	O	O
ran	O	O
off	O	O
.	O	O

While	O	O
there	O	O
was	O	O
some	O	O
fur	O	O
and	O	O
blood	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
nine	O	O
-	O	O
centimetre	O	O
blade	O	O
,	O	O
Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
said	O	O
he	O	O
does	O	O
n't	O	O
think	O	O
he	O	O
hurt	O	O
the	O	O
bear	O	O
badly	O	O
.	O	O

Both	O	O
Mr.	O	O
Parenteau	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Ms.	O	O
Doyon	B-PER	O
,	O	O
however	O	O
,	O	O
were	O	O
bleeding	O	O
badly	O	O
.	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
and	O	O
his	O	O
girlfriend	O	O
lashed	O	O
two	O	O
canoes	O	O
together	O	O
and	O	O
paddled	O	O
eight	O	O
kilometres	O	O
along	O	O
the	O	O
Soper	B-LOC	O
River	I-LOC	O
.	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
travelled	O	O
another	O	O
three	O	O
kilometres	O	O
by	O	O
foot	O	O
to	O	O
seek	O	O
help	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
nearest	O	O
settlement	O	O
.	O	O

Both	O	O
Mr.	O	O
Parenteau	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Ms.	O	O
Doyon	B-PER	O
were	O	O
airlifted	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
hospital	O	O
and	O	O
survived	O	O
,	O	O
though	O	O
Mr.	O	O
Parenteau	B-PER	O
had	O	O
a	O	O
gash	O	O
within	O	O
a	O	O
centimetre	O	O
of	O	O
his	O	O
jugular	O	O
,	O	O
Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

Dr.	O	O
Fortier	B-PER	O
was	O	O
one	O	O
of	O	O
15	O	O
people	O	O
to	O	O
receive	O	O
the	O	O
Carnegie	B-MISC	B-PER
Medal	I-MISC	O
on	O	O
Monday	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
bronze	O	O
medal	O	O
is	O	O
given	O	O
to	O	O
people	O	O
who	O	O
"	O	O
risk	O	O
their	O	O
lives	O	O
to	O	O
an	O	O
extraordinary	O	O
degree	O	O
while	O	O
saving	O	O
or	O	O
attempting	O	O
to	O	O
save	O	O
the	O	O
lives	O	O
of	O	O
others	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

The	O	O
other	O	O
Canadian	B-LOCderiv	O
recipient	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
medal	O	O
was	O	O
Ronald	B-PER	O
Joseph	I-PER	O
Crawford	I-PER	O
,	O	O
42	O	O
,	O	O
of	O	O
Hamilton	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
who	O	O
was	O	O
killed	O	O
Aug.	O	O
4	O	O
,	O	O
2002	O	O
,	O	O
while	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
defend	O	O
a	O	O
Hamilton	B-LOC	O
sandwich	O	O
shop	O	O
owner	O	O
from	O	O
a	O	O
robber	O	O
wielding	O	O
a	O	O
knife	O	O
.	O	O

Mr.	O	O
Crawford	B-PER	O
threw	O	O
several	O	O
punches	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
assailant	O	O
before	O	O
he	O	O
was	O	O
stabbed	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
heart	O	O
.	O	O

U.S.	B-LOCderiv	O
industrialist	O	O
Andrew	B-PER	O
Carnegie	I-PER	O
started	O	O
a	O	O
hero	O	O
fund	O	O
in	O	O
1904	O	O
after	O	O
being	O	O
inspired	O	O
by	O	O
rescue	O	O
stories	O	O
from	O	O
a	O	O
mine	O	O
disaster	O	O
that	O	O
killed	O	O
181	O	O
people	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
award	O	O
comes	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
$	O	O
3,500	O	O
(	O	O
U.S.	B-LOCderiv	O
)	O	O
grant	O	O
.	O	O

Important	O	O
information	O	O
of	O	O
big	O	O
companies	O	O

Apple	B-ORG	O
Computers	I-ORG	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
the	O	O
favorite	O	O
fruit	O	O
of	O	O
founder	O	O
Steve	B-PER	O
Jobs	I-PER	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
was	O	O
three	O	O
months	O	O
late	O	O
in	O	O
filing	O	O
a	O	O
name	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
business	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
he	O	O
threatened	O	O
to	O	O
call	O	O
his	O	O
company	O	O
Apple	B-ORG	O
Computers	I-ORG	O
if	O	O
the	O	O
other	O	O
colleagues	O	O
did	O	O
n't	O	O
suggest	O	O
a	O	O
better	O	O
name	O	O
by	O	O
5	O	O
O'clock	O	O
.	O	O

CISCO	B-ORG	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
an	O	O
acronym	O	O
as	O	O
popularly	O	O
believed	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
short	O	O
for	O	O
San	B-LOC	O
Francisco	I-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

Compaq	B-ORG	O

This	O	O
name	O	O
was	O	O
formed	O	O
by	O	O
using	O	O
COMp	O	O
,	O	O
for	O	O
computer	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
PAQ	O	O
to	O	O
denote	O	O
a	O	O
small	O	O
integral	O	O
object	O	O
.	O	O

Corel	B-ORG	O

The	O	O
name	O	O
was	O	O
derived	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
founder	O	O
's	O	O
name	O	O
Dr.	O	O
Michael	B-PER	O
Cowpland	I-PER	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
stands	O	O
for	O	O
COwpland	B-ORG	B-PER
REsearch	I-ORG	O
Laboratory	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

Google	B-ORG	O

The	O	O
name	O	O
started	O	O
as	O	O
a	O	O
joke	O	O
boasting	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
amount	O	O
of	O	O
information	O	O
the	O	O
search	O	O
-	O	O
engine	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
search	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
originally	O	O
named	O	O
'	O	O
Googol	O	O
'	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
word	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
number	O	O
represented	O	O
by	O	O
1	O	O
followed	O	O
by	O	O
100	O	O
zeros	O	O
.	O	O

After	O	O
founders	O	O
-	O	O
Stanford	B-ORG	B-PER
graduate	O	O
students	O	O
Sergey	B-PER	O
Brin	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Larry	B-PER	O
Page	I-PER	O
presented	O	O
their	O	O
project	O	O
to	O	O
an	O	O
angel	O	O
investor	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
received	O	O
a	O	O
cheque	O	O
made	O	O
out	O	O
to	O	O
'	O	O
Google	B-ORG	O
'	O	O

Hotmail	B-ORG	O

Founder	O	O
Jack	B-PER	O
Smith	I-PER	O
got	O	O
the	O	O
idea	O	O
of	O	O
accessing	O	O
e-mail	O	O
via	O	O
the	O	O
web	O	O
from	O	O
a	O	O
computer	O	O
anywhere	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
world	O	O
.	O	O

When	O	O
Sabeer	B-PER	O
Bhatia	I-PER	O
came	O	O
up	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
business	O	O
plan	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
mail	O	O
service	O	O
,	O	O
he	O	O
tried	O	O
all	O	O
kinds	O	O
of	O	O
names	O	O
ending	O	O
in	O	O
'	O	O
mail	O	O
'	O	O
and	O	O
finally	O	O
settled	O	O
for	O	O
hotmail	B-ORG	O
as	O	O
it	O	O
included	O	O
the	O	O
letters	O	O
"	O	O
html	O	O
"	O	O
-	O	O
the	O	O
programming	O	O
language	O	O
used	O	O
to	O	O
write	O	O
web	O	O
pages	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
initially	O	O
referred	O	O
to	O	O
as	O	O
HoTMaiL	B-ORG	O
with	O	O
selective	O	O
uppercasing	O	O
.	O	O

Hewlett	B-ORG	B-PER
Packard	I-ORG	B-PER

Bill	B-PER	O
Hewlett	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Dave	B-PER	O
Packard	I-PER	O
tossed	O	O
a	O	O
coin	O	O
to	O	O
decide	O	O
whether	O	O
the	O	O
company	O	O
they	O	O
founded	O	O
would	O	O
be	O	O
called	O	O
Hewlett	B-ORG	B-PER
-	I-ORG	O
Packard	I-ORG	B-PER
or	O	O
Packard	B-ORG	B-PER
-	I-ORG	O
Hewlett	I-ORG	B-PER
.	O	O

Intel	B-ORG	O

Bob	B-PER	O
Noyce	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Gordon	B-PER	O
Moore	I-PER	O
wanted	O	O
to	O	O
name	O	O
their	O	O
new	O	O
company	O	O
'	O	O
Moore	B-ORG	B-PER
Noyce	I-ORG	B-PER
'	O	O
but	O	O
that	O	O
was	O	O
already	O	O
trademarked	O	O
by	O	O
a	O	O
hotel	O	O
chain	O	O
so	O	O
they	O	O
had	O	O
to	O	O
settle	O	O
for	O	O
an	O	O
acronym	O	O
of	O	O
INTegrated	B-ORG	O
ELectronics	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

Lotus	B-ORG	O
(	O	O
Notes	O	O
)	O	O

Mitch	B-PER	O
Kapor	I-PER	O
got	O	O
the	O	O
name	O	O
for	O	O
his	O	O
company	O	O
from	O	O
'	O	O
The	O	O
Lotus	O	O
Position	O	O
'	O	O
or	O	O
'	O	O
Padmasana	O	O
'	O	O
.	O	O

Kapor	B-PER	O
used	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
teacher	O	O
of	O	O
Transcendental	O	O
Meditation	O	O
of	O	O
Maharishi	B-PER	O
Mahesh	I-PER	O
Yogi	I-PER	O
.	O	O

Microsoft	B-ORG	O

Coined	O	O
by	O	O
Bill	B-PER	O
Gates	I-PER	O
to	O	O
represent	O	O
the	O	O
company	O	O
that	O	O
was	O	O
devoted	O	O
to	O	O
MICROcomputer	O	O
SOFTware	O	O
.	O	O

Originally	O	O
christened	O	O
Micro	B-ORG	O
-	I-ORG	O
Soft	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
'	O	O
-	O	O
'	O	O
was	O	O
removed	O	O
later	O	O
on	O	O
.	O	O

Motorola	B-ORG	O

Founder	O	O
Paul	B-PER	O
Galvin	I-PER	O
came	O	O
up	O	O
with	O	O
this	O	O
name	O	O
when	O	O
his	O	O
company	O	O
started	O	O
manufacturing	O	O
radios	O	O
for	O	O
cars	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
popular	O	O
radio	O	O
company	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
time	O	O
was	O	O
called	O	O
Victrola	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

ORACLE	B-ORG	O

Larry	B-PER	O
Ellison	I-PER	O
and	O	O
Bob	B-PER	O
Oats	I-PER	O
were	O	O
working	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
consulting	O	O
project	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
CIA	B-ORG	O
(	O	O
Central	B-ORG	O
Intelligence	I-ORG	O
Agency	I-ORG	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
code	O	O
name	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
project	O	O
was	O	O
called	O	O
Oracle	B-ORG	O
(	O	O
the	O	O
CIA	B-ORG	O
saw	O	O
this	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
system	O	O
to	O	O
give	O	O
answers	O	O
to	O	O
all	O	O
questions	O	O
or	O	O
something	O	O
such	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
project	O	O
was	O	O
designed	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
use	O	O
the	O	O
newly	O	O
written	O	O
SQL	O	O
code	O	O
by	O	O
IBM	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
project	O	O
eventually	O	O
was	O	O
terminated	O	O
but	O	O
Larry	B-PER	O
and	O	O
Bob	B-PER	O
decided	O	O
to	O	O
finish	O	O
what	O	O
they	O	O
started	O	O
and	O	O
bring	O	O
it	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
world	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
kept	O	O
the	O	O
name	O	O
Oracle	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
created	O	O
the	O	O
RDBMS	O	O
engine	O	O
.	O	O

Later	O	O
they	O	O
kept	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
name	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
company	O	O
.	O	O

Sony	B-ORG	O

It	O	O
originated	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
Latin	B-MISC	O
word	O	O
'	O	O
sonus	O	O
'	O	O
meaning	O	O
sound	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
'	O	O
sonny	O	O
'	O	O
a	O	O
slang	O	O
used	O	O
by	O	O
Americans	B-LOCderiv	O
to	O	O
refer	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
bright	O	O
youngster	O	O
.	O	O

SUN	B-ORG	O

Founded	O	O
by	O	O
4	O	O
Stanford	B-ORG	B-PER
University	I-ORG	O
buddies	O	O
,	O	O
SUN	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
acronym	O	O
for	O	O
Stanford	B-ORG	B-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

Andreas	B-PER	O
Bechtolsheim	I-PER	O
built	O	O
a	O	O
microcomputer	O	O
;	O	O
Vinod	B-PER	O
Khosla	I-PER	O
recruited	O	O
him	O	O
and	O	O
Scott	B-PER	O
McNealy	I-PER	O
to	O	O
manufacture	O	O
computers	O	O
based	O	O
on	O	O
it	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
recruited	O	O
Bill	B-PER	O
Joy	I-PER	O
to	O	O
develop	O	O
a	O	O
UNIX	O	O
-	O	O
based	O	O
OS	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
computer	O	O
.	O	O

Yahoo!	B-ORG	O

The	O	O
word	O	O
was	O	O
invented	O	O
by	O	O
Jonathan	B-PER	O
Swift	I-PER	O
and	O	O
used	O	O
in	O	O
his	O	O
book	O	O
'	O	O
Gulliver	B-MISC	B-PER
's	I-MISC	O
Travels	I-MISC	O
'	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
represents	O	O
a	O	O
person	O	O
who	O	O
is	O	O
repulsive	O	O
in	O	O
appearance	O	O
and	O	O
action	O	O
and	O	O
is	O	O
barely	O	O
human	O	O
.	O	O

Yahoo!	B-ORG	O
Founders	O	O
Jerry	B-PER	O
Yang	I-PER	O
and	O	O
David	B-PER	O
Filo	I-PER	O
selected	O	O
the	O	O
name	O	O
because	O	O
they	O	O
considered	O	O
themselves	O	O
yahoos	O	O
...	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
on	O	O
Yahoo	B-ORG	O
!	I-ORG	O

Email	O	O
:	O	O
mayur...@yahoo.com	B-PER	O
SMS	O	O
:	O	O
+	O	O
919819602175	O	O
Web	O	O
:	O	O

Hi	O	O
all	O	O
,	O	O

There	O	O
are	O	O
already	O	O
several	O	O
forums	O	O
around	O	O
the	O	O
net	O	O
focused	O	O
on	O	O
discussing	O	O
Guild	B-MISC	O
Wars	I-MISC	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
why	O	O
create	O	O
a	O	O
new	O	O
one	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
say	O	O
why	O	O
not	O	O
?	O	O

The	O	O
main	O	O
reason	O	O
is	O	O
Google	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
more	O	O
accessible	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
global	O	O
community	O	O
and	O	O
you	O	O
can	O	O
rest	O	O
assured	O	O
that	O	O
it	O	O
's	O	O
not	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
go	O	O
away	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
seen	O	O
great	O	O
fan	O	O
sites	O	O
suddenly	O	O
disappear	O	O
without	O	O
notice	O	O
and	O	O
for	O	O
no	O	O
reason	O	O
.	O	O

Usually	O	O
this	O	O
happens	O	O
because	O	O
the	O	O
developer	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
site	O	O
can	O	O
no	O	O
longer	O	O
afford	O	O
the	O	O
cost	O	O
of	O	O
bandwidth	O	O
being	O	O
used	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
said	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
maintenance	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
forum	O	O
is	O	O
handled	O	O
by	O	O
Google	B-ORG	O
and	O	O
thus	O	O
will	O	O
remain	O	O
reliable	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
will	O	O
ultimately	O	O
give	O	O
us	O	O
more	O	O
time	O	O
to	O	O
play	O	O
:)	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
'm	O	O
nothing	O	O
more	O	O
than	O	O
a	O	O
devoted	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
game	O	O
myself	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
hope	O	O
that	O	O
this	O	O
area	O	O
can	O	O
become	O	O
a	O	O
haven	O	O
for	O	O
deep	O	O
fan	O	O
discussions	O	O
.	O	O

Regards	O	O
,	O	O

Humanpixel	B-PER	O

Aye	O	O
!	O	O

Good	O	O
Day	O	O
Mate	O	O
!	O	O

I	O	O
m	O	O
really	O	O
looking	O	O
forward	O	O
to	O	O
Guild	B-MISC	O
Wars	I-MISC	O
.	O	O

Anyone	O	O
know	O	O
a	O	O
release	O	O
date	O	O
?	O	O

Feb	O	O
2005	O	O

Feb	O	O
2005	O	O
is	O	O
the	O	O
projected	O	O
release	O	O
date	O	O
,	O	O
although	O	O
Guild	B-MISC	O
Wars	I-MISC	O
is	O	O
made	O	O
by	O	O
ex-members	O	O
of	O	O
Blizzard	B-ORG	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
Feb	O	O
2005	O	O
could	O	O
mean	O	O
August	O	O
2006	O	O
...	O	O

Anyway	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
tried	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
preorder	O	O
but	O	O
no	O	O
places	O	O
were	O	O
selling	O	O
it	O	O
so	O	O
I	O	O
missed	O	O
out	O	O
on	O	O
2/3	O	O
weekend	O	O
events	O	O
.	O	O

Oh	O	O
well	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
'll	O	O
get	O	O
it	O	O
when	O	O
it	O	O
comes	O	O
out	O	O
in	O	O
Febuary	O	O
.	O	O

rumor	O	O
has	O	O
feb	O	O
05	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
calender	O	O
.	O	O

BUT	O	O
they	O	O
stated	O	O
that	O	O
they	O	O
will	O	O
take	O	O
as	O	O
long	O	O
as	O	O
it	O	O
takes	O	O
to	O	O
work	O	O
out	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
bugs	O	O
so	O	O
who	O	O
really	O	O
know	O	O
how	O	O
long	O	O
.	O	O

as	O	O
far	O	O
as	O	O
pre	O	O
order	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
list	O	O
of	O	O
major	O	O
retailers	O	O
that	O	O
carry	O	O
it	O	O
there	O	O
are	O	O
also	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
websites	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
could	O	O
order	O	O
it	O	O
off	O	O
of	O	O
.	O	O

and	O	O
a	O	O
good	O	O
reason	O	O
for	O	O
starting	O	O
this	O	O
group	O	O
....	O	O
company	O	O
firewalls	O	O
lol	O	O
;)	O	O

I	O	O
was	O	O
kind	O	O
of	O	O
curious	O	O
,	O	O
what	O	O
exactly	O	O
is	O	O
Guild	B-MISC	O
Wars	I-MISC	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
hav	O	O
n't	O	O
heard	O	O
of	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

Check	O	O
out	O	O
the	O	O
Guild	B-MISC	O
Wars	I-MISC	O
Web	O	O
site	O	O
at	O	O
for	O	O
more	O	O
info	O	O
about	O	O
the	O	O
game	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
a	O	O
massive	O	O
multiplayer	O	O
role	O	O
playing	O	O
game	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
graphics	O	O
are	O	O
without	O	O
a	O	O
doubt	O	O
the	O	O
amoung	O	O
the	O	O
best	O	O
graphics	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
ever	O	O
seen	O	O
for	O	O
any	O	O
game	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
gaming	O	O
since	O	O
the	O	O
MUD	O	O
days	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
worth	O	O
a	O	O
look	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
preorder	O	O
and	O	O
am	O	O
even	O	O
considering	O	O
getting	O	O
a	O	O
second	O	O
preorder	O	O
to	O	O
have	O	O
multiple	O	O
accounts	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
have	O	O
participated	O	O
in	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
weekend	O	O
beta	O	O
events	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
world	O	O
preview	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
game	O	O
is	O	O
already	O	O
100	O	O
%	O	O
functional	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
ca	O	O
n't	O	O
imagine	O	O
them	O	O
not	O	O
being	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
meet	O	O
the	O	O
Feb	O	O
05	O	O
deadline	O	O
.	O	O

Warm	O	O
greetings	O	O
to	O	O
all	O	O
in	O	O
this	O	O
GW	B-MISC	O
community	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
Lady	O	O
Kingel	B-PER	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
hail	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-ORG	O
Legit	I-ORG	O
Gaming	I-ORG	O
Guilds	I-ORG	O
of	O	O
Guild	B-MISC	O
Wars	I-MISC	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
a	O	O
consortium	O	O
of	O	O
legit	O	O
honorable	O	O
guilds	O	O
that	O	O
was	O	O
established	O	O
in	O	O
1997	O	O
for	O	O
DI	B-MISC	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
now	O	O
adding	O	O
GW	B-MISC	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
list	O	O
of	O	O
games	O	O
played	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
alliance	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
pretty	O	O
straightforward	O	O
one	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
formed	O	O
to	O	O
allow	O	O
many	O	O
different	O	O
guilds	O	O
who	O	O
were	O	O
all	O	O
strictly	O	O
honorable	O	O
to	O	O
come	O	O
together	O	O
as	O	O
a	O	O
family	O	O
and	O	O
allow	O	O
them	O	O
many	O	O
people	O	O
to	O	O
game	O	O
with	O	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
are	O	O
no	O	O
other	O	O
requirements	O	O
other	O	O
than	O	O
we	O	O
ask	O	O
that	O	O
members	O	O
greet	O	O
each	O	O
new	O	O
member	O	O
and	O	O
each	O	O
new	O	O
alliance	O	O
and	O	O
also	O	O
feel	O	O
free	O	O
to	O	O
post	O	O
in	O	O
any	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
forums	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
also	O	O
a	O	O
group	O	O
who	O	O
is	O	O
looking	O	O
for	O	O
members	O	O
for	O	O
our	O	O
own	O	O
select	O	O
guild	O	O
called	O	O
ULGG	B-ORG	O
of	O	O
GW	B-MISC	O
...	O	O
which	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
part	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
alliance	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
name	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
play	O	O
in	O	O
all	O	O
aspects	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
game	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
hand	O	O
pick	O	O
our	O	O
members	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
personally	O	O
invite	O	O
each	O	O
of	O	O
you	O	O
to	O	O
visit	O	O
our	O	O
website	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
are	O	O
individuals	O	O
of	O	O
quality	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
in	O	O
our	O	O
alliance	O	O
we	O	O
seek	O	O
quality	O	O
of	O	O
member	O	O
over	O	O
quantity	O	O
of	O	O
member	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
asked	O	O
to	O	O
register	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
then	O	O
you	O	O
should	O	O
wander	O	O
over	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
Announce	B-MISC	O
Your	I-MISC	O
Arrival	I-MISC	O
Section	I-MISC	O
and	O	O
present	O	O
yourself	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
greeted	O	O
by	O	O
many	O	O
members	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
wonderful	O	O
family	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
do	O	O
hope	O	O
to	O	O
see	O	O
you	O	O
visiting	O	O
us	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
fire	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
shall	O	O
prepare	O	O
a	O	O
feast	O	O
for	O	O
you	O	O
,	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
paste	O	O
this	O	O
in	O	O
your	O	O
browser	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
will	O	O
take	O	O
you	O	O
directly	O	O
to	O	O
our	O	O
GW	B-MISC	O
website	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
extend	O	O
my	O	O
hand	O	O
to	O	O
each	O	O
of	O	O
you	O	O
in	O	O
true	O	O
friendship	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
honor	O	O
.	O	O

Come	O	O
and	O	O
say	O	O
hello	O	O
...	O	O
you	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
warmly	O	O
welcomed	O	O
!	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
currently	O	O
moving	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
new	O	O
server	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
we	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
down	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
while	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
inform	O	O
when	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
up	O	O
and	O	O
running	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
wish	O	O
all	O	O
happy	O	O
holidays	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
moreso	O	O
,	O	O
wish	O	O
peace	O	O
on	O	O
earth	O	O
.	O	O

Kingel	B-PER	O

Dear	O	O
Judges	O	O
,	O	O
Lawyers	O	O
,	O	O
Policemen	O	O
,	O	O
Guards	O	O
,	O	O
Counselors	O	O
,	O	O
Taxpayers	O	O
,	O	O
et.	O	O
al.	O	O
,	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
here	O	O
.	O	O

Like	O	O
it	O	O
or	O	O
not	O	O
,	O	O
for	O	O
good	O	O
or	O	O
bad	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
here	O	O
.	O	O

Who	O	O
are	O	O
we	O	O
?	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
downtrodden	O	O
and	O	O
dispossesed	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
self	O	O
-	O	O
torturing	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
disenfranchised	O	O
convicts	O	O
,	O	O
drug	O	O
and	O	O
alcohol	O	O
addicts	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
unemployed	O	O
and	O	O
unemployable	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
children	O	O
of	O	O
poverty	O	O
,	O	O
financial	O	O
and	O	O
spiritual	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
have	O	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
have	O	O
children	O	O
of	O	O
our	O	O
own	O	O
,	O	O
grandchildren	O	O
too	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
ex-cons	O	O
,	O	O
uninsured	O	O
,	O	O
homeless	O	O
,	O	O
of	O	O
many	O	O
colors	O	O
and	O	O
speaking	O	O
many	O	O
tongues	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
are	O	O
the	O	O
enemy	O	O
in	O	O
what	O	O
has	O	O
become	O	O
a	O	O
domestic	O	O
war	O	O
against	O	O
ourselves	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
who	O	O
are	O	O
you	O	O
?	O	O

You	O	O
who	O	O
like	O	O
the	O	O
tough	O	O
talk	O	O
of	O	O
Tough	B-MISC	O
on	I-MISC	O
Crime	I-MISC	O
?	O	O

You	O	O
who	O	O
watch	O	O
as	O	O
budgets	O	O
are	O	O
cut	O	O
in	O	O
education	O	O
and	O	O
health	O	O
care	O	O
while	O	O
you	O	O
militarize	O	O
a	O	O
police	O	O
force	O	O
?	O	O

Bullet	O	O
-	O	O
proof	O	O
vests	O	O
,	O	O
automatic	O	O
weapons	O	O
,	O	O
helicopters	O	O
,	O	O
tanks	O	O
,	O	O
robots	O	O
...	O	O
the	O	O
testosterone	O	O
is	O	O
oozing	O	O
through	O	O
the	O	O
streets	O	O
,	O	O
more	O	O
prisons	O	O
,	O	O
longer	O	O
sentences	O	O
,	O	O
tighten	O	O
the	O	O
belt	O	O
,	O	O
spartan	O	O
conditions	O	O
,	O	O
task	O	O
forces	O	O
,	O	O
gang	O	O
units	O	O
,	O	O
gun	O	O
courts	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
what	O	O
is	O	O
there	O	O
to	O	O
show	O	O
for	O	O
it	O	O
?	O	O

Unemployent	O	O
stays	O	O
low	O	O
because	O	O
half	O	O
the	O	O
population	O	O
oversees	O	O
those	O	O
"	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
workforce	O	O
"	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
dregs	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
rabble	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
enemy	O	O
?	O	O

Please	O	O
tell	O	O
me	O	O
there	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
deeper	O	O
reason	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
you	O	O
feel	O	O
safer	O	O
?	O	O

More	O	O
humane	O	O
?	O	O

More	O	O
like	O	O
a	O	O
cohesive	O	O
society	O	O
with	O	O
a	O	O
shared	O	O
sense	O	O
of	O	O
purpose	O	O
,	O	O
who	O	O
can	O	O
identify	O	O
Us	O	O
and	O	O
Them	O	O
?	O	O

Do	O	O
you	O	O
live	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
gated	O	O
community	O	O
or	O	O
gentrified	O	O
neighborhood	O	O
?	O	O

By	O	O
the	O	O
way	O	O
,	O	O
have	O	O
you	O	O
read	O	O
the	O	O
Declaration	B-MISC	O
of	I-MISC	O
Independence	I-MISC	O
and	O	O
US	B-MISC	B-LOCderiv
Constitution	I-MISC	O
-	O	O
or	O	O
do	O	O
you	O	O
only	O	O
know	O	O
the	O	O
first	O	O
phrases	O	O
?	O	O

It	O	O
's	O	O
about	O	O
time	O	O
we	O	O
got	O	O
together	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
yet	O	O
to	O	O
meet	O	O
a	O	O
convict	O	O
who	O	O
wants	O	O
their	O	O
child	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
thief	O	O
,	O	O
an	O	O
addict	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
dealer	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
prostitute	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
a	O	O
violent	O	O
individual	O	O
.	O	O

Most	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
still	O	O
have	O	O
hope	O	O
for	O	O
ourselves	O	O
even	O	O
when	O	O
stuck	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
darkest	O	O
dilemmas	O	O
,	O	O
ruts	O	O
and	O	O
catch	O	O
-	O	O
22s	O	O
.	O	O

Most	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
believe	O	O
in	O	O
crafting	O	O
laws	O	O
and	O	O
instilling	O	O
order	O	O
.	O	O

Many	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
have	O	O
burrowed	O	O
beneath	O	O
the	O	O
surface	O	O
to	O	O
find	O	O
a	O	O
spiritual	O	O
sense	O	O
of	O	O
being	O	O
,	O	O
an	O	O
understanding	O	O
force	O	O
at	O	O
least	O	O
as	O	O
powerful	O	O
as	O	O
those	O	O
we	O	O
succumbed	O	O
to	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
many	O	O
of	O	O
use	O	O
would	O	O
n't	O	O
escape	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
opened	O	O
the	O	O
front	O	O
door	O	O
.	O	O

Did	O	O
you	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
approximately	O	O
10	O	O
million	O	O
Americans	B-LOCderiv	O
are	O	O
either	O	O
incarcerated	O	O
,	O	O
on	O	O
probation	O	O
,	O	O
on	O	O
parole	O	O
or	O	O
once	O	O
were	O	O
in	O	O
those	O	O
categories	O	O
?	O	O

Each	O	O
of	O	O
those	O	O
10	O	O
million	O	O
have	O	O
families	O	O
,	O	O
friends	O	O
,	O	O
neighbors	O	O
...	O	O
and	O	O
so	O	O
closer	O	O
and	O	O
closer	O	O
does	O	O
the	O	O
We	O	O
interface	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
You	O	O
.	O	O

Do	O	O
n't	O	O
you	O	O
think	O	O
it	O	O
's	O	O
time	O	O
we	O	O
talked	O	O
?	O	O

Are	O	O
you	O	O
ready	O	O
?	O	O

Can	O	O
you	O	O
accept	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
road	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
travelling	O	O
points	O	O
toward	O	O
a	O	O
grim	O	O
and	O	O
painful	O	O
future	O	O
?	O	O

Do	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
the	O	O
heart	O	O
to	O	O
face	O	O
monumental	O	O
failures	O	O
while	O	O
bravely	O	O
struggling	O	O
beyond	O	O
where	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
now	O	O
?	O	O

I	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
some	O	O
of	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
that	O	O
some	O	O
of	O	O
us	O	O
are	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
what	O	O
gives	O	O
me	O	O
hope	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
need	O	O
our	O	O
insights	O	O
just	O	O
as	O	O
we	O	O
need	O	O
your	O	O
structure	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
never	O	O
over	O	O
,	O	O
especially	O	O
when	O	O
a	O	O
real	O	O
solution	O	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
real	O	O
treatment	O	O
for	O	O
our	O	O
sickness	O	O
,	O	O
is	O	O
yet	O	O
to	O	O
begin	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
Solidarity	O	O
,	O	O

Bruce	B-PER	O
Reilly	I-PER	O
(	O	O
a.k.a	O	O
Bruha	B-PER	O
)	O	O
P.O.	O	O
Box	O	O
8274	O	O
Cranston	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
RI	B-LOC	O
02920	O	O
USA	B-LOC	O

P.S.	O	O
-	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
conceptualize	O	O
an	O	O
effective	O	O
guerilla	O	O
media	O	O
campaign	O	O
to	O	O
promote	O	O
this	O	O
cause	O	O
.	O	O

Ideas	O	O
are	O	O
welcome	O	O
.	O	O

Collaboration	O	O
is	O	O
prayed	O	O
.	O	O

an	O	O
annotated	O	O
text	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
bill	O	O
,	O	O
read	O	O
the	O	O
article	O	O
by	O	O
D.	O	O
Singmaster	B-PER	O
in	O	O
"	O	O
The	B-MISC	O
Mathematical	I-MISC	O
Intelligencer	I-MISC	O
"	O	O
v	O	O
7	O	O
#	O	O
2	O	O
,	O	O
pp	O	O
69	O	O
-	O	O
72	O	O
.	O	O

---------------------------------------------------------------------------	O	O
-----	O	O

Subject	O	O
:	O	O
Where	O	O
can	O	O
I	O	O
get	O	O
the	O	O
necessary	O	O
software	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
a	O	O
"	O	O
smart	O	O
"	O	O
mail	O	O
system	O	O
running	O	O
on	O	O
my	O	O
machine	O	O
that	O	O
will	O	O
take	O	O
advantage	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
postings	O	O
in	O	O
comp.mail.maps	B-MISC	O
?	O	O
(	O	O
E.g.	O	O
,	O	O
pathalias	O	O
,	O	O
smail	O	O
,	O	O
etc.	O	O
)	O	O

There	O	O
are	O	O
a	O	O
couple	O	O
of	O	O
packages	O	O
available	O	O
through	O	O
the	O	O
supporters	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
comp.sources.unix	B-MISC	O
archives	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
sites	O	O
next	O	O
to	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
have	O	O
what	O	O
you	O	O
want	O	O
,	O	O
contact	O	O
your	O	O
nearest	O	O
comp.sources.unix	B-MISC	O
archive	O	O
,	O	O
or	O	O
the	O	O
moderator	O	O
.	O	O

Information	O	O
on	O	O
archive	O	O
sites	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
indices	O	O
of	O	O
comp.sources.unix	B-MISC	O
back	O	O
issues	O	O
are	O	O
posted	O	O
regularly	O	O
in	O	O
comp.sources.unix	B-MISC	O
and	O	O
comp.sources.d	B-MISC	O
.	O	O

---------------------------------------------------------------------------	O	O
-----	O	O

Subject	O	O
:	O	O
What	O	O
is	O	O
"	O	O
food	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
NSA	B-ORG	O
line	O	O
-	O	O
eater	O	O
"	O	O
?	O	O

This	O	O
refers	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
alleged	O	O
scanning	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
Usenet	B-MISC	O
traffic	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
National	B-ORG	O
Security	I-ORG	O
Agency	I-ORG	O
(	O	O
and	O	O
possibly	O	O
other	O	O
intelligence	O	O
organizations	O	O
)	O	O
for	O	O
interesting	O	O
keywords	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
"	O	O
food	O	O
"	O	O
is	O	O
believed	O	O
to	O	O
contain	O	O
some	O	O
of	O	O
those	O	O

Email	O	O
:	O	O
"	O	O
Peanutjake	B-PER	O
"	O	O
<	O	O
peanutjak...@usa.com	B-PER	O
>	O	O

Groups	O	O
:	O	O
misc.consumers	B-MISC	O

Subject	O	O
:	O	O
IMMEDIATE	O	O
ATTENTION	O	O
NEEDED	O	O
:	O	O

HIGHLY	O	O
CONFIDENTIAL	O	O
URGENT	O	O
ASSISTANCE	O	O
-	O	O
FROM	O	O
USA	B-LOC	O

FROM	O	O
:	O	O
GEORGE	B-PER	O
WALKER	I-PER	O
BUSH	I-PER	O
202.456.1414	O	O
/	O	O
202.456.1111	O	O
FAX	O	O
:	O	O
202.456.2461	O	O

Dear	O	O
Sir	O	O
/	O	O
Madam	O	O
,	O	O

This	O	O
letter	O	O
might	O	O
surprise	O	O
you	O	O
because	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
not	O	O
met	O	O
neither	O	O
in	O	O
person	O	O
nor	O	O
by	O	O
correspondence	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
came	O	O
to	O	O
know	O	O
of	O	O
you	O	O
in	O	O
my	O	O
search	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
reliable	O	O
and	O	O
reputable	O	O
person	O	O
to	O	O
handle	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
confidential	O	O
business	O	O
transaction	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
involves	O	O
the	O	O
transfer	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
huge	O	O
sum	O	O
of	O	O
money	O	O
to	O	O
an	O	O
account	O	O
requiring	O	O
maximum	O	O
confidence	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
writing	O	O
you	O	O
in	O	O
absolute	O	O
confidence	O	O
primarily	O	O
to	O	O
seek	O	O
your	O	O
assistance	O	O
in	O	O
acquiring	O	O
oil	O	O
funds	O	O
that	O	O
are	O	O
presently	O	O
trapped	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
republic	B-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
Iraq	I-LOC	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
partners	O	O
and	O	O
I	O	O
solicit	O	O
your	O	O
assistance	O	O
in	O	O
completing	O	O
a	O	O
transaction	O	O
begun	O	O
by	O	O
my	O	O
father	O	O
,	O	O
who	O	O
has	O	O
long	O	O
been	O	O
actively	O	O
engaged	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
extraction	O	O
of	O	O
petroleum	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-LOC	O
States	I-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
America	I-LOC	B-LOC
,	O	O
and	O	O
bravely	O	O
served	O	O
his	O	O
country	O	O
as	O	O
director	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-ORG	B-LOCderiv
States	I-ORG	I-LOCderiv
Central	I-ORG	O
Intelligence	I-ORG	O
Agency	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
the	O	O
decade	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
nineteen	O	O
-	O	O
eighties	O	O
,	O	O
my	O	O
father	O	O
,	O	O
then	O	O
vice	O	O
-	O	O
president	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-LOC	O
States	I-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
America	I-LOC	B-LOC
,	O	O
sought	O	O
to	O	O
work	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
good	O	O
offices	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
President	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Republic	B-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
Iraq	I-LOC	O
to	O	O
regain	O	O
lost	O	O
oil	O	O
revenue	O	O
sources	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
neighboring	O	O
Islamic	B-LOC	O
republic	I-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
Iran	I-LOC	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
unsuccessful	O	O
venture	O	O
was	O	O
soon	O	O
followed	O	O
by	O	O
a	O	O
falling	O	O
-	O	O
out	O	O
with	O	O
his	O	O
Iraqi	B-LOCderiv	O
partner	O	O
,	O	O
who	O	O
sought	O	O
to	O	O
acquire	O	O
additional	O	O
oil	O	O
revenue	O	O
sources	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
neighboring	O	O
emirate	B-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
Kuwait	I-LOC	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
wholly	O	O
-	O	O
owned	O	O
U.S.	B-LOCpart	B-LOCderiv
-	I-LOCpart	I-LOCderiv
British	I-LOCpart	I-LOCderiv
subsidiary	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
father	O	O
re-secured	O	O
the	O	O
petroleum	O	O
assets	O	O
of	O	O
Kuwait	B-LOC	O
in	O	O
1991	O	O
at	O	O
a	O	O
cost	O	O
of	O	O
sixty	O	O
-	O	O
one	O	O
billion	O	O
U.S.	B-MISC	B-LOCderiv
dollars	I-MISC	O
(	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
61,000,000,000	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Out	O	O
of	O	O
that	O	O
cost	O	O
,	O	O
thirty	O	O
-	O	O
six	O	O
billion	O	O
dollars	B-MISC	O
(	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
36,000,000,000	O	O
)	O	O
were	O	O
supplied	O	O
by	O	O
King	O	O
Hussein	B-PER	O
,	O	O
Kingdom	B-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
Saudi	I-LOC	O
Arabia	I-LOC	O
and	O	O
other	O	O
Persian	B-LOC	B-LOCderiv
Gulf	I-LOC	O
monarchies	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
sixteen	O	O
billion	O	O
dollars	B-MISC	O
(	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
16,000,000,000	O	O
)	O	O
supplied	O	O
by	O	O
German	B-LOCderiv	O
and	O	O
Japanese	B-LOCderiv	O
partners	O	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
my	O	O
father	O	O
's	O	O
former	O	O
Iraqi	B-LOCderiv	O
business	O	O
partner	O	O
remained	O	O
in	O	O
control	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
republic	B-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
Iraq	I-LOC	O
and	O	O
its	O	O
petroleum	O	O
reserves	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
family	O	O
is	O	O
calling	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
urgent	O	O
assistance	O	O
in	O	O
funding	O	O
the	O	O
removal	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
President	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Republic	B-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
Iraq	I-LOC	O
and	O	O
acquiring	O	O
the	O	O
petroleum	O	O
assets	O	O
of	O	O
his	O	O
country	O	O
,	O	O
as	O	O
compensation	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
costs	O	O
of	O	O
removing	O	O
him	O	O
from	O	O
power	O	O
.	O	O

Unfortunately	O	O
,	O	O
our	O	O
partners	O	O
from	O	O
1991	O	O
are	O	O
not	O	O
willing	O	O
to	O	O
shoulder	O	O
the	O	O
burden	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
new	O	O
venture	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
in	O	O
its	O	O
upcoming	O	O
phase	O	O
may	O	O
cost	O	O
the	O	O
sum	O	O
of	O	O
100	O	O
billion	O	O
to	O	O
200	O	O
billion	O	O
dollars	B-MISC	O
(	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
100,000,000,000	O	O
-	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
200,000,000,000	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
both	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
initial	O	O
acquisition	O	O
and	O	O
in	O	O
long	O	O
-	O	O
term	O	O
management	O	O
.	O	O

Without	O	O
the	O	O
funds	O	O
from	O	O
our	O	O
1991	O	O
partners	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
would	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
able	O	O
to	O	O
acquire	O	O
the	O	O
oil	O	O
revenue	O	O
trapped	O	O
within	O	O
Iraq	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
is	O	O
why	O	O
my	O	O
family	O	O
and	O	O
our	O	O
colleagues	O	O
are	O	O
urgently	O	O
seeking	O	O
your	O	O
gracious	O	O
assistance	O	O
.	O	O

Our	O	O
distinguished	O	O
colleagues	O	O
in	O	O
this	O	O
business	O	O
transaction	O	O
include	O	O
the	O	O
sitting	O	O
vice-president	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-LOC	O
States	I-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
America	I-LOC	B-LOC
,	O	O
Richard	B-PER	O
Cheney	I-PER	O
,	O	O
who	O	O
is	O	O
an	O	O
original	O	O
partner	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
Iraq	B-LOC	O
venture	O	O
and	O	O
former	O	O
head	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Halliburton	B-ORG	B-PER
oil	O	O
company	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
Condoleeza	B-PER	O
Rice	I-PER	O
,	O	O
whose	O	O
professional	O	O
dedication	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
venture	O	O
was	O	O
demonstrated	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
naming	O	O
of	O	O
a	O	O
Chevron	B-ORG	O
oil	O	O
tanker	O	O
after	O	O
her	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
would	O	O
beseech	O	O
you	O	O
to	O	O
transfer	O	O
a	O	O
sum	O	O
equaling	O	O
ten	O	O
to	O	O
twenty	O	O
-	O	O
five	O	O
percent	O	O
(	O	O
10	O	O
-	O	O
25	O	O
%	O	O
)	O	O
of	O	O
your	O	O
yearly	O	O
income	O	O
to	O	O
our	O	O
account	O	O
to	O	O
aid	O	O
in	O	O
this	O	O
important	O	O
venture	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
Internal	B-ORG	O
Revenue	I-ORG	O
Service	I-ORG	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-ORG	B-LOC
States	I-ORG	I-LOC
of	I-ORG	I-LOC
America	I-ORG	I-LOC
will	O	O
function	O	O
as	O	O
our	O	O
trusted	O	O
intermediary	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
propose	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
make	O	O
this	O	O
transfer	O	O
before	O	O
the	O	O
fifteenth	O	O
(	O	O
15th	O	O
)	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
month	O	O
of	O	O
April	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
know	O	O
that	O	O
a	O	O
transaction	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
magnitude	O	O
would	O	O
make	O	O
anyone	O	O
apprehensive	O	O
and	O	O
worried	O	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
I	O	O
am	O	O
assuring	O	O
you	O	O
that	O	O
all	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
well	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
end	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
day	O	O
.	O	O

A	O	O
bold	O	O
step	O	O
taken	O	O
shall	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
regretted	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
assure	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
do	O	O
be	O	O
informed	O	O
that	O	O
this	O	O
business	O	O
transaction	O	O
is	O	O
100	O	O
%	O	O
legal	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
not	O	O
wish	O	O
to	O	O
co-operate	O	O
in	O	O
this	O	O
transaction	O	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
contact	O	O
our	O	O
intermediary	O	O
representatives	O	O
to	O	O
further	O	O
discuss	O	O
the	O	O
matter	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
pray	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
understand	O	O
our	O	O
plight	O	O
.	O	O

My	O	O
family	O	O
and	O	O
our	O	O
colleagues	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
forever	O	O
grateful	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
reply	O	O
in	O	O
strict	O	O
confidence	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
contact	O	O
numbers	O	O
below	O	O
.	O	O

Sincerely	O	O
with	O	O
warm	O	O
regards	O	O
,	O	O

George	B-PER	O
Walker	I-PER	O
Bush	I-PER	O
Switchboard	O	O
:	O	O
202.456.1414	O	O
Comments	O	O
:	O	O
202.456.1111	O	O
Fax	O	O
:	O	O
202.456.2461	O	O
e-mail	O	O
:	O	O
presid...@whitehouse.gov	B-PER	O

US	B-LOCderiv	O
battles	O	O
to	O	O
save	O	O
storm	O	O
victims	O	O

Watch	O	O
the	O	O
airlift	O	O

Emergency	O	O
teams	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
southern	O	O
US	B-LOC	O
are	O	O
battling	O	O
to	O	O
reach	O	O
survivors	O	O
of	O	O
Hurricane	B-MISC	O
Katrina	I-MISC	B-PER
,	O	O
the	O	O
most	O	O
destructive	O	O
storm	O	O
to	O	O
hit	O	O
the	O	O
country	O	O
in	O	O
decades	O	O
.	O	O

Hundreds	O	O
of	O	O
people	O	O
are	O	O
feared	O	O
dead	O	O
in	O	O
Mississippi	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
Louisiana	B-LOC	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	O
Orleans	I-LOC	O
is	O	O
badly	O	O
flooded	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
city	O	O
mayor	O	O
said	O	O
rescuers	O	O
were	O	O
unable	O	O
to	O	O
retrieve	O	O
the	O	O
dead	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
They	O	O
're	O	O
just	O	O
pushing	O	O
them	O	O
aside	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
he	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

Amid	O	O
worsening	O	O
conditions	O	O
,	O	O
officials	O	O
plan	O	O
to	O	O
evacuate	O	O
a	O	O
New	B-LOCderiv	O
Orleans	I-LOCderiv	O
stadium	O	O
where	O	O
up	O	O
to	O	O
20,000	O	O
people	O	O
took	O	O
shelter	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
Superdome	B-LOC	O
stadium	I-LOC	O
is	O	O
without	O	O
power	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
toilets	O	O
are	O	O
overflowing	O	O
.	O	O

Map	O	O
of	O	O
central	O	O
New	B-LOC	O
Orleans	I-LOC	O

"	O	O
It	O	O
's	O	O
a	O	O
very	O	O
,	O	O
very	O	O
desperate	O	O
situation	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
Louisiana	B-LOC	O
Governor	O	O
Kathleen	B-PER	O
Blanco	I-PER	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

[	O	O
an	O	O
error	O	O
occurred	O	O
while	O	O
processing	O	O
this	O	O
directive	O	O
]	O	O

One	O	O
resident	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	O
Orleans	I-LOC	O
said	O	O
escaping	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
storm	O	O
was	O	O
"	O	O
hell	O	O
"	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
We	O	O
were	O	O
screaming	O	O
,	O	O
hollering	O	O
,	O	O
flashing	O	O
lights	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
was	O	O
complete	O	O
chaos	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
Kioka	B-PER	O
Williams	I-PER	O
told	O	O
the	O	O
Associated	B-ORG	O
Press	I-ORG	O
news	O	O
agency	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
had	O	O
to	O	O
hack	O	O
her	O	O
way	O	O
through	O	O
the	O	O
ceiling	O	O
of	O	O
her	O	O
beauty	O	O
shop	O	O
as	O	O
flood	O	O
waters	O	O
rose	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
half	O	O
a	O	O
million	O	O
people	O	O
-	O	O
much	O	O
of	O	O
which	O	O
lies	O	O
below	O	O
sea	O	O
level	O	O
.	O	O

Flooding	O	O

Walls	O	O
keeping	O	O
water	O	O
out	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
bowl	O	O
-	O	O
shaped	O	O
city	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
breached	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
emergency	O	O
teams	O	O
are	O	O
using	O	O
helicopters	O	O
to	O	O
drop	O	O
1,350	O	O
kg	O	O
(	O	O
3,000	O	O
lb	O	O
)	O	O
sandbags	O	O
and	O	O
concrete	O	O
barriers	O	O
into	O	O
the	O	O
gaps	O	O
.	O	O

Before	O	O
the	O	O
phones	O	O
went	O	O
,	O	O
I	O	O
was	O	O
told	O	O
[	O	O
my	O	O
family	O	O
in	O	O
Biloxi	B-LOC	O
]	O	O
had	O	O
lost	O	O
their	O	O
roof	O	O
,	O	O
barn	O	O
,	O	O
2	O	O
oak	O	O
trees	O	O
and	O	O
many	O	O
pines	O	O
and	O	O
they	O	O
were	O	O
letting	O	O
in	O	O
water	O	O

Natalie	B-PER	O
McVeigh	I-PER	O
Oakley	I-PER	O
,	O	O
England	B-LOC	O

Your	O	O
Katrina	B-MISC	B-PER
experiences	O	O

Blogging	O	O
Katrina	B-MISC	B-PER

New	B-LOC	O
Orleans	I-LOC	O
mayor	O	O
Ray	B-PER	O
Nagin	I-PER	O
said	O	O
up	O	O
to	O	O
80	O	O
%	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
was	O	O
submerged	O	O
,	O	O
in	O	O
some	O	O
cases	O	O
by	O	O
waters	O	O
6	O	O
m	O	O
(	O	O
20	O	O
ft	O	O
)	O	O
deep	O	O
.	O	O

He	O	O
warned	O	O
water	O	O
levels	O	O
could	O	O
still	O	O
rise	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
Some	O	O
sections	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
which	O	O
are	O	O
dry	O	O
now	O	O
could	O	O
see	O	O
nine	O	O
or	O	O
10	O	O
feet	O	O
(	O	O
some	O	O
3	O	O
m	O	O
)	O	O
of	O	O
water	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
he	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
US	B-ORG	B-ORG
Army	I-ORG	I-ORG
Corps	I-ORG	O
of	I-ORG	O
Engineers	I-ORG	O
says	O	O
it	O	O
could	O	O
take	O	O
a	O	O
month	O	O
to	O	O
clear	O	O
the	O	O
flood	O	O
waters	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
government	O	O
's	O	O
disaster	O	O
relief	O	O
agency	O	O
has	O	O
urged	O	O
evacuees	O	O
not	O	O
to	O	O
try	O	O
to	O	O
get	O	O
back	O	O
to	O	O
their	O	O
homes	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
BBC	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
Alastair	B-PER	O
Leithead	I-PER	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	O
Orleans	I-LOC	O
says	O	O
there	O	O
is	O	O
panic	O	O
as	O	O
vital	O	O
supplies	O	O
run	O	O
out	O	O
.	O	O

Heavily	O	O
armed	O	O
police	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
impose	O	O
a	O	O
form	O	O
of	O	O
martial	O	O
law	O	O
to	O	O
stem	O	O
outbreaks	O	O
of	O	O
looting	O	O
.	O	O

While	O	O
some	O	O
looters	O	O
are	O	O
stealing	O	O
non-essential	O	O
goods	O	O
,	O	O
others	O	O
are	O	O
simply	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
find	O	O
food	O	O
and	O	O
water	O	O
.	O	O

'	O	O
Hundreds	O	O
dead	O	O
'	O	O

The	O	O
situation	O	O
appears	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
even	O	O
worse	O	O
in	O	O
Mississippi	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
You	O	O
're	O	O
going	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
looking	O	O
at	O	O
hundreds	O	O
dead	O	O
along	O	O
the	O	O
coast	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
a	O	O
state	O	O
official	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

[	O	O
an	O	O
error	O	O
occurred	O	O
while	O	O
processing	O	O
this	O	O
directive	O	O
]	O	O

Casinos	O	O
housed	O	O
in	O	O
barges	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
hurled	O	O
onto	O	O
the	O	O
beach	O	O
and	O	O
beyond	O	O
.	O	O

Tens	O	O
of	O	O
thousands	O	O
are	O	O
homeless	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
officials	O	O
say	O	O
it	O	O
could	O	O
be	O	O
weeks	O	O
before	O	O
power	O	O
is	O	O
restored	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
only	O	O
imagine	O	O
that	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
what	O	O
Hiroshima	B-LOC	O
looked	O	O
like	O	O
60	O	O
years	O	O
ago	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
said	O	O
Mississippi	B-LOC	O
Governor	O	O
Haley	B-PER	O
Barbour	I-PER	O
after	O	O
viewing	O	O
the	O	O
destruction	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
air	O	O
.	O	O

Survivors	O	O
are	O	O
being	O	O
found	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
time	O	O
,	O	O
including	O	O
two	O	O
children	O	O
who	O	O
lost	O	O
their	O	O
parents	O	O
.	O	O

Harrison	B-LOC	O
County	I-LOC	O
in	O	O
Mississippi	B-LOC	O
bore	O	O
the	O	O
brunt	O	O
of	O	O
Hurricane	B-MISC	O
Katrina	I-MISC	B-PER
as	O	O
it	O	O
slammed	O	O
into	O	O
Biloxi	B-LOC	O
and	O	O
Gulfport	B-LOC	O
before	O	O
heading	O	O
inland	O	O
.	O	O

Mississippi	B-LOC	O
media	O	O
earlier	O	O
reported	O	O
54	O	O
people	O	O
killed	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
state	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
Biloxi	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
30	O	O
people	O	O
were	O	O
reported	O	O
dead	O	O
in	O	O
one	O	O
block	O	O
of	O	O
flats	O	O
which	O	O
was	O	O
hit	O	O
by	O	O
a	O	O
9	O	O
m	O	O
(	O	O
30	O	O
ft	O	O
)	O	O
"	O	O
storm	O	O
surge	O	O
"	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
town	O	O
's	O	O
death	O	O
toll	O	O
may	O	O
be	O	O
"	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
hundreds	O	O
"	O	O
,	O	O
municipal	O	O
spokesman	O	O
Vincent	B-PER	O
Creel	I-PER	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

Mobilising	O	O

Louisiana	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
Governor	O	O
Blanco	B-PER	O
urged	O	O
residents	O	O
to	O	O
spend	O	O
Wednesday	O	O
in	O	O
prayer	O	O
and	O	O
assured	O	O
them	O	O
the	O	O
crisis	O	O
would	O	O
eventually	O	O
be	O	O
overcome	O	O
.	O	O

Follow	O	O
Katrina	B-MISC	B-PER
's	I-MISC	I-PER
path	O	O

The	O	O
US	B-ORG	B-LOCderiv
Red	I-ORG	O
Cross	I-ORG	O
has	O	O
mobilised	O	O
thousands	O	O
of	O	O
volunteers	O	O
for	O	O
its	O	O
biggest	O	O
-	O	O
ever	O	O
natural	O	O
disaster	O	O
effort	O	O
and	O	O
federal	O	O
emergency	O	O
teams	O	O
are	O	O
being	O	O
dispatched	O	O
to	O	O
affected	O	O
areas	O	O
.	O	O

President	O	O
George	B-PER	O
W	I-PER	O
Bush	I-PER	O
,	O	O
who	O	O
has	O	O
cut	O	O
his	O	O
holiday	O	O
two	O	O
days	O	O
short	O	O
,	O	O
has	O	O
called	O	O
on	O	O
Americans	B-LOCderiv	O
to	O	O
donate	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
Red	B-ORG	O
Cross	I-ORG	O
or	O	O
other	O	O
organisations	O	O
.	O	O

Damage	O	O
estimates	O	O
of	O	O
more	O	O
than	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
25	O	O
bn	O	O
suggest	O	O
it	O	O
could	O	O
be	O	O
the	O	O
US	B-LOCderiv	O
insurance	O	O
industry	O	O
's	O	O
most	O	O
expensive	O	O
natural	O	O
disaster	O	O
ever	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
price	O	O
of	O	O
crude	O	O
oil	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
international	O	O
market	O	O
hit	O	O
a	O	O
record	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
70.85	O	O
a	O	O
barrel	O	O
due	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
vulnerability	O	O
of	O	O
oil	O	O
and	O	O
gas	O	O
fields	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
Gulf	B-LOC	O
of	I-LOC	O
Mexico	I-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
US	B-LOCderiv	O
energy	O	O
secretary	O	O
has	O	O
announced	O	O
that	O	O
oil	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
released	O	O
from	O	O
government	O	O
petroleum	O	O
reserves	O	O
.	O	O

Return	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
top	O	O

MOON	B-LOC	O
LANDING	O	O
HOAX	O	O
:	O	O
CHURCH	O	O
=	O	O
TECHNOLOGY	O	O
&	O	O
GOVERNMENT	O	O
-	O	O
Shuttle	O	O
Carried	O	O
on	O	O
Aircraft	O	O
model	O	O

Q	O	O
:	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
IS	O	O
A	O	O
WASTE	O	O
!	O	O

(	O	O
Answered	O	O
,	O	O
2	O	O
Comments	O	O
)	O	O

Question	O	O

Subject	O	O
:	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
IS	O	O
A	O	O
WASTE	O	O
!	O	O

Category	O	O
:	O	O
Science	O	O
>	O	O
Astronomy	O	O

Asked	O	O
by	O	O
:	O	O
yheggy	B-PER	O
-	O	O
ga	O	O

List	O	O
Price	O	O
:	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
2.00	O	O

Posted	O	O
:	O	O
25	O	O
Oct	O	O
2004	O	O
18:32	O	O
PDT	O	O

Expires	O	O
:	O	O
24	O	O
Nov	O	O
2004	O	O
17:32	O	O
PST	O	O

Question	O	O
ID	O	O
:	O	O
420072	O	O

How	O	O
much	O	O
money	O	O
does	O	O
the	O	O
USA	B-ORG	B-LOC
give	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
per	O	O
year	O	O
?	O	O

Answer	O	O

Subject	O	O
:	O	O
Re	O	O
:	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
IS	O	O
A	O	O
WASTE	O	O
!	O	O

Answered	O	O
By	O	O
:	O	O
googlenut	B-PER	O
-	O	O
ga	O	O
on	O	O
25	O	O
Oct	O	O
2004	O	O
19:14	O	O
PDT	O	O

Hello	O	O
yheggy	B-PER	O
-	O	O
ga	O	O
,	O	O

On	O	O
September	O	O
21	O	O
,	O	O
2004	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
U.S.	B-ORG	B-ORG
Senate	I-ORG	I-ORG
Appropriations	I-ORG	O
Committee	I-ORG	O
approved	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
16.379	O	O
billion	O	O
in	O	O
funding	O	O
for	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
for	O	O
fiscal	O	O
year	O	O
2005	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
200	O	O
million	O	O
increase	O	O
over	O	O
what	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
received	O	O
for	O	O
fiscal	O	O
year	O	O
2004	O	O
.	O	O

U.S.	B-ORG	B-ORG
Senate	I-ORG	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG	O
on	I-ORG	O
Appropriations	I-ORG	O

Press	O	O
Release	O	O

"	O	O
National	B-ORG	O
Aeronautics	I-ORG	O
and	I-ORG	O
Space	I-ORG	O
Administration	I-ORG	O
(	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
)	O	O
:	O	O
is	O	O
funded	O	O
at	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
16.379	O	O
billion	O	O
,	O	O
an	O	O
increase	O	O
of	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
200	O	O
million	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
FY04	O	O
enacted	O	O
level	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
a	O	O
reduction	O	O
of	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
665	O	O
million	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
budget	O	O
request	O	O
.	O	O

An	O	O
additional	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
800	O	O
million	O	O
in	O	O
emergency	O	O
funding	O	O
was	O	O
added	O	O
for	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
during	O	O
the	O	O
Committee	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
consideration	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
bill	O	O
.	O	O

--	O	O
The	O	O
return	O	O
to	O	O
flight	O	O
activities	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Shuttle	O	O
program	O	O
are	O	O
funded	O	O
at	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
4.319	O	O
billion	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
requested	O	O
level	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
Administration	O	O
.	O	O

--	O	O
The	O	O
International	B-ORG	O
Space	I-ORG	O
Station	I-ORG	O
is	O	O
funded	O	O
at	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
1.6	O	O
billion	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
bill	O	O
reduces	O	O
ISS	B-ORG	O
operations	O	O
by	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
120	O	O
million	O	O
due	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
continued	O	O
reduced	O	O
capability	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
ISS	B-ORG	O
for	O	O
at	O	O
least	O	O
half	O	O
of	O	O
FY05	O	O
.	O	O

--	O	O
The	O	O
Moon	B-LOCpart	O
/	I-LOCpart	O
Mars	I-LOCpart	O
vision	O	O
:	O	O

---	O	O
The	O	O
Crew	B-MISC	O
Exploration	I-MISC	O
Vehicle	I-MISC	O
(	O	O
CEV	B-MISC	O
)	O	O
is	O	O
funded	O	O
at	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
268	O	O
million	O	O
.	O	O

---	O	O
A	O	O
lunar	O	O
exploration	O	O
mission	O	O
is	O	O
funded	O	O
at	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
20	O	O
million	O	O
.	O	O

---	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
10	O	O
million	O	O
is	O	O
provided	O	O
for	O	O
Centennial	O	O
Challenges	O	O
.	O	O

Neighborhood	B-ORG	O
Reinvestment	I-ORG	O
Corporation	I-ORG	O
(	O	O
NRC	B-ORG	O
)	O	O
:	O	O
is	O	O
funded	O	O
at	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
115	O	O
million	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
same	O	O
as	O	O
FY04	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
budget	O	O
request	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

Spacetoday.net	B-MISC	O

Senate	O	O
increases	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
funding	O	O

"	O	O
The	O	O
Senate	B-ORG	B-ORG
Appropriations	I-ORG	O
Committee	I-ORG	O
used	O	O
a	O	O
somewhat	O	O
controversial	O	O
technique	O	O
Tuesday	O	O
to	O	O
increase	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
fiscal	O	O
year	O	O
2005	O	O
budget	O	O
by	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
200	O	O
million	O	O
over	O	O
what	O	O
President	O	O
Bush	B-PER	O
requested	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
committee	O	O
voted	O	O
to	O	O
give	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
$	B-MISC	O
16.4	O	O
billion	O	O
in	O	O
2005	O	O
,	O	O
about	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
200	O	O
million	O	O
more	O	O
than	O	O
what	O	O
the	O	O
President	O	O
requested	O	O
and	O	O
over	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
1	O	O
billion	O	O
more	O	O
than	O	O
what	O	O
House	B-ORG	O
appropriators	O	O
approved	O	O
in	O	O
July	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

I	O	O
hope	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
found	O	O
this	O	O
information	O	O
helpful	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
any	O	O
questions	O	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
request	O	O
clarification	O	O
prior	O	O
to	O	O
rating	O	O
the	O	O
answer	O	O
.	O	O

Googlenut	B-PER	O

Google	B-ORG	O
Search	O	O
Terms	O	O
:	O	O

nasa	B-ORG	O
funding	O	O

Comments	O	O
Log	O	O
in	O	O
to	O	O
add	O	O
a	O	O
comment	O	O

Subject	O	O
:	O	O
Re	O	O
:	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
IS	O	O
A	O	O
WASTE	O	O
!	O	O

From	O	O
:	O	O
saem_aero	B-PER	O
-	O	O
ga	O	O
on	O	O
26	O	O
Oct	O	O
2004	O	O
18:11	O	O
PDT	O	O

Excellent	O	O
answer	O	O
googlenut	B-PER	O
.	O	O

Let	O	O
me	O	O
add	O	O
some	O	O
additional	O	O
info	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
can	O	O
get	O	O
details	O	O
about	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
spending	O	O
here	O	O
,	O	O
from	O	O
their	O	O
own	O	O
webpage	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
,	O	O
from	O	O
their	O	O
own	O	O
webpage	O	O
,	O	O
reasons	O	O
why	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
important	O	O
,	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
5th	O	O
grade	O	O
format	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
guess	O	O
if	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
someone	O	O
not	O	O
familiar	O	O
with	O	O
how	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
benefits	O	O
our	O	O
society	O	O
I	O	O
can	O	O
see	O	O
how	O	O
one	O	O
might	O	O
form	O	O
the	O	O
opinion	O	O
of	O	O
yheggy	B-PER	O
-	O	O
ga	O	O
.	O	O

Let	O	O
me	O	O
put	O	O
it	O	O
this	O	O
way	O	O
-	O	O
If	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
watched	O	O
TV	O	O
recently	O	O
,	O	O
crossed	O	O
a	O	O
modern	O	O
bridge	O	O
,	O	O
flown	O	O
in	O	O
an	O	O
airplane	O	O
,	O	O
recieved	O	O
any	O	O
form	O	O
of	O	O
modern	O	O
medicine	O	O
,	O	O
did	O	O
any	O	O
mathematics	O	O
,	O	O
drove	O	O
a	O	O
car	O	O
,	O	O
used	O	O
a	O	O
cellular	O	O
phone	O	O
,	O	O
etc.	O	O
then	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
somehow	O	O
directly	O	O
reaped	O	O
the	O	O
rewards	O	O
which	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
has	O	O
returned	O	O
to	O	O
us	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
has	O	O
a	O	O
large	O	O
outreach	O	O
program	O	O
for	O	O
education	O	O
,	O	O
some	O	O
people	O	O
believe	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
important	O	O
.	O	O

Best	O	O
,	O	O
Steve	B-PER	O
.	O	O

Subject	O	O
:	O	O
Re	O	O
:	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
IS	O	O
A	O	O
WASTE	O	O
!	O	O
From	O	O
:	O	O
jaqamofino	B-PER	O
-	O	O
ga	O	O
on	O	O
26	O	O
Apr	O	O
2005	O	O
06:02	O	O
PDT	O	O

i	O	O
believe	O	O
that	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
HUGE	O	O
waste	O	O
of	O	O
tax	O	O
payers	O	O
'	O	O
money	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
there	O	O
are	O	O
so	O	O
many	O	O
huge	O	O
wastes	O	O
of	O	O
tax	O	O
payer	O	O
monies	O	O
,	O	O
that	O	O
i	O	O
find	O	O
it	O	O
best	O	O
not	O	O
to	O	O
think	O	O
about	O	O
it	O	O
.	O	O

i	O	O
also	O	O
think	O	O
the	O	O
National	B-ORG	O
Endowment	I-ORG	O
for	I-ORG	O
the	I-ORG	O
Arts	I-ORG	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
waste	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
i	O	O
guess	O	O
i	O	O
would	O	O
rather	O	O
see	O	O
my	O	O
money	O	O
go	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
NEA	B-ORG	O
than	O	O
NASA	B-ORG	O
.	O	O

of	O	O
course	O	O
,	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
perfect	O	O
world	O	O
,	O	O
tax	O	O
payers	O	O
'	O	O
money	O	O
would	O	O
go	O	O
toward	O	O
some	O	O
sort	O	O
of	O	O
national	O	O
healthcare	O	O
program	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
housing	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
homeless	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
far	O	O
from	O	O
a	O	O
perfect	O	O
world	O	O
.	O	O

in	O	O
response	O	O
to	O	O
Steve	B-PER	O
's	I-PER	O
comment	O	O
:	O	O
do	O	O
you	O	O
really	O	O
believe	O	O
that	O	O
spending	O	O
trillions	O	O
on	O	O
space	O	O
exploration	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
years	O	O
was	O	O
the	O	O
ONLY	O	O
way	O	O
to	O	O
invent	O	O
the	O	O
cellfone	O	O
?	O	O

and	O	O
bridges	O	O
???	O	O

i	O	O
find	O	O
that	O	O
extremely	O	O
hard	O	O
to	O	O
believe	O	O
.	O	O

i	O	O
think	O	O
it	O	O
could	O	O
have	O	O
been	O	O
done	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
much	O	O
more	O	O
cost	O	O
efficient	O	O
way	O	O
,	O	O
right	O	O
here	O	O
on	O	O
bad	O	O
-	O	O
old	O	O
-	O	O
planet	O	O
-	O	O
earth	O	O
.	O	O

just	O	O
my	O	O
two	O	O
cents	O	O
.	O	O

thanks	O	O
for	O	O
listening	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
take	O	O
a	O	O
moment	O	O
to	O	O
read	O	O
this	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
realize	O	O
that	O	O
it	O	O
may	O	O
sound	O	O
strange	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
desparate	O	O
in	O	O
our	O	O
efforts	O	O
and	O	O
are	O	O
willing	O	O
to	O	O
try	O	O
anything	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
our	O	O
dear	O	O
sick	O	O
friend	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
costs	O	O
absolutely	O	O
nothing	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
will	O	O
take	O	O
about	O	O
one	O	O
minute	O	O
of	O	O
your	O	O
time	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
is	O	O
not	O	O
a	O	O
hoax	O	O
,	O	O
as	O	O
so	O	O
many	O	O
of	O	O
these	O	O
emails	O	O
actully	O	O
are	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
quick	O	O
summary	O	O
,	O	O
Beyond	B-ORG	O
Control	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
local	O	O
band	O	O
in	O	O
our	O	O
area	O	O
,	O	O
is	O	O
sponoring	O	O
a	O	O
benefit	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
cancer	O	O
victim	O	O
whose	O	O
benefits	O	O
have	O	O
run	O	O
out	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
band	O	O
is	O	O
involved	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
local	O	O
competition	O	O
which	O	O
promises	O	O
a	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
5000	O	O
first	O	O
prize	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
they	O	O
would	O	O
like	O	O
to	O	O
win	O	O
in	O	O
order	O	O
to	O	O
donate	O	O
it	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
benefit	O	O
fund	O	O
which	O	O
they	O	O
have	O	O
started	O	O
.	O	O

Below	O	O
are	O	O
some	O	O
emails	O	O
to	O	O
friends	O	O
explaining	O	O
a	O	O
little	O	O
more	O	O
about	O	O
this	O	O
effort	O	O
.	O	O

What	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
is	O	O
solicit	O	O
votes	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
band	O	O
,	O	O
in	O	O
order	O	O
to	O	O
put	O	O
them	O	O
in	O	O
first	O	O
place	O	O
.	O	O

They	O	O
are	O	O
currently	O	O
in	O	O
third	O	O
place	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
need	O	O
your	O	O
help	O	O
so	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
prize	O	O
money	O	O
can	O	O
be	O	O
used	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
humanatarian	O	O
cause	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
can	O	O
vote	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
following	O	O
link	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
will	O	O
only	O	O
take	O	O
a	O	O
few	O	O
seconds	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
take	O	O
a	O	O
moment	O	O
to	O	O
click	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
link	O	O
below	O	O
and	O	O
cast	O	O
your	O	O
vote	O	O
for	O	O
Beyond	B-ORG	O
Control	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

Thank	O	O
you	O	O
in	O	O
advance	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
contribution	O	O
to	O	O
this	O	O
effort	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
,	O	O
please	O	O
pass	O	O
this	O	O
along	O	O
to	O	O
everyone	O	O
you	O	O
know	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
your	O	O
email	O	O
contacts	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
need	O	O
the	O	O
power	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
internet	O	O
to	O	O
pull	O	O
this	O	O
off	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
web	O	O
site	O	O
is	O	O

You	O	O
can	O	O
check	O	O
the	O	O
validity	O	O
of	O	O
all	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
Beyond	B-ORG	O
Control	I-ORG	O
website	O	O
.	O	O

That	O	O
address	O	O
is	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
home	O	O
page	O	O
for	O	O
Rockin	B-ORG	O
on	I-ORG	O
the	I-ORG	O
River	I-ORG	O
is	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
it	O	O
lists	O	O
all	O	O
the	O	O
acts	O	O
scheduled	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
season	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
can	O	O
check	O	O
that	O	O
out	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
,	O	O
to	O	O
confirm	O	O
that	O	O
this	O	O
is	O	O
all	O	O
real	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
worthy	O	O
cause	O	O
.	O	O

Abby	B-PER	O
is	O	O
our	O	O
beloved	O	O
friend	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
trying	O	O
to	O	O
raise	O	O
money	O	O
for	O	O
her	O	O
any	O	O
way	O	O
we	O	O
can	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
this	O	O
prize	O	O
money	O	O
is	O	O
important	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
her	O	O
continue	O	O
to	O	O
receive	O	O
her	O	O
life	O	O
-	O	O
saving	O	O
treatments	O	O
.	O	O

Many	O	O
thanks	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
may	O	O
God	O	O
bless	O	O
you	O	O
all	O	O
and	O	O
keep	O	O
you	O	O
healthy	O	O
.	O	O

Here	O	O
are	O	O
some	O	O
emails	O	O
we	O	O
have	O	O
sent	O	O
,	O	O
along	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
flyer	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Benefit	O	O
fund	O	O
raiser	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
holding	O	O
in	O	O
June	O	O
,	O	O
just	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
information	O	O
.	O	O

Roy	B-PER	O
,	O	O

I	O	O
am	O	O
sending	O	O
you	O	O
some	O	O
info	O	O
that	O	O
I	O	O
have	O	O
passed	O	O
along	O	O
regarding	O	O
the	O	O
effort	O	O
to	O	O
win	O	O
the	O	O
cash	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
fund	O	O
raising	O	O
benefit	O	O
.	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
can	O	O
pass	O	O
this	O	O
info	O	O
along	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
ask	O	O
everyone	O	O
you	O	O
know	O	O
to	O	O
forward	O	O
it	O	O
to	O	O
their	O	O
contacts	O	O
,	O	O
etc	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
may	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
shot	O	O
at	O	O
pulling	O	O
this	O	O
off	O	O
.	O	O

Thanks	O	O
,	O	O

Fred	B-PER	O

John	B-PER	O
,	O	O

I	O	O
will	O	O
attach	O	O
the	O	O
letter	O	O
explaining	O	O
the	O	O
benefit	O	O
we	O	O
are	O	O
sponsoring	O	O
.	O	O

There	O	O
is	O	O
a	O	O
link	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
contest	O	O
page	O	O
.	O	O

Any	O	O
help	O	O
in	O	O
distributing	O	O
this	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
greatly	O	O
appreciated	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
certainly	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
good	O	O
cause	O	O
.	O	O

Abby	B-PER	O
needs	O	O
to	O	O
fly	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	O
York	I-LOC	O
twice	O	O
a	O	O
month	O	O
for	O	O
these	O	O
treatments	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
her	O	O
time	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
Federal	O	O
Grant	O	O
program	O	O
has	O	O
expired	O	O
.	O	O

She	O	O
does	O	O
n't	O	O
have	O	O
the	O	O
funds	O	O
to	O	O
continue	O	O
without	O	O
the	O	O
grant	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
without	O	O
these	O	O
treatments	O	O
,	O	O
her	O	O
prognosis	O	O
is	O	O
grim	O	O
.	O	O

I	O	O
hope	O	O
you	O	O
have	O	O
a	O	O
huge	O	O
network	O	O
.	O	O

Also	O	O
encourage	O	O
your	O	O
recipients	O	O
to	O	O
forward	O	O
this	O	O
along	O	O
to	O	O
their	O	O
contacts	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
so	O	O
on	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
movement	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
her	O	O
grows	O	O
exponentially	O	O
.	O	O

We	O	O
must	O	O
finish	O	O
in	O	O
first	O	O
place	O	O
in	O	O
order	O	O
to	O	O
contribute	O	O
the	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
5000	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
benefit	O	O
fund	O	O
.	O	O

Thank	O	O
you	O	O
so	O	O
much	O	O
for	O	O
caring	O	O
enough	O	O
to	O	O
offer	O	O
your	O	O
help	O	O
.	O	O

Fred	B-PER	O

BENEFIT	O	O
AUCTION	O	O
&	O	O
RAFFLE	O	O
FOR	O	O
ABBY	B-PER	O
FREEMAN	I-PER	O

WHEN	O	O
:	O	O
JUNE	O	O
12	O	O
,	O	O
2005	O	O
,	O	O
2:00	O	O
P.M.	O	O
TO	O	O
2:00	O	O
A.M.	O	O

WHERE	O	O
:	O	O
MAIN	B-ORG	B-LOC
STREET	I-ORG	I-LOC
SALOON	I-ORG	O

ADMISSION	O	O
:	O	O
DONATIONS	O	O
AT	O	O
THE	O	O
DOOR	O	O

Abby	B-PER	O
Freeman	I-PER	O
is	O	O
our	O	O
good	O	O
friend	O	O
who	O	O
has	O	O
non-Hodgkin	B-PERpart	O
lymphoma	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
she	O	O
needs	O	O
your	O	O
help	O	O
!	O	O

Her	O	O
grant	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
life	O	O
saving	O	O
treatments	O	O
she	O	O
needs	O	O
has	O	O
run	O	O
out	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
we	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
her	O	O
to	O	O
continue	O	O
to	O	O
receive	O	O
these	O	O
treatments	O	O
.	O	O

Abby	B-PER	O
has	O	O
three	O	O
wonderful	O	O
young	O	O
children	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
friends	O	O
who	O	O
love	O	O
her	O	O
and	O	O
need	O	O
her	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
help	O	O
us	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
her	O	O
win	O	O
this	O	O
fight	O	O
.	O	O

With	O	O
your	O	O
help	O	O
,	O	O
we	O	O
know	O	O
she	O	O
can	O	O
do	O	O
it	O	O
!!	O	O

We	O	O
'll	O	O
have	O	O
four	O	O
bands	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
Big	B-PER	O
D	I-PER	O
is	O	O
cookin'	O	O
.....	O	O
lots	O	O
of	O	O
fun	O	O
and	O	O
great	O	O
prizes	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
is	O	O
an	O	O
event	O	O
you	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
miss	O	O
!!	O	O

Bands	O	O
,	O	O
food	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
prizes	O	O
are	O	O
sponsored	O	O
by	O	O
Beyond	B-ORG	O
Control	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
who	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
competing	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
Band	B-MISC	O
of	I-MISC	O
the	O	I-MISC
Year	I-MISC	O
Contest	I-MISC	O
at	O	O
the	O	O
River	B-ORG	O
Front	I-ORG	O
Festival	I-ORG	O
in	O	O
Cuyahoga	B-LOC	O
Falls	I-LOC	O
on	O	O
July	O	O
1	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
winner	O	O
of	O	O
this	O	O
competition	O	O
will	O	O
receive	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
5000	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
Beyond	B-ORG	O
Control	I-ORG	O
hopes	O	O
to	O	O
win	O	O
in	O	O
order	O	O
to	O	O
donate	O	O
it	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
Abby	B-PER	O
Freeman	I-PER	O
fund	O	O
.	O	O

Please	O	O
help	O	O
us	O	O
by	O	O
logging	O	O
onto	O	O
the	O	O
Rockin	B-ORG	O
on	I-ORG	O
the	I-ORG	O
River	I-ORG	O
website	O	O
at	O	O
.	O	O

Cast	O	O
a	O	O
vote	O	O
for	O	O
Beyond	B-ORG	O
Control	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
help	O	O
us	O	O
provide	O	O
Abby	B-PER	O
with	O	O
her	O	O
life	O	O
saving	O	O
treatments	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

Donations	O	O
can	O	O
also	O	O
be	O	O
made	O	O
through	O	O
Charter	B-ORG	O
One	I-ORG	O
Bank	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

Make	O	O
checks	O	O
payable	O	O
to	O	O
Kendel	B-PER	O
Bunnell	I-PER	O
c	O	O
/	O	O
o	O	O
Benefit	B-ORG	O
for	I-ORG	O
Abby	I-ORG	B-PER
Freeman	I-ORG	I-PER

By	O	O
Richard	B-PER	O
Spencer	I-PER	O

(	O	O
Filed	O	O
:	O	O
19/11/2004	O	O
)	O	O

China	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
insatiable	O	O
demand	O	O
for	O	O
energy	O	O
is	O	O
prompting	O	O
fears	O	O
of	O	O
financial	O	O
and	O	O
diplomatic	O	O
collisions	O	O
around	O	O
the	O	O
globe	O	O
as	O	O
it	O	O
seeks	O	O
reliable	O	O
supplies	O	O
of	O	O
oil	O	O
from	O	O
as	O	O
far	O	O
away	O	O
as	O	O
Brazil	B-LOC	O
and	O	O
Sudan	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

An	O	O
intrusion	O	O
into	O	O
Japanese	B-LOCderiv	O
territorial	O	O
waters	O	O
by	O	O
a	O	O
Chinese	B-LOCderiv	O
nuclear	O	O
submarine	O	O
last	O	O
week	O	O
and	O	O
a	O	O
trade	O	O
deal	O	O
with	O	O
Brazil	B-ORG	B-LOC
are	O	O
the	O	O
latest	O	O
apparently	O	O
unconnected	O	O
consequences	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
soaring	O	O
economic	O	O
growth	O	O
.	O	O

Increased	O	O
car	O	O
usage	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	O
is	O	O
creating	O	O
a	O	O
high	O	O
demand	O	O
for	O	O
petrol	O	O

The	O	O
connection	O	O
,	O	O
however	O	O
,	O	O
lies	O	O
in	O	O
an	O	O
order	O	O
issued	O	O
last	O	O
year	O	O
by	O	O
President	O	O
Hu	B-PER	O
Jintao	I-PER	O
to	O	O
seek	O	O
secure	O	O
oil	O	O
supplies	O	O
abroad	O	O
-	O	O
preferably	O	O
ones	O	O
which	O	O
could	O	O
not	O	O
be	O	O
stopped	O	O
by	O	O
America	B-ORG	B-LOC
in	O	O
case	O	O
of	O	O
conflict	O	O
over	O	O
Taiwan	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
submarine	O	O
incident	O	O
was	O	O
put	O	O
down	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
"	O	O
technical	O	O
error	O	O
"	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
Chinese	B-LOCderiv	O
government	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
apologised	O	O
to	O	O
Japan	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

But	O	O
even	O	O
before	O	O
the	O	O
incident	O	O
the	O	O
People	B-ORG	O
's	I-ORG	O
Daily	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
government	O	O
mouthpiece	O	O
,	O	O
had	O	O
commented	O	O
that	O	O
competition	O	O
over	O	O
the	O	O
East	B-LOC	O
China	I-LOC	B-LOC
Sea	I-LOC	O
between	O	O
the	O	O
two	O	O
countries	O	O
was	O	O
"	O	O
only	O	O
a	O	O
prelude	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
game	O	O
between	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
and	O	O
Japan	B-ORG	B-LOC
in	O	O
the	O	O
arena	O	O
of	O	O
international	O	O
energy	O	O
"	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
Brazil	B-LOC	O
trade	O	O
deal	O	O
included	O	O
funding	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
joint	O	O
oil	O	O
-	O	O
drilling	O	O
and	O	O
pipeline	O	O
programme	O	O
at	O	O
a	O	O
cost	O	O
that	O	O
experts	O	O
said	O	O
would	O	O
add	O	O
up	O	O
to	O	O
three	O	O
times	O	O
the	O	O
cost	O	O
of	O	O
simply	O	O
buying	O	O
oil	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
market	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
West	B-ORG	B-LOC
,	O	O
however	O	O
,	O	O
has	O	O
paid	O	O
little	O	O
attention	O	O
to	O	O
these	O	O
developments	O	O
.	O	O

For	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-ORG	B-LOC
States	I-ORG	I-LOC
and	O	O
Europe	B-ORG	B-LOC
are	O	O
far	O	O
more	O	O
concerned	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
even	O	O
more	O	O
sensitive	O	O
issues	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
relations	O	O
with	O	O
"	O	O
pariah	O	O
states	O	O
"	O	O
.	O	O

In	O	O
September	O	O
,	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
threatened	O	O
to	O	O
veto	O	O
any	O	O
move	O	O
to	O	O
impose	O	O
sanctions	O	O
on	O	O
Sudan	B-ORG	B-LOC
over	O	O
the	O	O
atrocities	O	O
in	O	O
Darfur	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
has	O	O
invested	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
3	O	O
billion	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
African	B-LOCderiv	O
country	O	O
's	O	O
oil	O	O
industry	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
supplies	O	O
it	O	O
with	O	O
seven	O	O
per	O	O
cent	O	O
of	O	O
its	O	O
needs	O	O
.	O	O

Then	O	O
,	O	O
this	O	O
month	O	O
,	O	O
it	O	O
said	O	O
that	O	O
it	O	O
opposed	O	O
moves	O	O
to	O	O
refer	O	O
Iran	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
nuclear	O	O
stand	O	O
-	O	O
off	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
International	B-ORG	O
Atomic	I-ORG	O
Energy	I-ORG	O
Agency	I-ORG	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-ORG	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG	I-ORG
Security	I-ORG	O
Council	I-ORG	O
.	O	O

A	O	O
week	O	O
before	O	O
,	O	O
China	B-LOC	O
's	I-LOC	O
second	O	O
biggest	O	O
state	O	O
oil	O	O
firm	O	O
had	O	O
signed	O	O
a	O	O
$	B-MISC	O
70	O	O
billion	O	O
deal	O	O
for	O	O
oilfield	O	O
and	O	O
natural	O	O
gas	O	O
development	O	O
with	O	O
Iran	B-ORG	B-LOC
,	O	O
which	O	O
already	O	O
supplies	O	O
13	O	O
per	O	O
cent	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
needs	O	O
.	O	O

China	B-LOC	O
has	O	O
its	O	O
own	O	O
reserves	O	O
of	O	O
oil	O	O
and	O	O
natural	O	O
gas	O	O
and	O	O
once	O	O
was	O	O
a	O	O
net	O	O
oil	O	O
exporter	O	O
.	O	O

But	O	O
as	O	O
its	O	O
economy	O	O
has	O	O
expanded	O	O
by	O	O
an	O	O
average	O	O
of	O	O
nine	O	O
per	O	O
cent	O	O
per	O	O
year	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
last	O	O
two	O	O
decades	O	O
,	O	O
so	O	O
has	O	O
its	O	O
demand	O	O
for	O	O
energy	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
year	O	O
it	O	O
overtook	O	O
Japan	B-ORG	B-LOC
as	O	O
the	O	O
world	O	O
's	O	O
second	O	O
largest	O	O
consumer	O	O
of	O	O
energy	O	O
,	O	O
behind	O	O
the	O	O
US	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

Its	O	O
projected	O	O
demand	O	O
,	O	O
boosted	O	O
by	O	O
a	O	O
huge	O	O
rise	O	O
in	O	O
car	O	O
ownership	O	O
as	O	O
well	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
need	O	O
to	O	O
find	O	O
alternatives	O	O
to	O	O
polluting	O	O
coal	O	O
for	O	O
electricity	O	O
generation	O	O
,	O	O
has	O	O
contributed	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
surge	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
price	O	O
of	O	O
oil	O	O
this	O	O
year	O	O
.	O	O

Shortages	O	O
are	O	O
already	O	O
leading	O	O
to	O	O
power	O	O
cuts	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
big	O	O
cities	O	O
.	O	O

Since	O	O
President	O	O
Hu	B-PER	O
ordered	O	O
state	O	O
-	O	O
owned	O	O
oil	O	O
firms	O	O
to	O	O
"	O	O
go	O	O
abroad	O	O
"	O	O
to	O	O
ensure	O	O
supply	O	O
,	O	O
they	O	O
have	O	O
begun	O	O
drilling	O	O
for	O	O
gas	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
East	B-LOC	O
China	I-LOC	B-LOC
Sea	I-LOC	O
,	O	O
just	O	O
west	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
line	O	O
that	O	O
Japan	B-ORG	B-LOC
regards	O	O
as	O	O
its	O	O
border	O	O
.	O	O

Japan	B-ORG	B-LOC
protested	O	O
,	O	O
to	O	O
no	O	O
avail	O	O
,	O	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
project	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
joint	O	O
one	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
two	O	O
are	O	O
also	O	O
set	O	O
to	O	O
clash	O	O
over	O	O
Russia	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
oil	O	O
wealth	O	O
.	O	O

China	B-ORG	B-LOC
is	O	O
furious	O	O
that	O	O
Japan	B-ORG	B-LOC
has	O	O
outbid	O	O
it	O	O
in	O	O
their	O	O
battle	O	O
to	O	O
determine	O	O
the	O	O
route	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
pipeline	O	O
that	O	O
Russia	B-ORG	B-LOC
intends	O	O
to	O	O
build	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
Far	B-LOC	O
East	I-LOC	O
.	O	O

Japan	B-ORG	B-LOC
favoured	O	O
a	O	O
route	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
sea	O	O
,	O	O
enabling	O	O
oil	O	O
to	O	O
be	O	O
shipped	O	O
to	O	O
both	O	O
Japan	B-LOC	O
and	O	O
China	B-LOC	O
.	O	O

China	B-ORG	B-LOC
wanted	O	O
an	O	O
overland	O	O
route	O	O
through	O	O
its	O	O
own	O	O
territory	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
would	O	O
give	O	O
it	O	O
ultimate	O	O
control	O	O
if	O	O
hostilities	O	O
broke	O	O
out	O	O
.	O	O

Increasingly	O	O
,	O	O
analysts	O	O
are	O	O
saying	O	O
that	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
efforts	O	O
have	O	O
gone	O	O
beyond	O	O
what	O	O
is	O	O
safe	O	O
or	O	O
even	O	O
in	O	O
its	O	O
own	O	O
interests	O	O
.	O	O

Claude	B-PER	O
Mandil	I-PER	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
executive	O	O
director	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
International	B-ORG	O
Energy	I-ORG	O
Agency	I-ORG	O
in	O	O
Paris	B-LOC	O
,	O	O
said	O	O
the	O	O
reserves	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
East	B-LOC	O
China	I-LOC	B-LOC
Sea	I-LOC	O
were	O	O
hardly	O	O
worth	O	O
the	O	O
trouble	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
Nobody	O	O
thinks	O	O
that	O	O
there	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
lot	O	O
of	O	O
oil	O	O
and	O	O
gas	O	O
in	O	O
this	O	O
part	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
world	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
he	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
It	O	O
may	O	O
be	O	O
a	O	O
difficult	O	O
political	O	O
issue	O	O
but	O	O
I	O	O
do	O	O
n't	O	O
think	O	O
the	O	O
energy	O	O
content	O	O
is	O	O
worthwhile	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

Eurasia	B-ORG	B-LOC
Group	I-ORG	O
,	O	O
a	O	O
New	B-LOCpart	O
York	I-LOCpart	O
-	I-LOCpart	O
based	I-LOCpart	O
firm	O	O
of	O	O
political	O	O
analysts	O	O
,	O	O
said	O	O
its	O	O
oil	O	O
experts	O	O
worked	O	O
out	O	O
that	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
was	O	O
paying	O	O
such	O	O
an	O	O
inflated	O	O
price	O	O
for	O	O
its	O	O
investment	O	O
in	O	O
Brazil	B-LOC	O
that	O	O
the	O	O
cost	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
oil	O	O
it	O	O
ended	O	O
up	O	O
with	O	O
was	O	O
three	O	O
times	O	O
the	O	O
market	O	O
price	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
If	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
economy	O	O
falters	O	O
,	O	O
which	O	O
,	O	O
in	O	O
my	O	O
view	O	O
,	O	O
appears	O	O
increasingly	O	O
likely	O	O
,	O	O
then	O	O
commodity	O	O
prices	O	O
will	O	O
plummet	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
with	O	O
them	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
value	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
assets	O	O
that	O	O
produce	O	O
them	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
Jason	B-PER	O
Kindopp	I-PER	O
,	O	O
Eurasia	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
lead	O	O
China	B-LOC	O
analyst	O	O
,	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
Beijing	B-ORG	B-LOC
may	O	O
end	O	O
up	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
early	O	O
1990s	O	O
Japan	B-LOC	O
situation	O	O
,	O	O
where	O	O
it	O	O
is	O	O
forced	O	O
to	O	O
sell	O	O
recently	O	O
purchased	O	O
overseas	O	O
assets	O	O
for	O	O
a	O	O
fraction	O	O
of	O	O
what	O	O
it	O	O
paid	O	O
for	O	O
them	O	O
.	O	O
"	O	O

China	B-ORG	B-LOC
's	I-ORG	I-LOC
wider	O	O
aggression	O	O
to	O	O
secure	O	O
oil	O	O
and	O	O
gas	O	O
was	O	O
the	O	O
greatest	O	O
threat	O	O
to	O	O
its	O	O
international	O	O
standing	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
next	O	O
decade	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
Sudan	B-ORG	B-LOC
is	O	O
the	O	O
primary	O	O
example	O	O
,	O	O
"	O	O
he	O	O
said	O	O
.	O	O

"	O	O
It	O	O
marks	O	O
the	O	O
first	O	O
time	O	O
in	O	O
recent	O	O
years	O	O
that	O	O
China	B-ORG	B-LOC
has	O	O
promised	O	O
to	O	O
wield	O	O
its	O	O
veto	O	O
power	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
UN	B-ORG	B-ORG
Security	I-ORG	O
Council	I-ORG	O
against	O	O
a	O	O
petition	O	O
initiated	O	O
by	O	O
the	O	O
United	B-ORG	B-LOC
States	I-ORG	I-LOC
and	O	O
backed	O	O
by	O	O
France	B-ORG	B-LOC
and	O	O
Great	B-ORG	B-LOC
Britain	I-ORG	I-LOC
.	O	O
"	O	O

Email	O	O
:	O	O
dharmad...@gmail.com	B-PER	O

Visualizations	O	O
as	O	O
a	O	O
helpful	O	O
beginning	O	O
technique	O	O

-----------------------------------------------	O	O

If	O	O
you	O	O
consider	O	O
that	O	O
you	O	O
still	O	O
need	O	O
the	O	O
assistance	O	O
of	O	O
other	O	O
visualizations	O	O
to	O	O
help	O	O
the	O	O
mind	O	O
feel	O	O
the	O	O
spirit	O	O
of	O	O
transcendence	O	O
,	O	O
try	O	O
the	O	O
following	O	O
before	O	O
moving	O	O
onto	O	O
the	O	O
more	O	O
formal	O	O
method	O	O
below	O	O
.	O	O

Visualisations	O	O
can	O	O
be	O	O
as	O	O
useful	O	O
tools	O	O
,	O	O
but	O	O
meditation	O	O
is	O	O
more	O	O
than	O	O
that	O	O
.	O	O

Meditation	O	O
has	O	O
to	O	O
do	O	O
with	O	O
what	O	O
is	O	O
called	O	O
ideation	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
is	O	O
always	O	O
good	O	O
to	O	O
stick	O	O
to	O	O
a	O	O
formal	O	O
intense	O	O
meditation	O	O
practice	O	O
like	O	O
the	O	O
one	O	O
for	O	O
beginners	O	O
described	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
MP3	O	O
file	O	O
that	O	O
follows	O	O
after	O	O
the	O	O
visualisations	O	O
.	O	O

Find	O	O
a	O	O
comfortable	O	O
place	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
floor	O	O
and	O	O
sit	O	O
with	O	O
your	O	O
legs	O	O
crossed	O	O
.	O	O

Place	O	O
your	O	O
hands	O	O
one	O	O
on	O	O
top	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
other	O	O
in	O	O
your	O	O
lap	O	O
,	O	O
keep	O	O
your	O	O
back	O	O
straight	O	O
,	O	O
keep	O	O
eyes	O	O
closed	O	O
and	O	O
keep	O	O
tongue	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
roof	O	O
of	O	O
your	O	O
mouth	O	O
.	O	O

Your	O	O
breathing	O	O
should	O	O
be	O	O
calm	O	O
and	O	O
relaxed	O	O
,	O	O
through	O	O
the	O	O
nose	O	O
.	O	O

Spend	O	O
a	O	O
minute	O	O
or	O	O
so	O	O
concentrating	O	O
on	O	O
your	O	O
breath	O	O
,	O	O
feeling	O	O
the	O	O
air	O	O
flowing	O	O
through	O	O
your	O	O
nostrils	O	O
.	O	O

1	O	O
.	O	O
Warm	O	O
Sun	O	O
Visualization	O	O

Continue	O	O
to	O	O
breathe	O	O
slowly	O	O
and	O	O
deeply	O	O
.	O	O

With	O	O
each	O	O
breath	O	O
,	O	O
feel	O	O
the	O	O
muscles	O	O
in	O	O
your	O	O
body	O	O
becoming	O	O
lighter	O	O
and	O	O
lighter	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
also	O	O
your	O	O
external	O	O
motor	O	O
and	O	O
sensory	O	O
organs	O	O
are	O	O
feeling	O	O
like	O	O
they	O	O
are	O	O
withdrawing	O	O
from	O	O
the	O	O
world	O	O
into	O	O
a	O	O
special	O	O
inner	O	O
quietness	O	O
.	O	O

Imagine	O	O
the	O	O
tension	O	O
melting	O	O
away	O	O
as	O	O
you	O	O
continue	O	O
breathing	O	O
rhythmically	O	O
and	O	O
naturally	O	O
.	O	O

Picture	O	O
yourself	O	O
sitting	O	O
on	O	O
a	O	O
warm	O	O
,	O	O
tropical	O	O
beach	O	O
basking	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
glow	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
sun	O	O
...	O	O
.	O	O

Visualize	O	O
the	O	O
vivid	O	O
,	O	O
beautiful	O	O
colours	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
earth	O	O
(	O	O
its	O	O
flowers	O	O
and	O	O
plants	O	O
)	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
sea	O	O
next	O	O
to	O	O
you	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
sky	O	O
above	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

Feel	O	O
yourself	O	O
floating	O	O
above	O	O
the	O	O
earth	O	O
and	O	O
sea	O	O
.	O	O

As	O	O
you	O	O
sit	O	O
above	O	O
the	O	O
world	O	O
,	O	O
the	O	O
warmth	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
golden	O	O
sun	O	O
penetrates	O	O
your	O	O
body	O	O
and	O	O
makes	O	O
you	O	O
feel	O	O
warmer	O	O
and	O	O
warmer	O	O
.	O	O

It	O	O
surrounds	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
golden	O	O
rays	O	O
feel	O	O
soft	O	O
and	O	O
soothing	O	O
.	O	O

Now	O	O
you	O	O
are	O	O
far	O	O
above	O	O
the	O	O
earth	O	O
-	O	O
into	O	O
space	O	O
.	O	O

Everything	O	O
around	O	O
you	O	O
is	O	O
so	O	O
vast	O	O
.	O	O

Yet	O	O
,	O	O
there	O	O
is	O	O
warmth	O	O
and	O	O
a	O	O
familiarity	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
vastness	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
merge	O	O
your	O	O
mind	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
greater	O	O
universal	O	O
Mind	O	O
that	O	O
surrounds	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

Continue	O	O
to	O	O
ideate	O	O
on	O	O
this	O	O
intense	O	O
desire	O	O
for	O	O
your	O	O
mind	O	O
to	O	O
merge	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
that	O	O
universal	O	O
Consciousness	O	O
.	O	O

And	O	O
while	O	O
doing	O	O
so	O	O
continue	O	O
using	O	O
the	O	O
Baba	O	O
Nam	O	O
Kevalam	O	O
mantra	O	O
(	O	O
breathe	O	O
in	O	O
with	O	O
Baba	O	O
Nam	O	O
,	O	O
breathe	O	O
out	O	O
with	O	O
Kevalam	O	O
)	O	O
.	O	O

Try	O	O
this	O	O
for	O	O
5	O	O
to	O	O
10	O	O
minutes	O	O
.	O	O

Now	O	O
come	O	O
back	O	O
to	O	O
earth	O	O
again	O	O
-	O	O
slowly	O	O
.	O	O

Imagine	O	O
yourself	O	O
sitting	O	O
on	O	O
the	O	O
beach	O	O
serenely	O	O
and	O	O
restfully	O	O
.	O	O

Your	O	O
muscles	O	O
are	O	O
loose	O	O
and	O	O
limp	O	O
.	O	O

Feel	O	O
your	O	O
body	O	O
sinking	O	O
slightly	O	O
into	O	O
the	O	O
sand	O	O
making	O	O
that	O	O
earthly	O	O
connection	O	O
again	O	O
.	O	O

The	O	O
sun	O	O
's	O	O
rays	O	O
and	O	O
warmth	O	O
are	O	O
still	O	O
with	O	O
you	O	O
,	O	O
surrounding	O	O
you	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
are	O	O
in	O	O
a	O	O
state	O	O
of	O	O
peace	O	O
and	O	O
relaxation	O	O
.	O	O

With	O	O
each	O	O
breath	O	O
,	O	O
watch	O	O
your	O	O
body	O	O
and	O	O
ensure	O	O
that	O	O
it	O	O
remains	O	O
relaxed	O	O
-	O	O
at	O	O
peace	O	O
.	O	O

Continue	O	O
to	O	O
feel	O	O
the	O	O
warmth	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
sunlight	O	O
all	O	O
over	O	O
your	O	O
body	O	O
,	O	O
warming	O	O
you	O	O
deeply	O	O
and	O	O
gently	O	O
.	O	O

You	O	O
want	O	O
to	O	O
bring	O	O
something	O	O
back	O	O
with	O	O
you	O	O
from	O	O
your	O	O
deep	O	O
space	O	O
experience	O	O
where	O	O
you	O	O
sensed	O	O
your	O	O
mind	O	O
merging	O	O
with	O	O
the	O	O
universal	O	O
Mind	O	O
.	O	O

This	O	O
will	O	O
be	O	O
the	O	O
warmth	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
sun	O	O
-	O	O
a	O	O
close	O	O
reminder	O	O
and	O	O
link	O	O
between	O	O
earth	O	O
and	O	O
the	O	O
infinite	O	O
space	O	O
.	O	O

Visualize	O	O
the	O	O
inside	O	O
of	O	O
your	O	O
body	O	O
bathed	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
golden	O	O
light	O	O
,	O	O
absorbing	O	O
every	O	O
ray	O	O
and	O	O
glowing	O	O
as	O	O
radiantly	O	O
as	O	O
the	O	O
sun	O	O
.	O	O
